<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>marketing strategy &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/marketing-strategy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Email marketing and the numbers you can count on</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/24/2014/email-marketing-and-the-numbers-you-can-count-on/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 14:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[email marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[infographic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3926</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There’s a piece of paper I keep pinned at my desk.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There’s a piece of paper I keep pinned at my desk. It’s filled with numbers, stats to be precise, and serves as a daily reminder that email marketing is a powerful tool. One that should be at the heart of every suitable strategic campaign, integrated as a conversation tool in nurturing customers.</p>
<p>The rise of social networks, mobile and instant messaging has shifted focus away from email, and while these channels are becoming increasingly important for marketers to engage on, it remains essential to harness the force of the mighty inbox.</p>
<p>When planned properly and executed in the right way, emails become a highly targeted, cost-effective and powerful communicator that gets results.</p>
<p>Here, the numbers I’ve collected speak for themselves.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Infographic31.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-3948" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Infographic31.jpg" alt="Infographic3[1]" width="470" height="1625" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stay Classy, America</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/27/2014/stay-classy-america/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 17:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anchorman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ben & Jerry's]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dodge Durango]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[olympics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ron Burgundy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3429</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Ron Burgundy is everywhere!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ron Burgundy is everywhere!</p>
<p>The promotion of Anchorman 2 was unconventional to say the least. Ron appeared as a band member on Conan O&#8217;Brien, and in numerous Dodge Durango commercials; he attended the MTV VMA awards and even showed up at the Olympic Curling Trials. Most recently he co-hosted a local North Dakota news program.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/2b5IhzGuMPg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>(Ron&#8217;s photo bombs are especially amusing.)</p>
<p>Ben &amp; Jerry even created an ice cream flavor in Ron&#8217;s honor, called “Scotchy, Scotch, Scotch.”</p>
<p><img class="alignnone" alt="" src="http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-r5fBpwo0XmE/Uo_t0nm4cgI/AAAAAAAALv8/vIuUgAgEw0k/s1600/ben%2Bjerrys%2Bron%2Bburgundy%2Bscotchy%2Bscotch%2Bscotch%2Bice%2Bcream%2Bpint.jpg" width="227" height="254" /></p>
<p>Some think all the promotion is too much––they&#8217;ve had enough of Mr. Burgundy.</p>
<p>I think it is pure marketing genius, thinking outside the box of boring commercials, ads, and billboards. I actually watch and enjoy the Dodge commercials, as opposed to my normal habit of changing the channel. Not to mention how viral his videos have gone––all free advertising!</p>
<p>Keep making us laugh Ron!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>So, I&#8217;m a Marketing Nerd!</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/20/2014/so-im-a-marketing-nerd/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 14:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deadliest Catch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TLC]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3300</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[While watching Deadliest Catch on the Discovery Channel with my husband one night a few months ago, I started noticing a pattern.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While watching <i>Deadliest Catch</i> on the Discovery Channel with my husband one night a few months ago, I started noticing a pattern. During every commercial break, we were assaulted with commercials for men’s products: Ford F-150 pickup trucks, razors with four blades for a closer shave, Slim Jims–the list goes on.</p>
<p>I laughed out loud and said, &#8220;Oh man, I guess I&#8217;m not in the target market for <i>this </i>show. I love when that happens! I feel like I&#8217;m beating the system!&#8221; I expected my husband to chuckle and agree. Instead, he looked at me like I had three heads and said, &#8220;What?&#8221;</p>
<p>I realized, then, that not everybody in the world notices or pays attention when they&#8217;re being marketed to. For the first time, I felt special as a professional working in marketing.  Over the next few weeks I noticed that I really do find it fun to determine if I am inside or outside the target market for the products or services I&#8217;m being marketed.</p>
<p>Here are a few examples:</p>
<ul>
<li>On a random weekday home sick, I was watching <i>The Price is Right</i> on CBS. Denture cleaner–Nope!  Nice try, marketers, but thankfully I have all my teeth!  Scooter Store–Nope!  Emergency Life Alert button–Nope!  Pampers Cruisers diapers…OK, you got me on that one.  Touché, marketers.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Checking my Email: Groupon to Niagra Falls–Nope!  Adidas Men&#8217;s Golf Shoes–Nope!  50% off on preschool portraits…wait, let me see that one.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Watching <i>What Not to Wear</i> on TLC, while folding laundry on a Saturday afternoon: OK, I admit, I am 100% in the center circle of TLC&#8217;s target market diagram.  Whatever I see a commercial for, I want to buy, to watch, to check out.  Way to go, TLC, you found me!</li>
</ul>
<p>Marketers have a different way of looking at the world–of breaking down human behavior and trying to understand, at the core, what moves and motivates people. I am happy to consider myself part of this group of professionals. I feel at home in this little world because it&#8217;s really interesting to me. I am also happy that I&#8217;m not tasked with advertising to smart-ass marketers like myself!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Giving Company Materials a Little Spice for the Holidays</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/20/2013/giving-company-materials-a-little-spice-for-the-holidays/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3400</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Everybody who’s flown a lot probably knows an airline’s take off instructions by heart.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everybody who’s flown a lot probably knows an airline’s take off instructions by heart. However, government-required informational videos can be something that enhances your brand, and not just a checkmark on the “must have” list.</p>
<p>Case in point: Delta Airlines’ holiday-themed safety video:</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/0P-fqUoHMBc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sports Authority Holiday Spot Hits the Right Notes</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/13/2013/sports-authority-holiday-spot-hits-the-right-notes/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 07:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holiday]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Authority]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3311</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I caught this ad for Sports Authority during a recent Clippers-Thunder game and it tugged at me in a way that few commercials do.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/5K9GPJiRLno?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>I caught this ad for Sports Authority during a recent Clippers-Thunder game and it tugged at me in a way that few commercials do. I&#8217;m not a Luddite, fanatical holiday shopper, or obsessive sports fan. I just appreciate a nice message that captures something pertinent about our time, and this one does.</p>
<p>In addition to the usual annual slate of electronics, this holiday season sees the arrival of two new video game consoles, which are now released every six years or so. At the same time, culturally we seem to be more and more experiencing a sort of post-tech-explosion malaise. For many people, the honeymoon bliss of social networks and mobile computing is fading and they&#8217;re trying to reconnect with the more organic joys in life.</p>
<p>With all that in mind, this ad from <a href="http://www.factorylabs.com/" target="_blank">Factory Design Lab</a> seems especially well-timed and on-point. So well done, guys. I don&#8217;t have any kids to give basketballs to, but if I did, I&#8217;d have to give it some serious thought.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Actions Speak Louder Than Ads</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/11/2013/actions-speak-louder-than-ads/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 18:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coca Cola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Haiyan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Phillipines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Typhoon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Typhoon Haiyan]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3318</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Coca Cola put the brakes on any and all of their advertising spending last Monday in order to help those in need.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coca Cola put the brakes on any and all of their advertising spending last Monday in order to help those in need. How does this work? Well, the sugary-sweet beverage company decided to take all the money they would have spent on advertising and pass it along to aid in the relief and rebuilding efforts in the Philippines after Typhoon Haiyan.</p>
<p>Not only does this story warm the cockles of my heart, but it&#8217;s also nice to see a major business setting such a good example for the rest of the nation (and the world). As a trained &#8220;communicator,&#8221; I&#8217;d venture to guess no one will miss Coke&#8217;s advertisements this holiday season—in fact, I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if this soda-pushing powerhouse sees an increase in sales as a result of such positive publicity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Modern Family, and What it Means for Advertisers</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/02/2013/the-modern-family-and-what-it-means-for-advertisers/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[modern family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proctor & Gamble]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thanksgiving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3322</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey. I prepared with two practice rounds in early November, roasting whole chickens for my husband and me. I was ready.</p>
<p>On the big day, as my dad read each instruction for turkey prep–remove gizzards, rinse turkey, pat dry, lay on roasting rack, rub salt–<del cite="mailto:Michael%20Garcia" datetime="2013-12-02T09:23"></del>a refrain began to take shape. “Oh, Jordy normally does that part,” I kept saying.</p>
<p>My mom, supervising from the sidelines had caught on to what my husband, to date, hasn’t. “What exactly do <i>you </i>do to cook if Jordy does all this work?”* Oops, I’d been caught. Caught in the act of being a Modern Family.</p>
<p>With both of us working (and two dogs to care for), the “traditional” roles are thrown out the window in my household. We contribute equally (or so I’ve duped my husband into thinking, hehe) when it comes to the household chores. I do my share, but he has taken on a wide range of household tasks, from cooking, to vacuuming, and (in my greatest victory of all), grocery shopping.  On and on his list goes, our modern roles taking shape before our (and my mother’s) very eyes.</p>
<p>The other group to have caught on to the modern family? Tide detergent. Over the holiday weekend, I watched both a holiday movie marathon on Lifetime AND a thrilling Villanova basketball game (victory over Kansas!) on NBC Sports. I saw more Tide laundry detergent commercials on the latter, clearly targeted towards husbands who help around the house. Slowly, I’ve been noticing these ads cropping up. Their messages are heartwarming and humorous, and I love what Proctor &amp; Gamble has done to get there.</p>
<p>Tide and P&amp;G went right back to the basics. They got to know their audience, all over again. It may not be the same audience it’s been since its introduction 67 years ago, and that’s okay. It is one thing to stay where your audience is–social media, mobile devices, Netflix–but entirely  another thing to truly know who your audience is now and will be down the road. It takes work, it takes research, and it takes the ability to not only accept change but to capitalize on it.</p>
<p>Kudos, Tide. I can’t wait to see what happens next time “laundry detergent” is on the grocery list.</p>
<p>*In case you’ve been wondering, my role in the chicken and turkey cooking comes in once the gross handling of raw fowl is complete, and I can season, stuff, smother it in butter and spices, and place it in the oven.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Univar ES Rebrand</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/11/18/2013/univar/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 17:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tradeshow planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design & development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3221</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Univar Environmental Sciences is widely known for providing top-quality chemical products, but their brand lacked humanity.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Univar Environmental Sciences is widely known for providing top-quality chemical products, but their brand lacked humanity. So, FVM engaged in research, asked some tough questions, and created an authentic and differentiated brand position—brought to life through vibrant design. The result: a stronger, warmer, more down-to-earth brand that showcased the human element so crucial to Univar’s success, and laid the foundation for all future marketing efforts.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OCE Choose My Future</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/20/2013/oce-choose-my-future/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 14:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[email marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design & development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3147</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[What did the Office of Catholic Education do when they need to increase numbers at Catholic High Schools?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What did the Office of Catholic Education do when they need to increase numbers at Catholic High Schools? They called FVM and the full-fledged marketing and awareness campaign “Choose My Future” was born. Now in its third year, the enrollment-boosting campaign is email nurturing, content marketing and advertising at its best and can be seen on planes (over the Jersey shore), trains and buses across Philadelphia.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s all about the trust</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/16/2013/its-all-about-the-trust/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 19:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Van Metre]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand consulting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[competitive analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[logo design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3127</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I couldn’t help myself.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I couldn’t help myself. I opened my eyes at 5am one morning, the TV still on from the night before, and what program was on? <em>The Pitch</em>, AMC’s reality show that gives a behind-the-scenes view as two ad agencies vie for a new account. How could I NOT watch?</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-3131" alt="0614_fuller-brush2" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2-147x220.jpg" width="147" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2-147x220.jpg 147w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2.jpg 500w" sizes="(max-width: 147px) 100vw, 147px" /></p>
<p>In this case, the account was The Fuller Brush Company. <em>THE</em> Fuller Brush Company! An iconic brand from my childhood whose distribution channel was The Fuller Brush Man (thousands of them, actually) selling door-to-door-to-door-to-door. Seriously.</p>
<p>Fuller, one of America’s oldest and most trusted brands that was once known by every household in America (and according to my mother, “Made the best toilet brush on the planet,”) is now virtually unknown by anyone under the age of 45. With a new owner who just rescued the 100-year-old company from bankruptcy, the agency assignment was to “reboot the brand for the modern market.” Again, who wouldn’t love this show?</p>
<p>Without going blow by blow through the episode, suffice it to say, I found it both entertaining and a bit unbelievable. Particularly the part when both agencies came up with exactly the same “Live Fuller” concept to build their pitches around. Yeah, kinda’ fishy.</p>
<p>Anyway, the question is, how does CEO David Sabin choose between two agencies <em>that just presented the exact same big idea?</em></p>
<p>My answer (and here comes the lesson): Clients don’t choose agencies based on the creative they pitch. They choose agencies based on whether they can imagine trusting the agency’s people with their brand.</p>
<p>Think about your closest relationships, your best friends. The best ones are those who spend the most time with you, expend the most energy on you, appreciate you and love you just the way you are. And more than likely, they are also the ones whom you allow to carefully, kindly, and almost naturally help you grow into a better version of yourself. Because they are the ones you trust.</p>
<p>In my view, the Monogram agency didn’t win because of their creative execution. They won because they showed the client he could trust them because they took the time to understand. They spent time on research and then shared their views of potential new customers; they first understood and then echoed the client’s love of The Fuller Brush Man icon while recommending a modern makeover; and they even showed personal empathy and appreciation for the quality of the brand by mentioning using a Fuller hairbrush for over 50 years.</p>
<p>Monogram got it. They understood that the pitch wasn’t about the idea, the destination. It was about their process, their journey to understanding – recounting what they did, what they learned and then what they recommended based on years of experience and expertise.</p>
<p>Monogram got it all &#8212; the brand, the client’s trust, and the account.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
