<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>content strategy &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/content-strategy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Are Super Bowl Ads Worth The Investment?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/30/2014/are-super-bowl-ads-worth-the-investment/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commercials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl XLVIII]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3422</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event. It&#8217;s the most watched program of the year. Even those who have no idea who the Denver Broncos or the Seattle Seahawks are will tune in. Why? Typically it&#8217;s because everyone else is doing it, but another reason is the advertising. In 2013, the average cost of a 30-second spot was $4 million. The effectiveness of these ads in boosting a company&#8217;s sales has been in question over the past few years. Experts have compared the investment of the cost of an ad vs. overall increased revenue after the Super Bowl, and it shows little to no change. Forbes magazine claims that most companies would be better off airing 10 commercials at $400,000 each, to increase repetition. Forbes also claims that Super Bowl Ads have become memorible for presentation, but forgettable in terms of persuasion.</p>
<p>The University of Wisconsin-Eau Claire <a href="http://www.uwec.edu/newsbureau/release/past/2000/00-01/010400super.html">did a study of over 500 Super Bowl spots that ran between 2000 and 2009</a>, and found that many did not work. Some Super Bowl Ads fail due to the fact that people typically recall the story, but not the product. More often than not, Super Bowl ads attempt to deliver broad humor for entertainment purposes, rather than sell the product. Sometimes companies will enlist celebrities to sponsor their Super Bowl Ad, but experts have also concluded this tactic is ineffective as the celebrity may lack relevance to the product. Still the question must be asked, is the Super Bowl ad worth the investment?</p>
<p>Forbes magazine says yes.</p>
<p>The real reason companies invest in Super Bowl spots is because the announcement of buying airtime for the Super Bowl can boost their stock price, at least in the short term. A business will typically announce their Super Bowl buy weeks prior to the big game, and even debut the advertisement early on social sites such as YouTube, Facebook and Twitter. Experts have found that any positive impact on a businesses stock price comes at the announcement of the Super Bowl spot, not after the spot runs. Whether or not an advertisement is successful is secondary to the impact it has on a business&#8217; exposure in the stock market. So yes, for an enterprise business that can afford the $4,000,000+ on advertising their investment is well worth it.</p>
<p>Whether you watch for the love of the game, advertising, or Peyton Manning––sit back, relax and enjoy the entertainment. It&#8217;ll be a long time until your next fantasy football draft night, and that&#8217;s depressing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pay-Per-Gaze: The future of advertising</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/13/2014/pay-per-gaze-the-future-of-advertising/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 19:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google Glass]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marty McFly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mashable]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pay-per-click]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3272</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[&#8220;Advertising is going to change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 100,&#8221; says Chris Taylor of Mashable OP-ED.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Advertising is going to change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 100,&#8221; <a title="says Chris Taylor of Mashable OP-ED." href="http://mashable.com/2013/08/15/the-future-of-advertising-pay-per-gaze-is-just-the-beginning/" target="_blank">says Chris Taylor of Mashable OP-ED. </a>In recent months Google, the world’s largest search engine provider, was granted a patent for a Google Glass-based ad system known as &#8220;pay-per-gaze.”</p>
<p>Google Glass is a wearable computer with an optical head-mounted display, which is being developed by Google as part of a mission to produce a mass-market ubiquitous computer.  To operate Google Glass, wearers simply tilt their head 30 degrees upward or tap the touchpad and say, &#8220;O.K., Glass.&#8221;  After the glasses are activated simple requests can be made such as, &#8220;Take a picture”, &#8220;Record a video&#8221;, or &#8220;Send a message to.”  That&#8217;s where &#8220;pay-per-gaze&#8221; comes in.  Google’s &#8220;pay-per-gaze&#8221; would charge advertisers for the number of times someone looks at their ad through Google Glass, the same way pay-per-click works today when users click on a link.  Google Glass contains technology that would track the direction the wearer’s pupils are pointing, and for how long they are gazing at a message.</p>
<p>This technology could potentially be a major risk for Google as people are infinitely exposed to advertising.  The money would flow in endlessly, and advertisers might second-guess themselves and their decision to invest in &#8220;pay-per-gaze.”  Still, this technology is something not even Marty McFly would have imagined.  Personally, I&#8217;ll stick with my Ray Bans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Giving Company Materials a Little Spice for the Holidays</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/20/2013/giving-company-materials-a-little-spice-for-the-holidays/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3400</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Everybody who’s flown a lot probably knows an airline’s take off instructions by heart.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everybody who’s flown a lot probably knows an airline’s take off instructions by heart. However, government-required informational videos can be something that enhances your brand, and not just a checkmark on the “must have” list.</p>
<p>Case in point: Delta Airlines’ holiday-themed safety video:</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/0P-fqUoHMBc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Actions Speak Louder Than Ads</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/11/2013/actions-speak-louder-than-ads/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 18:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coca Cola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Haiyan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Phillipines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Typhoon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Typhoon Haiyan]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3318</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Coca Cola put the brakes on any and all of their advertising spending last Monday in order to help those in need.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coca Cola put the brakes on any and all of their advertising spending last Monday in order to help those in need. How does this work? Well, the sugary-sweet beverage company decided to take all the money they would have spent on advertising and pass it along to aid in the relief and rebuilding efforts in the Philippines after Typhoon Haiyan.</p>
<p>Not only does this story warm the cockles of my heart, but it&#8217;s also nice to see a major business setting such a good example for the rest of the nation (and the world). As a trained &#8220;communicator,&#8221; I&#8217;d venture to guess no one will miss Coke&#8217;s advertisements this holiday season—in fact, I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if this soda-pushing powerhouse sees an increase in sales as a result of such positive publicity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simpana 10 Launch</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/18/2013/simpana-10-launch/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 15:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[demand generation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sales enablement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design & development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3155</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When CommVault released their latest and greatest software, Simpana 10, FVM answered with an innovative content strategy and multi-media launch.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When CommVault released their latest and greatest software, Simpana 10, FVM answered with an innovative content strategy and multi-media launch. We used digital media to drive the IT world to a content-packed interactive microsite—including, demos, videos, literature, partner interviews and more—which was explored for an average of 10 minutes per visit. The splash was felt globally and established the product as an industry leader.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Volunteering: good for all</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/04/2013/volunteering-good-for-all/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 18:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ambler gives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Big Brothers/Big Sisters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[campaign reporting & analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fashion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro bono]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volunteering]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3006</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I don’t think people even realize it but the power of volunteering has an extraordinary rippling effect.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I don’t think people even realize it but the power of volunteering has an extraordinary rippling effect. Not only does the recipient benefit, but the volunteer gets a renewed sense of accomplishment and pride. They bring that feeling to the workplace, which helps build a positive environment for everyone. So it makes sense that employers should encourage community service to help increase morale.</p>
<p>Whether you participate as a team effort on a pro-bono project or you partake in an individual day of service, you are ultimately contributing to a positive work environment. Most people like the idea of giving back to their community but find it difficult to carve out the time. Thankfully, more employers realize this and offer the opportunity to participate in community service within the workplace.</p>
<p>FVM has been fortunate enough to work with a wonderful group of people at Big Brothers Big Sisters/Ambler Gives. They think they’re lucky because they got a free awesome new website, but in reality, our team got the reward. We got to flex our creative muscles beyond our usual realm of B-to-B and into a trendy fashion show event. Our developers explored new software for online donations and ticket purchases. So while we learned new skills and flourished creatively, Ambler Gives kicked off a stellar event benefitting young children. Everyone won.</p>
<p>Benefits of community service:<br />
1. Stronger communities = stronger business opportunities<br />
2. Team building – working on a goal outside of your everyday office routine<br />
3. Morale boost – Pride and personal satisfaction that comes from helping someone in need<br />
(Proven to positively impact your physical and mental health)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How a starfish sparked an idea</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/02/2013/how-a-starfish-sparked-an-idea/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 17:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3066</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I was beaming.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="attachment_3104" style="max-width: 175px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img class="size-medium wp-image-3104" alt="Isn't she adorable?!" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-165x220.jpeg" width="165" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-165x220.jpeg 165w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-768x1024.jpeg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 165px) 100vw, 165px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Isn&#8217;t she adorable?!</p></div>
<p>I was beaming. My favorite family member (don’t tell my husband), Macy, had just graduated from Puppy Kindergarten with flying colors, and she was totally into the toy I bought her for a congratulatory present. So into it, in fact, that I immediately logged on to the company’s website to hunt for more. Because, you know, her 5 ½-month birthday is just around the corner.</p>
<p>And there it was: “Become a Dog Toy Tester.” The deal was, sign up to receive four toys a year. Agree to write a review and you get those toys at 40% off. 40% off toys Macy loves? And I get to share stories of my puppy with the entire world? What’s not to love?</p>
<p>At that exact same time, our B2B client was looking to increase reviews of products on their website. The strategy was an Apple product giveaway—always a great incentive, but what about giving the actual products away at a discount in return for a review? You better believe that in the long run, it’s going to sell more product. Here’s why it works:</p>
<p>1. It shows customers you value their opinion, which creates loyalty.<br />
2. It gives customers more of what they need. Sure, an iPad mini is great, but that product I was going to buy anyway? I need that.<br />
3. The discount encourages customers to try new products—if it doesn’t work out, at least they didn’t pay full price.<br />
4. It’s less hassle on your end. No need to run complex sweepstakes giveaways, partner with third parties, jump through legal hoops, or figure out complex rules.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Plan for video success</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/25/2013/plan-for-video-success/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 18:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3015</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Creating effective video content requires a lot of planning.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Creating effective video content requires a lot of planning. It may sound obvious, but planning can be the make or break of a marcom strategy using video assets.</p>
<p>Here are some ways to plan for a successful video:</p>
<p><strong>1. Focus on your viewer and forget the rest </strong><br />
Too often, we want to appeal to everyone with one big, great video. Rather, split it up so you can focus on reaching that specific viewer. Video is not the expensive, resource-taxing venture it once was. Cut videos down and make them sharp. Like <a title="The Cost of Renting" href="http://kellerwilliams.vzaar.me/915941" target="_blank">Keller Williams’ video</a> that appeals to prospective real estate buyers tired of all the hoopla.</p>
<p><strong>2. Choose a format and stick with it</strong><br />
If you can help it, don’t switch gears mid-way through production. Changing the format will cost money, irritate talent and waste valuable time that could be used in post-production. Seems obvious, but often videos try to do too much with different formats and the video ends up being nothing more than a great bounce rate booster. A combo is ok. But be clear. Is it an interview? Documentary? Animated storyteller with interview segments? Whatever it is, stick to it.</p>
<p><strong>3. Get everyone on board</strong><br />
Is your video formal? Humorous? Poignant? Professional? Choose a style and make sure everyone involved–from talent to film crew—gets it. This is perhaps the most challenging step, as it can be hard to convey to creative or film crews or talent. Don’t be afraid to reinforce it. Over and over, if necessary.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Soccer scores with social media</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/07/20/2013/u-s-soccer-scores-with-social-media/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 15:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Women's Soccer Team]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3059</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The 1999 Women’s World Cup team captured fans’ hearts with their down-to-earth, girl-next-door persona.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 1999 Women’s World Cup team captured fans’ hearts with their down-to-earth, girl-next-door persona. Now, thanks to the the U.S. Soccer Federation’s <a href="http://www.youtube.com/user/ussoccerdotcom?feature=g-high-crv" target="_blank">phenomenal online media presence</a>, we fans feel more connected than ever to these incredible players.</p>
<p>Never have athletes been so accessible. Hop on to U.S. Soccer’s YouTube channel and watch practice footage, sideline clips, and player interviews. You can even travel with the team as they make their way to the 2012 Olympics via their <a href="http://www.youtube.com/user/ussoccerdotcom/videos?flow=grid&amp;view=50&amp;shelf_index=7" target="_blank">“Behind The Crest” series</a>. Still can’t get enough? See how some players live in the off-season as they take you to their hometowns in the “Back Home” series.</p>
<p>This may not seem like a big deal to some, but think about the last time you felt like you were part of your favorite team. Professional athletes are becoming more and more removed from society—forgetting the fans and focusing solely on endorsement deals and big paychecks. It’s nice to see some sports organizations, especially federal governing bodies, like US Soccer, sticking to their roots and keeping in mind those that fuel fire of their success: their fans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>YouTube had me at &#8220;Hello&#8221;</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/07/05/2013/youtube-had-me-at-hello/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 14:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[YouTube]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3056</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There are a handful of great social media platforms out there, but I’ve always been an advocate for YouTube.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are a handful of great social media platforms out there, but I’ve always been an advocate for YouTube. I read somewhere that on average, people watch four more hours of online video than regular TV every week. When you think about it, YouTube can be a pretty powerful thing. Take Bieber for example. This pint-sized crooner made it out of small-town Canada and into our hearts, all thanks to YouTube. Other teenage talents, like comedian Bo Burnham, songstress Esmee Denters, and the lovable Gaga-singing <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bxDlC7YV5is" target="_blank">Greyson Chance</a> have all had similar success.</p>
<p>So I know what you’re thinking. “Yeah, YouTube is great and fun to watch, but what’s in it for me?” My advice to you? Throw your hat in the ring. It only takes one video to go viral and your world can be turned upside down. Whether you’re a small business looking for a creative way to advertise, or a large corporation looking to attract a new generation of customers—YouTube could be the answer you’ve been looking for. It just takes one idea: one funny, thought provoking, interesting idea to get the attention of the hundreds of thousands of people who visit YouTube every day. So what have you got to lose? Grab a camera, draw up a storyboard and get started!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
