<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>brand strategy &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/brand-strategy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Are Super Bowl Ads Worth The Investment?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/30/2014/are-super-bowl-ads-worth-the-investment/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commercials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl XLVIII]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3422</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event. It&#8217;s the most watched program of the year. Even those who have no idea who the Denver Broncos or the Seattle Seahawks are will tune in. Why? Typically it&#8217;s because everyone else is doing it, but another reason is the advertising. In 2013, the average cost of a 30-second spot was $4 million. The effectiveness of these ads in boosting a company&#8217;s sales has been in question over the past few years. Experts have compared the investment of the cost of an ad vs. overall increased revenue after the Super Bowl, and it shows little to no change. Forbes magazine claims that most companies would be better off airing 10 commercials at $400,000 each, to increase repetition. Forbes also claims that Super Bowl Ads have become memorible for presentation, but forgettable in terms of persuasion.</p>
<p>The University of Wisconsin-Eau Claire <a href="http://www.uwec.edu/newsbureau/release/past/2000/00-01/010400super.html">did a study of over 500 Super Bowl spots that ran between 2000 and 2009</a>, and found that many did not work. Some Super Bowl Ads fail due to the fact that people typically recall the story, but not the product. More often than not, Super Bowl ads attempt to deliver broad humor for entertainment purposes, rather than sell the product. Sometimes companies will enlist celebrities to sponsor their Super Bowl Ad, but experts have also concluded this tactic is ineffective as the celebrity may lack relevance to the product. Still the question must be asked, is the Super Bowl ad worth the investment?</p>
<p>Forbes magazine says yes.</p>
<p>The real reason companies invest in Super Bowl spots is because the announcement of buying airtime for the Super Bowl can boost their stock price, at least in the short term. A business will typically announce their Super Bowl buy weeks prior to the big game, and even debut the advertisement early on social sites such as YouTube, Facebook and Twitter. Experts have found that any positive impact on a businesses stock price comes at the announcement of the Super Bowl spot, not after the spot runs. Whether or not an advertisement is successful is secondary to the impact it has on a business&#8217; exposure in the stock market. So yes, for an enterprise business that can afford the $4,000,000+ on advertising their investment is well worth it.</p>
<p>Whether you watch for the love of the game, advertising, or Peyton Manning––sit back, relax and enjoy the entertainment. It&#8217;ll be a long time until your next fantasy football draft night, and that&#8217;s depressing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Giving Company Materials a Little Spice for the Holidays</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/20/2013/giving-company-materials-a-little-spice-for-the-holidays/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3400</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Everybody who’s flown a lot probably knows an airline’s take off instructions by heart.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everybody who’s flown a lot probably knows an airline’s take off instructions by heart. However, government-required informational videos can be something that enhances your brand, and not just a checkmark on the “must have” list.</p>
<p>Case in point: Delta Airlines’ holiday-themed safety video:</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/0P-fqUoHMBc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sports Authority Holiday Spot Hits the Right Notes</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/13/2013/sports-authority-holiday-spot-hits-the-right-notes/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 07:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holiday]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Authority]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3311</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I caught this ad for Sports Authority during a recent Clippers-Thunder game and it tugged at me in a way that few commercials do.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/5K9GPJiRLno?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>I caught this ad for Sports Authority during a recent Clippers-Thunder game and it tugged at me in a way that few commercials do. I&#8217;m not a Luddite, fanatical holiday shopper, or obsessive sports fan. I just appreciate a nice message that captures something pertinent about our time, and this one does.</p>
<p>In addition to the usual annual slate of electronics, this holiday season sees the arrival of two new video game consoles, which are now released every six years or so. At the same time, culturally we seem to be more and more experiencing a sort of post-tech-explosion malaise. For many people, the honeymoon bliss of social networks and mobile computing is fading and they&#8217;re trying to reconnect with the more organic joys in life.</p>
<p>With all that in mind, this ad from <a href="http://www.factorylabs.com/" target="_blank">Factory Design Lab</a> seems especially well-timed and on-point. So well done, guys. I don&#8217;t have any kids to give basketballs to, but if I did, I&#8217;d have to give it some serious thought.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Actions Speak Louder Than Ads</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/11/2013/actions-speak-louder-than-ads/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 18:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coca Cola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Haiyan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Phillipines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Typhoon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Typhoon Haiyan]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3318</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Coca Cola put the brakes on any and all of their advertising spending last Monday in order to help those in need.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coca Cola put the brakes on any and all of their advertising spending last Monday in order to help those in need. How does this work? Well, the sugary-sweet beverage company decided to take all the money they would have spent on advertising and pass it along to aid in the relief and rebuilding efforts in the Philippines after Typhoon Haiyan.</p>
<p>Not only does this story warm the cockles of my heart, but it&#8217;s also nice to see a major business setting such a good example for the rest of the nation (and the world). As a trained &#8220;communicator,&#8221; I&#8217;d venture to guess no one will miss Coke&#8217;s advertisements this holiday season—in fact, I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if this soda-pushing powerhouse sees an increase in sales as a result of such positive publicity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Modern Family, and What it Means for Advertisers</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/02/2013/the-modern-family-and-what-it-means-for-advertisers/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[modern family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proctor & Gamble]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thanksgiving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3322</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey. I prepared with two practice rounds in early November, roasting whole chickens for my husband and me. I was ready.</p>
<p>On the big day, as my dad read each instruction for turkey prep–remove gizzards, rinse turkey, pat dry, lay on roasting rack, rub salt–<del cite="mailto:Michael%20Garcia" datetime="2013-12-02T09:23"></del>a refrain began to take shape. “Oh, Jordy normally does that part,” I kept saying.</p>
<p>My mom, supervising from the sidelines had caught on to what my husband, to date, hasn’t. “What exactly do <i>you </i>do to cook if Jordy does all this work?”* Oops, I’d been caught. Caught in the act of being a Modern Family.</p>
<p>With both of us working (and two dogs to care for), the “traditional” roles are thrown out the window in my household. We contribute equally (or so I’ve duped my husband into thinking, hehe) when it comes to the household chores. I do my share, but he has taken on a wide range of household tasks, from cooking, to vacuuming, and (in my greatest victory of all), grocery shopping.  On and on his list goes, our modern roles taking shape before our (and my mother’s) very eyes.</p>
<p>The other group to have caught on to the modern family? Tide detergent. Over the holiday weekend, I watched both a holiday movie marathon on Lifetime AND a thrilling Villanova basketball game (victory over Kansas!) on NBC Sports. I saw more Tide laundry detergent commercials on the latter, clearly targeted towards husbands who help around the house. Slowly, I’ve been noticing these ads cropping up. Their messages are heartwarming and humorous, and I love what Proctor &amp; Gamble has done to get there.</p>
<p>Tide and P&amp;G went right back to the basics. They got to know their audience, all over again. It may not be the same audience it’s been since its introduction 67 years ago, and that’s okay. It is one thing to stay where your audience is–social media, mobile devices, Netflix–but entirely  another thing to truly know who your audience is now and will be down the road. It takes work, it takes research, and it takes the ability to not only accept change but to capitalize on it.</p>
<p>Kudos, Tide. I can’t wait to see what happens next time “laundry detergent” is on the grocery list.</p>
<p>*In case you’ve been wondering, my role in the chicken and turkey cooking comes in once the gross handling of raw fowl is complete, and I can season, stuff, smother it in butter and spices, and place it in the oven.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Univar ES Rebrand</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/11/18/2013/univar/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 17:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tradeshow planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design & development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3221</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Univar Environmental Sciences is widely known for providing top-quality chemical products, but their brand lacked humanity.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Univar Environmental Sciences is widely known for providing top-quality chemical products, but their brand lacked humanity. So, FVM engaged in research, asked some tough questions, and created an authentic and differentiated brand position—brought to life through vibrant design. The result: a stronger, warmer, more down-to-earth brand that showcased the human element so crucial to Univar’s success, and laid the foundation for all future marketing efforts.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simpana 10 Launch</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/18/2013/simpana-10-launch/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 15:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[demand generation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sales enablement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design & development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3155</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When CommVault released their latest and greatest software, Simpana 10, FVM answered with an innovative content strategy and multi-media launch.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When CommVault released their latest and greatest software, Simpana 10, FVM answered with an innovative content strategy and multi-media launch. We used digital media to drive the IT world to a content-packed interactive microsite—including, demos, videos, literature, partner interviews and more—which was explored for an average of 10 minutes per visit. The splash was felt globally and established the product as an industry leader.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s all about the trust</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/16/2013/its-all-about-the-trust/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 19:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Van Metre]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand consulting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[competitive analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[logo design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3127</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I couldn’t help myself.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I couldn’t help myself. I opened my eyes at 5am one morning, the TV still on from the night before, and what program was on? <em>The Pitch</em>, AMC’s reality show that gives a behind-the-scenes view as two ad agencies vie for a new account. How could I NOT watch?</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-3131" alt="0614_fuller-brush2" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2-147x220.jpg" width="147" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2-147x220.jpg 147w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2.jpg 500w" sizes="(max-width: 147px) 100vw, 147px" /></p>
<p>In this case, the account was The Fuller Brush Company. <em>THE</em> Fuller Brush Company! An iconic brand from my childhood whose distribution channel was The Fuller Brush Man (thousands of them, actually) selling door-to-door-to-door-to-door. Seriously.</p>
<p>Fuller, one of America’s oldest and most trusted brands that was once known by every household in America (and according to my mother, “Made the best toilet brush on the planet,”) is now virtually unknown by anyone under the age of 45. With a new owner who just rescued the 100-year-old company from bankruptcy, the agency assignment was to “reboot the brand for the modern market.” Again, who wouldn’t love this show?</p>
<p>Without going blow by blow through the episode, suffice it to say, I found it both entertaining and a bit unbelievable. Particularly the part when both agencies came up with exactly the same “Live Fuller” concept to build their pitches around. Yeah, kinda’ fishy.</p>
<p>Anyway, the question is, how does CEO David Sabin choose between two agencies <em>that just presented the exact same big idea?</em></p>
<p>My answer (and here comes the lesson): Clients don’t choose agencies based on the creative they pitch. They choose agencies based on whether they can imagine trusting the agency’s people with their brand.</p>
<p>Think about your closest relationships, your best friends. The best ones are those who spend the most time with you, expend the most energy on you, appreciate you and love you just the way you are. And more than likely, they are also the ones whom you allow to carefully, kindly, and almost naturally help you grow into a better version of yourself. Because they are the ones you trust.</p>
<p>In my view, the Monogram agency didn’t win because of their creative execution. They won because they showed the client he could trust them because they took the time to understand. They spent time on research and then shared their views of potential new customers; they first understood and then echoed the client’s love of The Fuller Brush Man icon while recommending a modern makeover; and they even showed personal empathy and appreciation for the quality of the brand by mentioning using a Fuller hairbrush for over 50 years.</p>
<p>Monogram got it. They understood that the pitch wasn’t about the idea, the destination. It was about their process, their journey to understanding – recounting what they did, what they learned and then what they recommended based on years of experience and expertise.</p>
<p>Monogram got it all &#8212; the brand, the client’s trust, and the account.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TandD Foods</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/16/2013/tandd-foods/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 16:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3160</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Regulatory policies are complicated for food service businesses.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Regulatory policies are complicated for food service businesses. So when Japan-based data management company TandD Foods wanted to break into the U.S. market, FVM took a unique approach. Rather than worry about complexity, we chose to focus on a simple solution: the easiest way to keep perishable food safe and compliance in check. We targeted decision makers through an integrated digital strategy, topped with refreshed, relevant branding.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digesting copy over lunch</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/03/2013/lunchtime-reading/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chipotle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2993</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Lunch at Chipotle is always awesome.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lunch at Chipotle is always awesome. Today, it was especially awesome to see good ole fashioned words on paper telling an effective brand story in this impatient, digital world of ours. The burrito king’s cups and wrapping paper are playfully covered with musings about all-things-Chipotle, from the pleasure of foil licking to the reservoir of deliciousness at the bottom of each burrito. The kind of things that we Chipotle-lovers can relate to—and, more importantly, help to build brand loyalty.</p>
<p>Copy is still a powerful tool. You just need to seek out those rare moments when your audience is happy to read them. Like when they have a big, fat, juicy burrito in their hands.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
