<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tom O&#8217;Brien &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/blog/author/tobrien/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>FVM wins two W3 Awards for web excellence</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/26/2017/fvm-wins-two-w3-awards-for-web-excellence/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 23:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=7037</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Wow!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wow! FVM is beyond proud to have been recognized with two Silver 2017 W3 Awards for our work on behalf of digital pathology startup Proscia and campus safety non-profit Clery Center.</p>
<p>The W3s — which are judged by the Academy of Interactive and Visual Arts (AIVA) and honor creative excellence on the web — awarded <a href="https://proscia.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Proscia.com</a> for copywriting and <a href="https://clerycenter.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CleryCenter.org</a> for non-profit website.</p>
<p>So a big pat on the back to FVM’s storytellers, designers, and developers who work passionately and skillfully to connect B2B brands to their audiences. And a HUGE thank you to our clients whose incredible businesses and trusting partnerships challenge and inspire us every day to come up with truly creative solutions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does your B2B brand have personality?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/14/2016/does-your-b2b-brand-have-personality/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 14:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4349</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If your organization magically transformed into a person, what would he or she be like?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If your organization magically transformed into a person, what would he or she be like? Would they be the kind of person you’d like to go out for coffee with? Would they be helpful or interesting? Would you trust the things they said?</p>
<p>It may seem odd to think of your company as a person, especially in the world of B2B. But this exercise is key to discovering your brand personality—a set of human traits closely associated with your brand. It’s a roadmap for adding a vital, relatable dimension that helps engage with customers.</p>
<p>The consumer world is bustling with big brand personalities. There’s energetic, adventurous Red Bull; positive, feminine Dove; cool, intuitive Apple; and the list goes on. These brands convey a distinct personality across every touchpoint, from website and advertising to packaging and sponsorships. Consumers identify with what these brands stand for, and make decisions accordingly.</p>
<p>Granted, B2B marketing is a different beast altogether. A business decision to invest millions in manufacturing equipment is hardly an emotional one. But we B2B marketers can still benefit from the use of brand personality. Because people power all those businesses you’re targeting—and a clear, consistent brand personality will engage them.</p>
<p>Of course, unlike people, brands aren’t born with personalities. They need to be created from scratch to connect with certain audiences and stand apart from the competition. So don’t worry if your organization has zero personality today – you can start crafting an effective one for tomorrow.</p>
<h2><strong>Get a personality</strong></h2>
<p>Put simply, brand personality is the way a brand looks and sounds—it sets the tone of all communications, and shapes audience perception. A typical brand personality is a set of adjectives—E.g. “bold,” “sophisticated” and “approachable”—that, together, create a unique point of view. Here’s how you can start making one for yourself.</p>
<h3><strong>Step 1: Make it relevant</strong></h3>
<p>Before you start the personality journey, consider the following:</p>
<p><strong>• Your audience<br />
</strong>What are they like? What matters to them? Why do they turn to your brand? The more you define your audience, the easier it will be to think of personality traits that appeal to them. For example, if your industry is characterized by down-to-earth people, then a genuine and grounded personality might be received well.</p>
<p><strong>• Your competition<br />
</strong>What do they look like and sound like in the market? How might you set your brand apart? Say you’re a technology provider, and all your competitors use technical language and cold imagery. Your personality could stand out from the crowd by being simple, or playful.</p>
<p><strong>• Your culture<br />
</strong>What are your people like? What are your organization’s guiding principles? If &#8220;above-and-beyond&#8221; customer service is part of your company’s DNA, then a vibrant, helpful personality would bring that to life for the wider world.</p>
<h3><strong>Step 2: Words and themes</strong></h3>
<p>Creative exercises are a great way to come up with brand personality traits. Most importantly, they’re fun and yield a wide variation of ideas. So arm yourselves with flipchart paper, caffeine and snacks, and try these on for size.</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>If my brand were a dog</strong> – Associations are a great way to think differently about your brand. What would your brand be if it was a car? A superhero? A famous actor? A plant? A color?</li>
<li><strong>Meet Mr. Brand </strong>– Back to imagining your brand as a person. What does it look and sound like? How does it dress? Where is it from, and where is it going?</li>
<li><strong>Today vs. tomorrow</strong> – Write down adjectives that describe how your brand is perceived today. Next, write down adjectives that say how you want to be perceived 10 years from now.</li>
</ol>
<p>Once you have all your words on paper, start grouping them together. Similarities and themes will emerge. Rank them according to importance and/or relevancy.</p>
<h3><strong>Step 3: Choose words you can draw</strong></h3>
<p>With your top themes outlined, choose 3-5 adjectives that best encapsulate them. Brand personality traits guide the creation of touchpoints like web copy, ads, graphic design, and business collateral. So it’s important that your personality traits are “words you can draw.” For example, “passionate” comes to mind because your team is so enthusiastic. But how do you design a “passionate” banner ad? Turn to the thesaurus and explore synonyms like “lively” or “vibrant.” These words are more visually descriptive; you can picture a vibrant design or lively web copy.</p>
<h2><strong>You have personality. Now what?</strong></h2>
<p>Creating a brand personality is just the beginning—bringing it to life is an ongoing pursuit. In the short term, it can act as a checklist for your communications. Hold those words next to any email, copy or design to make sure they align. Keep true to it, and your brand personality will naturally shine.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another four through the door</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/07/20/2016/another-four-through-the-door/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 22:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6356</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[At FVM, refrigerator real estate is getting scarce.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At FVM, refrigerator real estate is getting scarce. Some people have to stand at agency meetings for lack of available chairs. And sometimes there’s a line for the ping pong table. But we don’t care because we have FOUR. NEW. HIRES!</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6352 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FVM-New-Hires-1.jpg" alt="FVM New Hires" width="600" height="401" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/FVM-New-Hires-1.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/FVM-New-Hires-1-220x147.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" />Our new talent comes in to serve the agency’s growing list of clients, with (L-R) Matthew Johnson joining as Senior Designer; Steven Rayesky as Developer; Kiersten Hepler as Account Executive; and Molly McDevitt as Account Coordinator.</p>
<p>We’re also excited to have made two key promotions to the roles of Associate Creative Director. Having proven themselves as exceptional creative leaders, Jon Tran (left) now oversees our brand positioning and copy strategy capabilities, while Russell Falk (right) heads up visual identity and design.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6353 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Russell-and-Jon-1.png" alt="Russell and Jon" width="600" height="368" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Russell-and-Jon-1.png 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Russell-and-Jon-1-220x135.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ArcherIMS.com wins W³</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/23/2015/archerims-com-wins-w%c2%b3/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 14:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5700</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[ArcherIMS.com has been honored with a 2015 W³ Award from the Academy of Interactive and Visual Arts (AIVA)!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.archerims.com/" target="_blank">ArcherIMS.com</a> has been honored with a 2015 W³ Award from the Academy of Interactive and Visual Arts (AIVA)!</p>
<p>The website for software and services provider Archer won a Silver Award in the Financial Services category, and is FVM’s second gleaming tower of cubes in two years.</p>
<p>“It’s great to see our digital work recognized once again by AIVA,” says Jon Cohen, EVP Client Services. “The website brought the full <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/portfolio/archer/" target="_blank">Archer rebrand</a> to life for the first time, it has become a great outlet for thought-leadership, and it&#8217;s a vital platform to support future growth. It was a lot of fun to create and something we’re very proud of.”</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.w3award.com/awards/" target="_blank">W³</a> is sanctioned and judged by AIVA, an invitation-only body consisting of top-tier professionals from a &#8220;Who&#8217;s Who&#8221; of acclaimed media, interactive, advertising, and marketing firms. Website entries are judged on creativity, usability, navigation, functionality, visual design, and ease of use, and represent the very best in digital excellence.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FVM grows with four new hires</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/15/2015/fvm-grows-with-four-new-hires/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5679</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Over the past few weeks we&#8217;ve welcomed some top new talent to strengthen our core competences and enhance our offering.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past few weeks we&#8217;ve welcomed some top new talent to strengthen our core competences and enhance our offering.</p>
<h6><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-5680" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/New-Hires-blog.jpg" alt="New-Hires-blog" width="800" height="549" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/New-Hires-blog.jpg 800w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/New-Hires-blog-220x151.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /><br />
<strong>L-R: Emily Walsh, Jon Tran, Coleman Rigg, Roger Finch.</strong></h6>
<p>With over 10 years of industry experience, new Senior Copywriter Jon Tran joins FVM from Princeton marketing agency, Ripen, to lead copy strategy and creation, and brand strategy. Full Stack Developer Roger Finch arrives after three years with Geary LSF, bringing with him development and digital strategy expertise. And marketing graduates Emily Walsh and Coleman Rigg come onboard to provide key assistance on a wide array of accounts.</p>
<p>Glad to have you here, guys!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Internet of Things</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/02/09/2015/the-internet-of-things/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 17:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4909</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Internet of Things.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Internet of Things. The buzzword that has replaced Big Data. Now widely known, but often misunderstood, the IoT is the idea that our lives are becoming exponentially more interconnected. It promises to transform daily life, serving as the impetus for new technological innovation, and ushering older devices into the digital age. Previously “dumb” technology like thermostats and refrigerators are now becoming enlightened, connecting even the most mundane aspects of our lives to the vast personal data network already occupied by devices like mobile phones, tablets, and wearable tech. Here’s a bit more info in a handy video summary from Intel:</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q3ur8wzzhBU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>In a recent study conducted by IDC, the <a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/gilpress/2014/08/22/internet-of-things-by-the-numbers-market-estimates-and-forecasts/" target="_blank">market size for IoT solutions alone could reach $7.1 trillion dollars by 2020</a>, compared to a 2013 estimate of $1.9 trillion. Some companies are forecasting even higher numbers (Cisco says $14.4 trillion) for the IoT’s total impact on economic growth.</p>
<p>Those staggering projections are based on disruption in just about every industry one could imagine. Many companies are already scrambling to get ahead of the curve and capitalize on smarter data grids of customer information and business automation. <a href="http://www.gxsblogs.com/morleym/2013/10/how-the-internet-of-things-will-impact-b2b-and-global-supply-chains.html" target="_blank">Major corporations like GE</a> have set up entire divisions dedicated solely to figuring out how best to position themselves as leaders in this emerging market.</p>
<h2><strong>Internet of insight</strong></h2>
<p>Where the IoT promises to streamline every aspect of life for end users, the result for advertisers is a bumper crop of useable data that yields a wealth of information.</p>
<p>As more aspects of consumers’ lives become quantifiable, the less volatile and erratic these business processes become, presenting marketers with the mouthwatering prospect of knowing exactly where to focus their dollars, possibly on a granular level.</p>
<p>For B2Bs dealing with a considered purchase and long sales cycles, one chief benefit the IoT promises is better insight into customer behavior during various touch points in the lead-nurturing process. Instead of sending a cookie cutter follow-up email to a prospective buyer, advertisers will now have a wider menu of richer event-based options to reach the prospect’s pipeline. With more knowledge and choice, comes the opportunity to deliver more meaningful, targeted messaging. The IoT will not only impact high-level brand strategy, but how companies approach media planning as well.</p>
<p>Just look at the campaign Netflix launched in France, where <a href="http://www.digitalbuzzblog.com/netflix-real-time-reactive-gif-campaign/" target="_blank">digital billboards played animated GIFs reacting to local weather</a> and other topical events. Imagine the remarketing value this could represent to a company like FedEx Small Business or Stamps.com when one these interactive ads is located just a few steps away from the entrance to the local post office.</p>
<h2><strong>Better connected</strong></h2>
<p>A major challenge, especially for B2B companies looking to capitalize on this rising trend, is that there are very few unifying platforms that link all of these internet-connected devices together. What good would it be for a manufacturer to provide its suppliers with real-time order management technology if each end user has a different, incompatible sales platform?</p>
<p>The usual suspects, such as the aforementioned Cisco and GE, as well as IBM, are all building products to bring these networks together. How quickly the IoT becomes a practical business investment will largely be determined by the ability of these massive networks to integrate products from small software and hardware manufacturers.</p>
<h2><strong>Walking a fine line</strong></h2>
<p>The IoT promises to bring 20<sup>th</sup> century things into the 21<sup>st</sup> century; linking them to an impossibly large grid of interconnected data and making daily chores more efficient.</p>
<p>Such a bevy of  data and user demographics will have the advertising world champing at the bit. The challenge will be that—on the inevitable march towards progress and innovation—marketers must find new and creative ways to deliver personalized messaging <a href="http://fedscoop.com/the-internet-of-things-convenient-and-creepy/" target="_blank">without being so invasive</a> that the user opts out completely. The mantra is: “Be personal, not creepy. Remember <em>Minority Report</em>.&#8221;</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7bXJ_obaiYQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FVM welcomes Christiana &#8220;Vex&#8221; Del Vecchio!</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/21/2015/fvm-welcomes-christiana-vex-del-vecchio/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 16:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4847</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Meet Christiana, our new Junior Graphic Designer!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meet Christiana, our new Junior Graphic Designer!</p>
<p>Whether she’s carving her way down the slopes of Bear Mountain or photographing architecture from Philly sidewalks, Christiana is all about clean lines and cutting edge. This Art Institute of Philadelphia grad freelanced her way through college, taking on branding, illustration, editorial and product design work for clients such as Di Bruno Bros and the University of Penn Law School. Christiana is now applying her design sensibilities to web, print and everything in between as part of our close-knit creative team, while harboring a healthy/unhealthy obsession for Kevin Spacey.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-4849 size-full alignright" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/IMG_0985.jpg" alt="IMG_0985" width="600" height="400" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_0985.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_0985-220x147.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /> <img class="size-full wp-image-4851 alignright" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/IMG_09861.jpg" alt="IMG_0986[1]" width="600" height="400" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_09861.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_09861-220x147.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting sentimental with interactive video</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/11/2015/spark-of-digital-getting-sentimental-with-interactive-video/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 15:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4435</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Attention spans are decreasing at an alarming rate.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://blogs.sap.com/innovation/sales-marketing/thanks-social-media-average-attention-span-now-shorter-goldfish-01251966" target="_blank">Attention spans are decreasing at an alarming rate</a>. Not only does your content need to pique interest and attract visitors; it has to keep them hooked, too. With Web 2.0 came the advent of amazing new interactive tools for marketers to reach audiences, and videos are no exception. It’s not enough to be the visually stimulating alternative to boring old text anymore, video has to promise a payoff and offer a reason to stay.</p>
<p>Enter the folks at <em><a href="http://www.raptmedia.com/" target="_blank">Rapt Media</a></em>, who have created something awesome. Their platform allows users to easily create interactive videos with a smart and simple interface. And it even has SEO capabilities baked right in. Check out how they were able to help <em>Deloitte</em> gamify their recruiting process with a slickly designed video that plays out like one of those <em>Choose Your Own Adventure</em> books from when you were a kid.</p>
<p><iframe src="http://cdn1.raptmedia.com/projects/j2Nu6adZ/embed?autoplay=false&amp;controls=overlay#http://www.raptmedia.com/project/deloitte" width="100%" height="300" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Iframes are required to view this content.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Interactive videos aren’t necessarily new; clickable links and embedded popups are common across the web, especially on sites like <em>YouTube</em> and <em>Vimeo</em>. What <em>Rapt</em> has done is produce interactive videos that demand viewer attention. That’s why they can tout longer user engagement and higher CTRs.</p>
<p>So how does it all work? <em>Rapt’s</em> platform is simple yet elegant in its design.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-4437 alignright" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Untitled21.png" alt="Untitled2" width="900" height="532" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled21.png 900w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled21-220x130.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></p>
<p>An interactive layer is placed over the main video with clickable hotspots linking to other clips at strategic points. This allows marketers to create videos with multiple outcomes, depending on a viewer’s preference. The result is almost like a built-in A/B test (or A/B/C/D…) showing which path each user took.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.prdaily.com/Main/Articles/The_role_of_sentiment_in_social_data_analysis__16072.aspx" target="_blank">Brand sentiment</a> has become an increasingly important aspect of digital marketing. The ability to understand an audience at a granular level is invaluable to marketers. So building rich, interactive videos that hold viewer attention and demand genuine engagement is no small thing, and worth our attention.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cradles to Crayons</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/22/2014/cradles-to-crayons/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 16:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4813</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[With the holidays approaching, we decided to break from the traditional FVM festive quiz and do something a little a different.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the holidays approaching, we decided to break from the traditional FVM festive quiz and do something a little a different. We closed our MacBooks and caravanned down to Cradles to Crayons in Conshohocken.</p>
<p>Cradles to Crayons helps individuals and businesses to get hands on with clothing collections, fundraisers or working in their warehouses, and provide children living in low income families or homelessness with essential items such as clothes, toys and school materials. These gently used or new goods help to keep some of Philadelphia’s most vulnerable kids safe, protected from the weather and ready to learn—making them feel valued.</p>
<p>Philadelphia has the highest poverty rate among America’s largest cities, with 130,000 children living in poverty. The city also has the highest rate of deep poverty—people with incomes below the half of the poverty line—at 12.2 percent, including 60,000 children.</p>
<p>So we were grateful for the opportunity to roll up our sleeves as volunteers in the warehouse and sort some of the thousands of clothes donated each year.</p>
<p>If you or your company would like to contribute to this great cause, just contact the amazing people at <a href="http://www.cradlestocrayons.org/">Cradles to Crayons</a>.</p>
<p>We highly recommend it.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4815" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-211.jpg" alt="photo 2[1]" width="700" height="525" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-211.jpg 700w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-211-220x165.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4818" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-2.jpeg" alt="Unknown-2" width="700" height="525" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-2.jpeg 700w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-2-220x165.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4816" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-5.jpg" alt="photo 5" width="700" height="525" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-5.jpg 700w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-5-220x165.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4817" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-11.jpeg" alt="Unknown-1" width="700" height="525" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-11.jpeg 700w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-11-220x165.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4819" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-3.jpeg" alt="Unknown-3" width="700" height="525" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-3.jpeg 700w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-3-220x165.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4814" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FVM_12-17-14_funny.jpg" alt="FVM_12-17-14_funny" width="700" height="525" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/FVM_12-17-14_funny.jpg 700w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/FVM_12-17-14_funny-220x165.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Taking the fall (internship): Amanda!</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/24/2014/taking-the-fall-internship-amanda/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 17:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4271</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Have you ever met a Lilly Pulitzer-loving, globetrotting, Duke-basketball-nut?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever met a Lilly Pulitzer-loving, globetrotting, Duke-basketball-nut? Now you have! Say hello to our newest intern, Amanda Lang.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4272" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/IMG_0511.jpg" alt="" width="864" height="576" /></p>
<p>Keen to get stuck into all things FVM, the Elon University Communications graduate will gain a bucket-load of experience across branding, strategy, creative, advertising and media.</p>
<p>Together with tons of other cool stuff, Amanda will be putting her marketing and social media skills to good use in assisting on OCE’s Choose My Future fall campaign and Ambler’s Fashion For A Cause event in October. Go, Amanda!</p>
<p>We offer a number of internship opportunities each year, so if you’re interested in being our next, email us at <a href="mailto:*protected email*">*protected email*</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
