<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Jon Cohen &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/blog/author/jcohen/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>B2B, coast to coast</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/05/2017/our-30th-birthday-and-some-exciting-news/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 04:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Cohen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6930</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[FVM is 30 years old!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FVM is 30 years old! Finally, we’re mature, sensible adults. So happy birthday to us. And our big news is that we’re opening a second location in beautiful Portland, OR to expand our B2B brand and marketing offering and better serve west coast businesses.</p>
<p>Portland is a city with thriving tech and B2B industries, top creative talent, and without a doubt one of the best food cart scenes we’ve ever binged on. Looking right at you <a href="https://www.yelp.com/biz/nongs-khao-man-gai-portland">Nong’s</a>. <em>And,</em> Portland is well connected to other major business hubs like Seattle and San Francisco. For us, the expansion is an opportunity to do more of what we’re passionate about: working with savvy clients to build and sustain standout brands. We’ll seek out companies to partner with in complex and competitive B2B industries and help position them to compete, grow, and win, just like we always have.</p>
<p>But apart from spreading out to the west coast, it’s business as usual. We’ll keep on keepin’ on with the same hard working, forward thinking approach that got us this far.</p>
<p>Here’s to the next 30 years! And welcome to the world FVM Portland.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Software provider ProLease hires FVM</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/11/01/2016/prolease-hires-fvm/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 19:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Cohen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6381</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We’re thrilled to announce that ProLease Software has become our new client.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We’re thrilled to announce that ProLease Software has become our new client.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6389 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/ProLease-Logo-2.png" alt="ProLease Logo" width="600" height="197" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/ProLease-Logo-2.png 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/ProLease-Logo-2-220x72.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p>The fast-growing Real Estate and Facility Management software company has signed on for brand positioning, visual identity, web design, and full 2017 integrated marketing strategy, as it looks to strengthen its offering and grow market share. And with over 600 clients, a much-loved product, and an excellent reputation, we can’t wait to support <a href="http://proleasesoftware.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ProLease</a> in taking on the competition.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6370 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/fall_logos.jpg" alt="fall_logos" width="600" height="300" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fall_logos.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fall_logos-220x110.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p>ProLease is one of many great businesses we’ve been fortunate enough to add to our roster recently. Others include:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://golightpath.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lightpath</a>, a major New York regional business telecom company offering high-performance connectivity for medium to enterprise-level businesses, who hired FVM for corporate and product brand positioning, visual identity, web design, and campaigns.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://clerycenter.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Clery Center for Security on Campus</a>, a national non-profit organization that works with college and university communities to create safer campuses, who joined us for brand positioning, visual identity, web design, and marketing strategy.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.lsslibraries.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Library Systems and Services (LS&amp;S)</a>, a national company that partners with local government to improve operations and services for their Library systems, who came onboard for brand positioning, web design, and marketing strategy.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.ncea.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">National Catholic Educational Association (NCEA)</a>, the world’s largest private-professional education organization, who took us on for brand positioning, and visual identity.</li>
</ul>
<p>We love working with such a diverse range of B2B businesses. Finding unique ways to solve varied marketing obstacles across complex industries is what gets us up in the morning.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The B2B brand exam</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/03/30/2016/the-b2b-brand-exam/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 14:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Cohen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6115</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[“I’m sorry to have to tell you this, but you have a brand problem” feels like a brave thing to say to a prospective client.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>“I’m sorry to have to tell you this, but you have a brand problem” feels like a brave thing to say to a prospective client.</p>
<p>They came asking for a lead gen campaign and already mentioned “ROI” eight times in fifteen minutes. These people want results, fast. And while we could develop a lead gen campaign complete with goals and KPIs, whatever success we generated would be short-lived.</p>
<p>It’s tough news to break, but we’d rather be in it for the long haul.</p>
<p>Companies usually come to us for help with a specific marketing challenge. They’re reaching out to a B2B agency with a simple need for more qualified leads, killer content, a digital presence, or a new product launch. They <em>know</em> the tactics they want to pursue and are looking for a partner to help them execute their vision.</p>
<p>So we listen. We ask a lot of questions. And we find the holes.</p>
<p>More often that not, those holes are in the brand. Because for every lead generated, piece of content created, campaign launched, or website built, it all comes back to brand. If your brand isn’t watertight — if it isn’t consistent with what your marketing is saying or doesn’t connect to your audience — then the aforementioned tactics may produce numbers, but they won’t land. They may even harm your relationship with customers in the long run.</p>
<h3><strong>A brand solution</strong></h3>
<p>B2B marketing has become a complicated machine, and it’s easy to believe that small iterations on your tactical approach will earn you new leads, greater share of wallet, <em>and</em> advance your brand all at the same time. But to find sustained success, a brand needs to know exactly who it is. It needs to be strong, consistent, and cohesive across all touch points.</p>
<p>So before you get into any costly tactics, first examine your brand. Here’s how:</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>Inquisition your position<br />
</strong>What does your brand promise and is that promise being met? What exactly are your customers gaining from their relationship with you? Are you selling products or offering helpful solutions? Take a step back and analyze where your brand is right now. Does it all make sense?</li>
</ol>
<ol start="2">
<li><strong>Take a long hard look at yourself<br />
</strong>Consistency is key. Look across all marketing platforms and sales materials. Is the messaging strong and cohesive? Is the visual brand solid? Do you see any disconnect? What are you actually communicating?</li>
</ol>
<ol start="3">
<li><strong>Check for structural damage<br />
</strong>How is your brand architecture holding up at mother brand, product and sub-brand level? Is it clear? Is it intuitive? Over time, architecture can loosen, weaken, or fall completely out of alignment.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="4">
<li><strong>Eye up the competition<br />
</strong>Analyze positioning, messaging, creative, content, social, and advertising activity. How does your brand compare? Where are the opportunities to differentiate? It’s not good enough to say, “we’re different.” You need to strategically define your ownable space.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="5">
<li><strong>Go inside<br />
</strong>Talk to people within your organization. These are the people in direct contact with customers; your brand advocates. How do they perceive your value proposition? Do they have a clear idea of what your company stands for, and are they representing it?</li>
</ol>
<ol start="6">
<li><strong>Go outside<br />
</strong>How do your partners and customers feel about your brand? Reach out to customers, sales reps, suppliers, distribution channels, and any industry insiders. Their perspectives are crucial, and they probably won’t sugarcoat them.</li>
</ol>
<p>These are just some of the methods you can use to dig into your brand. And as you begin these important assessments, you’ll probably find the same kind of holes we usually uncover.</p>
<p>Your team won’t agree on the results. Your customers, partners or investors won’t completely align. You may begin to question everything you thought you knew about your brand. Paranoia is completely normal.</p>
<p>But if you face your fears, do the hard work, and begin building an authentic brand from the bottom up, you’ll lay the foundation for marketing tactics that yield both immediate and long-term success.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tech start-up Proscia hires FVM</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/27/2015/tech-start-up-proscia-partners-with-fvm/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 16:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Cohen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5199</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that we’ve added Proscia, a medical technology start-up, to our roster of clients.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We’re excited to announce that we’ve added Proscia, a medical technology start-up, to our roster of clients.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-5647" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FinalStyleTile2.jpg" alt="FinalStyleTile2" width="858" height="296" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/FinalStyleTile2.jpg 858w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/FinalStyleTile2-220x76.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 858px) 100vw, 858px" /></p>
<p>We’ve engaged to take on branding, messaging, and web design for the digital pathology solutions provider, as it goes to market with its first-generation cloud-based software platform dedicated to organizing the world’s pathology information.</p>
<p>The company has a big story to tell, with a computing platform that can revolutionize pathology through an array of technical features and specific benefits, so we’re excited to amplify Proscia’s game-changing vision</p>
<p>Proscia is the latest technology software and services client to partner with us, joining recent additions <a href="http://www.archerims.com/" target="_blank">Archer Investment Management Solutions</a>, <a href="http://www.arrayasolutions.com/" target="_blank">Arraya Solutions</a>, and <a href="http://www.esopeconomics.com/telescope" target="_blank">ESOP Economics</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Honor hat-trick</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/05/19/2015/honor-hat-trick/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 14:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Cohen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5066</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In our B2B game, creating cut-through digital content that connects buyers to sellers and affects real business change is what it’s all about.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In our B2B game, creating cut-through digital content that connects buyers to sellers and affects real business change is what it’s all about. So it’s nice to receive recognition when you do it well.</p>
<div id="attachment_5208" style="max-width: 710px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="wp-image-5208 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1317-copy.jpg" alt="L-R: Karen Murphy (Director, Media), Jon Cohen (EVP), Alex Pickel (Director, Client Services)" width="700" height="301" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1317-copy.jpg 700w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1317-copy-220x95.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">L-R: Karen Murphy (Director, Media), Jon Cohen (EVP), Alex Pickel (Director, Client Services)</p></div>
<p>Recently, we potted two shiny new statues and one glimmering prism that say “pretty, pretty good!” for online marketing, design, and an integrated digital campaign.</p>
<p>Univar’s <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/work/portfolio_post/univar-connectivity/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>Connectivity</em></a> E-Zine picked up a Gold <a href="https://www.daveyawards.com/awards/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Davey Award</a> and Gold <a href="http://contentmarketingawards.com/about/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Content Marketing Award</a> for Best Design, while CommVault’s <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/work/portfolio_post/cv-total-value/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><em>Total Value of Simpana Software</em></a> took a Silver <a href="https://www.w3award.com/awards/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">W3 Award</a> for Integrated Digital Campaign.</p>
<p><em>Connectivity </em>continues to deliver stellar content through beautiful design and technology; while <em>Total Value</em> leveraged key customer research and an awesome efficiencies calculator to educate and engage tech buyers—paying off in hundreds of qualified leads.</p>
<p>These awards reflect two things we pride ourselves on delivering for our clients: powerful content marketing and effective lead-gen campaigns. And because awards can’t be won without trusting and talented clients, my hat goes off to them.</p>
<p>B2B isn’t about print ads, conservative blues, or one-size-fits-all plug and play work. It’s human and it’s helpful. It’s about people. And that’s always at the heart of our strategies.</p>
<p>We have a lot of fun learning what buyers like, how to reach and engage them, and what to do once we have their attention. That&#8217;s where we get our kicks, and awards are the icing on the cake.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FVM scores four new clients</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/11/2014/fvm-scores-four-new-clients/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 16:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Cohen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4762</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Building on another year of sustained growth, we’re excited to have added four new clients to our roster!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Building on another year of sustained growth, we’re excited to have added four new clients to our roster!</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-4763 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/4-Logos.jpg" alt="4 Logos" width="600" height="600" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/4-Logos.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/4-Logos-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/4-Logos-220x220.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p>Investment management software company, Market Street Advisors; technology services provider, Arraya Solutions; and repurchase obligation software firm, ESOP Economics join an already diverse and burgeoning client list; while the Perinatal Research Consortium has signed on as a new pro bono account.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Market Street Advisors</strong>, a leading investment management software provider, has engaged us for a full company rebrand and creative services, including naming, brand identity, product positioning, website design and development, content marketing and brand launch.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Arraya Solutions</strong>, a top infrastructure consulting, application development and managed services provider, comes onboard for brand positioning, website design and development, content marketing and a comprehensive marcomm strategy.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>ESOP Economics</strong>, the industry leader in repurchase obligation software and consultation, selected us to launch its latest software to the market, with a campaign including digital strategy, content marketing, event strategy, social media and media planning.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Perinatal Research Consortium</strong>, an integrated system of nine research centers dedicated to research in Perinatal and Women’s health, has joined with us to develop their brand and design and their first website.</li>
</ul>
<p>Over the past year we’ve seen more and more B2B companies recognizing a need to elevate their brands and distinguish their offerings in increasingly competitive markets. Lending our strategic and creative guidance in this way is something we love and have proven good at—so we’re looking forward to the work.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
