<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>digital strategy &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/digital-strategy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>CV SolutionSets</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/08/2014/cv-solutionsets/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 16:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=4608</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When CommVault decided to offer a radically different way to purchase their enterprise software, FVM was challenged to deliver that message to the market.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When CommVault decided to offer a radically different way to purchase their enterprise software, FVM was challenged to deliver that message to the market. Through striking iconography, bold copywriting, enhanced UX and graphics, we told compelling and unique stories for each Solution Set on CommVault.com. The marriage of engaging design and content aligned seamlessly with sales initiatives and propelled the company forward.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Email marketing and the numbers you can count on</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/24/2014/email-marketing-and-the-numbers-you-can-count-on/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 14:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[email marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[infographic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3926</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There’s a piece of paper I keep pinned at my desk.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There’s a piece of paper I keep pinned at my desk. It’s filled with numbers, stats to be precise, and serves as a daily reminder that email marketing is a powerful tool. One that should be at the heart of every suitable strategic campaign, integrated as a conversation tool in nurturing customers.</p>
<p>The rise of social networks, mobile and instant messaging has shifted focus away from email, and while these channels are becoming increasingly important for marketers to engage on, it remains essential to harness the force of the mighty inbox.</p>
<p>When planned properly and executed in the right way, emails become a highly targeted, cost-effective and powerful communicator that gets results.</p>
<p>Here, the numbers I’ve collected speak for themselves.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Infographic31.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-3948" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Infographic31.jpg" alt="Infographic3[1]" width="470" height="1625" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Great news for the good online marketers out there</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/14/2013/great-news-for-the-good-online-marketers-out-there/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 15:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[campaign reporting & analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3064</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Although I&#8217;m only halfway through a MarketingProfs University &#8220;Search Marketing School&#8221; online seminar (5 courses down, 5 to go!), the overall theme is already becoming very clear: with its newest SEO updates, Google is attempting to penalize over-optimized websites, and reward sites that are user-friendly, nicely designed, and stocked with helpful information for customers and [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although I&#8217;m only halfway through a MarketingProfs University &#8220;Search Marketing School&#8221; online seminar (5 courses down, 5 to go!), the overall theme is already becoming very clear: with its newest SEO updates, Google is attempting to penalize over-optimized websites, and reward sites that are user-friendly, nicely designed, and stocked with helpful information for customers and prospects.</p>
<p>Yay for common-sense marketing to humans! Boo for back-end Search Engine Optimization trickery!</p>
<p>From what I&#8217;m learning, less emphasis is being placed on excessive link building, keyword stuffing, and meaningless irrelevant content. Instead, things like a quick site load time; a friendly mobile experience; useful, timely multi-media content; quality links; and a strong social presence matter more.</p>
<p>So, if you&#8217;ve been trying to &#8220;do it right&#8221; all along by creating a user-friendly, nicely designed website that attempts to offer customers and potential customers helpful information – you’re in luck! Way to go, Google.</p>
<p>Of course, the basic structural back-end geeky web stuff, like proper meta-tagging, 301 redirects, and HTML site maps are still very necessary. (Do you like how I threw those terms around? Lucky for me, I have our awesome web team on hand to translate into English.)</p>
<p>Next on the list: FINISH the online seminar. Perhaps I&#8217;ll come across some more interesting nuggets to share from the next five courses.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Go easy on the eyes</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/05/2013/go-easy-on-the-eyes/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 19:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BBEdit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CSS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HTML]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Notepad++]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TextWrangler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3019</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The other day as I was working on the newly-redesigned Faith In The Future Foundation website, FVM Sr.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The other day as I was working on the <a href="http://www.faithinthefuture.com" target="_blank">newly-redesigned Faith In The Future Foundation website</a>, FVM Sr. Art Director Mark Parker idled for a moment as he strolled past my desk and made the following comment:</p>
<p>&#8220;I can&#8217;t believe you like to code like that.&#8221;</p>
<p>Code like what? I thought I was doing it correctly. Not so. He was of course referring to TextWrangler&#8217;s default color settings, which, though not deal-breaking, do leave something to be desired. I tried to justify my nonchalant (read: negligent) attitude towards optimizing my workspace, but he remained unimpressed and, if I was being honest with myself, my position was defensible only by laziness.</p>
<div id="attachment_3020" style="max-width: 230px" class="wp-caption alignright"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-1.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="size-medium wp-image-3020 " alt="In TextWrangler's factory settings, attribute names and values are actually different colors, but you wouldn't know from looking..." src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-1-220x220.jpg" width="220" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-1-220x220.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-1-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-1.jpg 425w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">In TextWrangler&#8217;s factory settings, attribute names and values are actually different colors, but you wouldn&#8217;t know from looking&#8230;</p></div>
<p>One of the few things I miss about my old Windows-based workstation is <a href="http://notepad-plus-plus.org" target="_blank">Notepad++</a>, with its granular syntax highlighting options and slew of built in color schemes that make changing it up a breeze (although even the default settings look good). TextWrangler ostensibly has but two options: the factory settings, or customizing each color manually. You can, however, add color preference files to the ~/Library/Application Support/TextWrangler/Color Schemes/ directory and then activate them using the preset dropdown in the Text Colors preferences menu from within TextWrangler. In newer versions of OS X, the user Library folder is hidden by default, so you&#8217;ll need to use the Terminal or hit Go &gt; Go to Folder in the Finder.</p>
<p>Overhearing our conversation, our new developer, Kat Sioson, suggested <a href="http://www.andrewhazelden.com/blog/2012/06/midnight-blue-color-scheme-for-textwrangler-and-bbedit/" target="_blank">Andrew Hazelden&#8217;s Midnight Blue color scheme for BBEdit and TextWrangler</a>, and soon I was knee deep in the world of user-created color schemes. You can find a good entry point <a href="http://bbeditextras.org/wiki/index.php?title=Color_Schemes" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<p>I found Midnight Blue to be pretty good though I modified it so that general markup is a different color than plain text. I&#8217;m particularly fond of <a href="http://ethanschoonover.com/solarized" target="_blank">Ethan Schoonover&#8217;s Solarized Dark</a>, which is available, along with a Light counterpart, for a variety of applications beyond those from Bare Bones Software.</p>
<p>In the spirit of giving back, I figured I&#8217;d add my own contribution &#8211; <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FVM-Color-Schemes.zip" target="_blank">FVM Dark</a>, which uses the tones on our newly-redesigned agency website.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FVM-Color-Schemes.zip">FVM-Color-Schemes</a></p>
<p>I spend the bulk of my coding time working with HTML and CSS, so if you spend more time with Javascript, Ruby, Python, etc., you may find it needs some tweaking. Just drag and drop the colors around until you find something that works for you.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-3.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-3021" alt="image-3" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-3-220x220.jpg" width="220" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-3-220x220.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-3-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-3.jpg 425w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a><br />
If you&#8217;re in the mood for a more seasonally appropriate work environment, also included in that archive is an Autumn color scheme I put together as well, inspired by the foliage outside our offices. Happy coding!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Volunteering: good for all</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/04/2013/volunteering-good-for-all/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 18:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ambler gives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Big Brothers/Big Sisters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[campaign reporting & analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fashion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pro bono]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[volunteering]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3006</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I don’t think people even realize it but the power of volunteering has an extraordinary rippling effect.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I don’t think people even realize it but the power of volunteering has an extraordinary rippling effect. Not only does the recipient benefit, but the volunteer gets a renewed sense of accomplishment and pride. They bring that feeling to the workplace, which helps build a positive environment for everyone. So it makes sense that employers should encourage community service to help increase morale.</p>
<p>Whether you participate as a team effort on a pro-bono project or you partake in an individual day of service, you are ultimately contributing to a positive work environment. Most people like the idea of giving back to their community but find it difficult to carve out the time. Thankfully, more employers realize this and offer the opportunity to participate in community service within the workplace.</p>
<p>FVM has been fortunate enough to work with a wonderful group of people at Big Brothers Big Sisters/Ambler Gives. They think they’re lucky because they got a free awesome new website, but in reality, our team got the reward. We got to flex our creative muscles beyond our usual realm of B-to-B and into a trendy fashion show event. Our developers explored new software for online donations and ticket purchases. So while we learned new skills and flourished creatively, Ambler Gives kicked off a stellar event benefitting young children. Everyone won.</p>
<p>Benefits of community service:<br />
1. Stronger communities = stronger business opportunities<br />
2. Team building – working on a goal outside of your everyday office routine<br />
3. Morale boost – Pride and personal satisfaction that comes from helping someone in need<br />
(Proven to positively impact your physical and mental health)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Attention all browsers: Testing websites in all conditions</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/29/2013/attention-all-browsers-testing-websites-in-all-conditions/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 19:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AB testing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cross browser]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2818</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Designers all too often understand the frustration of having so many web browsers.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Designers all too often understand the frustration of having so many web browsers. A beautiful looking website works great on modern web browsers like Safari, Firefox, and Chrome, but performs horridly in older versions of Internet Explorer. So what’s the solution? Cross browser testing.</p>
<p>The web is evolving, pretty much every minute of every day. Web browsers are constantly updating their programs to accommodate for new technologies and pushing out updates to their software on a regular basis. Unfortunately that leaves designers and coders at the mercy of their users, some of whom may not have or cannot update to more savvy HTML5 browsers. So cross browser testing is an important step in the development process.</p>
<p>Cross browser testing is exactly what it sounds like. You look at a coded website in one browser, click all the links, view all the page templates, and make sure that everything looks and works as expected. It gets tedious sometimes. There are tools to help you along the way, probably the best is <a href="http://www.crossbrowsertesting.com/" target="_blank">http://www.crossbrowsertesting.com/</a>.</p>
<p>This monthly subscriptions service provides remote machine access to dozens of web browser platforms old and new. Their screenshot feature allows you to submit a URL and automatically scan and save images of your website’s layout in every browser you choose. You can also use their live testing method to select an operating system and web browser to actively navigate a website’s functionality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Using full-bleed photography to make websites pop</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/29/2013/using-full-bleed-photography-to-make-websites-pop/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 19:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[full-bleed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2820</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If you haven’t noticed already, this website is filled with full-bleed photography.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you haven’t noticed already, this website is filled with full-bleed photography. Just see <a title="Home" href="/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="Work" href="/work/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="Jordy Pickel" href="/people/jordy-pickel/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="About" href="/about/" target="_blank">here</a>, and <a title="Contact" href="/contact/" target="_blank">here</a>. This type of coding process allows for hi-resolution images to expand or contract to the frame’s width, resulting in a flawless edge to edge look. There are of course, some things to watch out for:</p>
<h3>1. Have really nice images</h3>
<p>If your photos are hi-resolution, there’s little point in stuffing your design with full-bleed photos. You have to allow for the image to expand to some of the largest browser sizes. On a typical desktop, that could 1,500 pixels wide. New computers such as the MacBook with Retina display or the new iPad have two times the screen resolution as they used to. That means that a standard 1,024 x 768 iPad actually has a resolution of 2,048 x 1,536 pixels.</p>
<p>On our website we use images that are 2,400 pixels wide. For now, that’s probably enough to look good on most every device. However, as resolutions standards continue to increase, the max image size is probably going to have to go up.</p>
<h3>2. Use CSS to format images, not JavaScript</h3>
<p>Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) are code documents that tell your website how to look. It controls column width, typography, colors, and image effects. JavaScript on the other hand is a script that&#8217;s loaded as the page loads, and can alter the look and feel of a website. JavaScript isn&#8217;t horrible in this scenario, but CSS is just an easier way to go.</p>
<p>To allow for images to expand and contract to their frame, just indicate the image&#8217;s full width:</p>
<pre>img { width: 100%; height: auto; }</pre>
<p>This will adjust the image&#8217;s width to 100% of the container it&#8217;s in, and adjust the height proportionally. If you wanted to make the image &#8220;bleed&#8221; off the page (go 100% of the width while <em>also</em> going 100% of the height) you&#8217;ll want to place the image as a background image. In that scenario, you would indicate that the background image have a cover effect:</p>
<pre>div { background-image: url(imagepath.jpg); background-size: cover; }</pre>
<p>This adjusts the background image to fit both horizontally and vertically in the container you specify. If the image is a wide one, it will expand to 100% of the frame&#8217;s height and the sides of them image would be cut off. If it were a skinny image, the width would expand to 100% and the top and bottom would be cut off.</p>
<p>This is of course not an exact science; you website&#8217;s design will look slightly different according to the user&#8217;s browser size. However, with the proper background images, it can look really nice.</p>
<h3>3. Understand that not all browsers are your friend</h3>
<p>As is the case with most HTML5 techniques, image resizing doesn&#8217;t always work in every browser. Namely, Internet Explorer 7 and 8. Rather than loading in a separate page or image for those specific browsers, you can fix their deficiencies with <a href="http://www.modernizr.com" target="_blank">Modernizr</a> or using a <a href="https://github.com/louisremi/background-size-polyfill" target="_blank">Polyfill</a>. Always cross browser check!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Soccer scores with social media</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/07/20/2013/u-s-soccer-scores-with-social-media/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 15:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Women's Soccer Team]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3059</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The 1999 Women’s World Cup team captured fans’ hearts with their down-to-earth, girl-next-door persona.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 1999 Women’s World Cup team captured fans’ hearts with their down-to-earth, girl-next-door persona. Now, thanks to the the U.S. Soccer Federation’s <a href="http://www.youtube.com/user/ussoccerdotcom?feature=g-high-crv" target="_blank">phenomenal online media presence</a>, we fans feel more connected than ever to these incredible players.</p>
<p>Never have athletes been so accessible. Hop on to U.S. Soccer’s YouTube channel and watch practice footage, sideline clips, and player interviews. You can even travel with the team as they make their way to the 2012 Olympics via their <a href="http://www.youtube.com/user/ussoccerdotcom/videos?flow=grid&amp;view=50&amp;shelf_index=7" target="_blank">“Behind The Crest” series</a>. Still can’t get enough? See how some players live in the off-season as they take you to their hometowns in the “Back Home” series.</p>
<p>This may not seem like a big deal to some, but think about the last time you felt like you were part of your favorite team. Professional athletes are becoming more and more removed from society—forgetting the fans and focusing solely on endorsement deals and big paychecks. It’s nice to see some sports organizations, especially federal governing bodies, like US Soccer, sticking to their roots and keeping in mind those that fuel fire of their success: their fans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter is advancing: Are you?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/05/2012/twitter-is-advancing-are-you/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 18:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=2416</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The debate over Twitter’s place in modern day culture is complex –some people mock it and some people tweet it.  But one thing’s for sure: businesses are benefitting immensely from the social networking site.  Without a doubt, Twitter has allowed businesses to grow their brands, extend customer service, boost SEO performance and the list goes [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The debate over Twitter’s place in modern day culture is complex –some people mock it and some people tweet it.  But one thing’s for sure: businesses are benefitting immensely from the social networking site.  Without a doubt, Twitter has allowed businesses to grow their brands, extend customer service, boost SEO performance and the list goes on.  Whether you’re the type of person who scans Twitter every hour for celebrity perspectives on life or you’re doing life just fine without Twitter , you will have difficulty in trying to argue against Twitter’s long list of benefits to a business’s success.</p>
<p>We can tackle all the specific benefits more in-depth at another time (or visit this <a href="http://www.ragan.com/Main/Articles/15_business_benefits_of_Twitter__44058.aspx">Ragan article</a> for a quick review), but what I want to convey immediately is that <strong>now</strong> is the time for businesses to immerse themselves.  There’s a new door opening to join (if you haven’t already) or to improve your Twitter ROI.</p>
<h2>Twitter is changing in big ways, fast</h2>
<p>In December, Twitter launched branded pages.  If you are unaware of this development, you’ll want to review Twitter’s <a href="https://business.twitter.com/advertise/enhanced-profile/">Enhanced Profile</a> help page.  Basically, in December, Twitter launched a branded page as an option, which “increases your brand’s Twitter presence by prominently featuring your most important content and visually branding your page.”</p>
<p>With the enhanced profile pages in mind, Twitter is now moving forward with a new focus on creating a new “experience,” both for businesses and their customers.  In my mind two major developments capture this new focus entirely.</p>
<h3>1. The Open Platform</h3>
<p>Twitter’s end goal with an open platform is to create new ways for customers to engage with your brand.  The industry’s majority agrees with <a href="http://www.readwriteweb.com/archives/author/richard-macmanus.php">Richard Macmanus</a> in that open web services is a major web trend picking up and Twitter’s new API (Application Program Inteface) is an ideal platform to see the advantages.  By opening their platform to independent developers, Twitter allows “brands to create deeper interactions with consumers through custom experiences,” says Mashable’s David Clarke.  From smaller mobile applications to versions of Twitter visually recreated, developers now have the capability to build onto Twitter’s infrastructure and expand the user’s experience exponentially.  A brand is not limited to its look and feel living on Twitter.  You can now combine Twitter’s functions with your own ideas.  Biz Stone says &#8220;The API has been … inarguably, the most important thing we’ve done with Twitter.”</p>
<h3>2. T-Commerce</h3>
<p>Facebook failed at it, now Twitter will attempt to succeed where it’s adversary failed.  E-commerce on Twitter has pronounced itself loud and clear just recently with multiple real opportunities for e-commerce companies that you’ve probably overlooked.</p>
<ul>
<li>First and foremost, the most easily forgotten, the <strong>call-to-action</strong>: you must provide a link in every tweet.  If someone is interested in a product or service, make sure you’ve given them a way to act.</li>
<li>Provide great customer service. Everything is public, so customers will gain trust that you will stand by your offerings.</li>
<li>Pay on Twitter.  Yes, customers can now pay directly via Twitter.  This will expedite purchasing process and reduce consumer hesitation.  Look into <a href="http://chirpify.com/">Cherpify</a> and Twitpay.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you currently using Twitter to help grow your business and reach customers?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
