<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>full-bleed &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/full-bleed/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Using full-bleed photography to make websites pop</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/29/2013/using-full-bleed-photography-to-make-websites-pop/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 19:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[full-bleed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2820</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If you haven’t noticed already, this website is filled with full-bleed photography.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you haven’t noticed already, this website is filled with full-bleed photography. Just see <a title="Home" href="/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="Work" href="/work/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="Jordy Pickel" href="/people/jordy-pickel/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="About" href="/about/" target="_blank">here</a>, and <a title="Contact" href="/contact/" target="_blank">here</a>. This type of coding process allows for hi-resolution images to expand or contract to the frame’s width, resulting in a flawless edge to edge look. There are of course, some things to watch out for:</p>
<h3>1. Have really nice images</h3>
<p>If your photos are hi-resolution, there’s little point in stuffing your design with full-bleed photos. You have to allow for the image to expand to some of the largest browser sizes. On a typical desktop, that could 1,500 pixels wide. New computers such as the MacBook with Retina display or the new iPad have two times the screen resolution as they used to. That means that a standard 1,024 x 768 iPad actually has a resolution of 2,048 x 1,536 pixels.</p>
<p>On our website we use images that are 2,400 pixels wide. For now, that’s probably enough to look good on most every device. However, as resolutions standards continue to increase, the max image size is probably going to have to go up.</p>
<h3>2. Use CSS to format images, not JavaScript</h3>
<p>Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) are code documents that tell your website how to look. It controls column width, typography, colors, and image effects. JavaScript on the other hand is a script that&#8217;s loaded as the page loads, and can alter the look and feel of a website. JavaScript isn&#8217;t horrible in this scenario, but CSS is just an easier way to go.</p>
<p>To allow for images to expand and contract to their frame, just indicate the image&#8217;s full width:</p>
<pre>img { width: 100%; height: auto; }</pre>
<p>This will adjust the image&#8217;s width to 100% of the container it&#8217;s in, and adjust the height proportionally. If you wanted to make the image &#8220;bleed&#8221; off the page (go 100% of the width while <em>also</em> going 100% of the height) you&#8217;ll want to place the image as a background image. In that scenario, you would indicate that the background image have a cover effect:</p>
<pre>div { background-image: url(imagepath.jpg); background-size: cover; }</pre>
<p>This adjusts the background image to fit both horizontally and vertically in the container you specify. If the image is a wide one, it will expand to 100% of the frame&#8217;s height and the sides of them image would be cut off. If it were a skinny image, the width would expand to 100% and the top and bottom would be cut off.</p>
<p>This is of course not an exact science; you website&#8217;s design will look slightly different according to the user&#8217;s browser size. However, with the proper background images, it can look really nice.</p>
<h3>3. Understand that not all browsers are your friend</h3>
<p>As is the case with most HTML5 techniques, image resizing doesn&#8217;t always work in every browser. Namely, Internet Explorer 7 and 8. Rather than loading in a separate page or image for those specific browsers, you can fix their deficiencies with <a href="http://www.modernizr.com" target="_blank">Modernizr</a> or using a <a href="https://github.com/louisremi/background-size-polyfill" target="_blank">Polyfill</a>. Always cross browser check!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
