<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>art direction &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/art-direction/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Doodling</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/02/07/2014/doodling/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[art direction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doodling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3368</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ve always doodled.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve always doodled. I doodle in meetings and when I&#8217;m on the phone. Some of my doodles blossom into full-fledged drawings. At my previous job, this practice was frowned upon. The boss thought I wasn&#8217;t paying attention. But I was. My current bosses accept and even encourage it. This blog post will provide you, the reader, with different levels of detail about this topic, broken down as follows:</p>
<p><b>For the person who thinks reading a blog is like a homework assignment and just wants to look at pictures of some of the doodles that I&#8217;ve made:</b></p>
<p><b>For the person who can&#8217;t be bothered reading long, boring blog posts, read this:</b></p>
<p>Doodling helps people retain information during meetings (stop here) (or, for the person that is skeptical and would like a little more clarification):</p>
<p><b>For the person who is skeptical and just wants a little more detail:</b></p>
<p>When you doodle, you don&#8217;t daydream. Daydreaming may seem absentminded and pointless, but it actually demands a lot of the brain&#8217;s processing power. You start daydreaming about a vacation, which leads you to think about potential destinations, how you would pay for the trip, whether you could get the flight upgraded, how you might score a bigger hotel room. These cognitions require what psychologists call &#8220;executive functioning&#8221; — for example, planning for the future and comparing costs and benefits.</p>
<p>Doodling, in contrast, requires very few executive resources but just enough cognitive effort to keep you from daydreaming, which — if unchecked — will jump-start activity in cortical networks that will keep you from remembering what&#8217;s going on. Doodling forces your brain to expend just enough energy to stop it from daydreaming but not so much that you don&#8217;t pay attention.  (stop here) (or, for entire articles on the subject):</p>
<p><b>For the person who wants to read entire articles on the subject:</b></p>
<p><a href="http://content.time.com/time/health/article/0,8599,1882127,00.html#ixzz2mXaZ1ClX">http://content.time.com/time/health/article/0,8599,1882127,00.html#ixzz2mXaZ1Cl</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2012/08/03/i-draw-pictures-all-day">http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2012/08/03/i-draw-pictures-all-day</a>/</p>
<p><a href="http://www.cnn.com/2013/10/03/business/doodlilng-in-a-meeting-drawing">http://www.cnn.com/2013/10/03/business/doodlilng-in-a-meeting-drawing</a>/</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Remembering Professor Anliker</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/14/2013/remembering-professor-anliker/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 18:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[art direction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3112</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[These days, college graduates can boast that they are a proud owner of a degree in computer design.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>These days, college graduates can boast that they are a proud owner of a degree in computer design. That is like having a degree in pencil design. After all, the computer is also a tool to create visual art. Who is teaching these students about how to compose an image; to utilize the visual elements; to even understand what the visual elements are; to understand typography; to understand color concepts; to draw? I consider myself very fortunate to have received superior training in all of those areas, and so much more, largely in one classroom/studio and under the direction of one remarkable person. His name is professor Roger Anliker, and he passed away on September 25 at the age of 89.</p>
<div id="attachment_3113" style="max-width: 230px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img class="size-medium wp-image-3113" alt="Painting by Roger Anliker, self portrait, title and date unknown" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/roger-220x173.jpeg" width="220" height="173" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/roger-220x173.jpeg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/roger-1024x808.jpeg 1024w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/roger.jpeg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Painting by Roger Anliker, self portrait, title and date unknown</p></div>
<p>I took a drawing and painting class freshman year, and was introduced to the man who now comes up in my conversations almost daily. Professor Anliker gave demonstrations in class that were awe-inspiring. He read us passages from Nabokov while we worked. He had us compile lists of things that we would eagerly enter into our notebooks, often alphabetically starting from A. I can remember doing a list of structures and someone calling out chicken-coop for C; a list of flowers with bachelor button for B; a list of hats with snood or shako for S. Everything in the visual arts was based on a strong foundation with Roger. Drawing was first. In writing, he taught us, spelling comes first. That is the foundation. One cannot spell “creatively or artfully.”</p>
<p>He came into the studio on nights and weekends to design, construct, paint and decorate elaborate stages for the live model to integrate with. As he worked on these set-ups, he was always careful to use muted colors, earth tones, gentle shapes and arches, various screens and transparent screeds, all designed to enhance and support the human figure that was to inhabit the space, not detract from it.</p>
<p>He stayed after class to answer questions for students, but while most hurried off to get back to the dorms or leave, a friend and I stayed. Often hours would pass, with Professor Anliker patiently explaining a technical process or even going back to a demonstration. Although we were exhausted, we couldn’t help but think about how much education we were receiving for our tuition dollar. It was practically one-on-one training for hours and hours after everyone else had left.</p>
<p>He was always watching out for students, telling them when to complain to the University when our needs were not being met. He was a sharp critic, and could find flaws in almost anything. It made us work harder as not to disappoint him. He gave us advice from what colors look good on cars to how to eat properly. Even how to keep proper posture when ascending stairs by imagining a string attached to the top of your head being pulled taut as you lift each knee.</p>
<p>Every phase of the arts were covered in the eight courses that I took with Professor Anliker. It didn’t even matter what the course was called, pastel drawing, whatever. As long as I was in the class. He considered me such a fine student that he invited me and a friend over to his inner-sanctum for dinner some time after graduation. We were in awe. The paintings that we had only glimpsed in photos before were on well-lit walls all around his house in full splendor. I can remember the tuna salad he served had grapes in it, which I didn’t think would work, but I was so wrong. The beverage he served was about the best thing I ever tasted. He explained that it was comprised of five fruit juices in carefully measured amounts.</p>
<p>Hours went by that evening, with Professor Anliker explaining concepts to us in all fields, not just fine arts. Just when we thought the evening was over and we started heading for the door in sheer exhaustion, he invited us to sit down as he slid a record out of a sleeve and placed it on the turntable. A multiple-part spoken word record series of Dante’s Inferno started to crackle through the speakers. We started to discreetly slap ourselves, for our bodies could take no more and we were fighting with every ounce of energy to stay awake. We did not want to disappoint the master.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fail harder</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/05/08/2013/fail-harder/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 19:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[art direction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[creative workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[education]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=2546</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Wieden + Kennedy 12, an experimental advertising school run by Portland ad agency W+K, has taught us a valuable lesson in what it means to succeed.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wieden + Kennedy 12, an experimental advertising school run by Portland ad agency W+K, has taught us a valuable lesson in what it means to succeed.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-2548 aligncenter" alt="art_and_copy (1)" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/art_and_copy-1.jpg" width="480" height="270" /></p>
<p>These guys took failure to a whole new level when they bought out all available clear push pins on the west coast in 2006. Over 100,000 thumbtacks were used during a 351 hour period to create a wall mural that spells out Fail Harder, a message that underlines the importance of failure during the creative process.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong> The background is made of push pins. &#8220;The easy way would have been to do the lettering as push pins and leave the wall blank. They chose the hard way. It&#8217;s a perfectly executed concept,&#8221; says David Kennedy of Wieden+Kennedy. &#8220;It&#8217;s like Babe Ruth trying to hit a homerun. If you miss, you miss, but at least you swung the bat as hard as you could.&#8221;</p>
<p>As cool as this mural is, this wasn&#8217;t the first time W+K used the idea of failure as motivation. Check out their <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SlX1S8mJrIQ">1999 Nike ad</a> featuring the one &amp; only, Michael Jordan.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
