<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Branding &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/branding/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Getting more out of your B2B focus groups</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/17/2018/getting-more-out-of-your-b2b-focus-groups/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=7322</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Focus groups often get an unfair rap.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Focus groups often get an unfair rap. In high-stakes B2B environments, the phrase can conjure up images of wasted time and wasted money.</p>
<p>But focus groups provide a valuable opportunity to learn firsthand from customers and prospects about the issues that matter most. As a primary, qualitative research tool, focus groups can be used to uncover the emotional and rational reasons behind behavior, brand loyalty, and the buyer journey.</p>
<p>Extracting value from focus groups requires proper prep work, skilled moderating, and a detailed analysis integrated with other discovery work. This ensures that the time, effort, and resources required for a B2B focus group pay off in insights that drive results.</p>
<p>Here are the critical steps you can take to make sure that your focus group pays off for your business, and how to demonstrate the value of a focus group.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-7344 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Focus-Group-e1516894509534.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="533" /></p>
<p><strong>Set Objectives<br />
</strong>A clear, distinct objective allows for a more focused discussion, leading to deeper understanding of the issues at hand. Defining a clear-cut purpose can filter out surface-level findings and helps avoid leaving a negative impression among participants (who are likely customers).</p>
<p>The objective depends on the progress made during the discovery process, but typically falls into one of three categories:</p>
<p><u>Understanding broad, common topics</u><br />
Early in discovery work, focus groups provide a wide view of the industry, audience, and issues, revealing overarching trends. This approach usually requires extensive follow-up and isn’t recommended for B2B, where these themes can be discovered elsewhere.</p>
<p><u>Validating or refuting themes</u><br />
A focus group that occurs sometime in the middle of discovery work can confirm or deny previously uncovered findings among a broader set of customers. This is likely the best use of a B2B group.</p>
<p><u>Testing creative<br />
</u>Towards the end of discovery and into brand development, you can test the industry tropes and customer preferences uncovered during prior discovery work. The focus group can tell you which directions resonate and which fall flat.</p>
<p><strong>Recruit Participants<br />
</strong>The right mix of participants can make or break a focus group. It’s important that the group is representative of the audience as a whole, but with enough commonalities that the conversation will be productive. Group participants also need to be able to talk openly and honestly among peers.</p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Recruiting for Focus Groups: B2B vs. B2C</strong></span><span style="color: #000000;"><strong><br />
</strong></span>Participant recruiting is probably where B2B focus groups differ most from traditional B2C. Keep these tips in mind when you begin your recruiting process:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Be persistent.</strong> Targeted audiences make for a much smaller pool of possible participants. Professionals are often busy, making them difficult to reach and unlikely to participate.</li>
<li><strong>Beware of biases.</strong> Most participants are recommended and recruited by the sales force because they’re already fans of the brand meaning results could be positively skewed.</li>
<li><strong>Remember the bigger picture.</strong> Only one person from a given customer type or prospect may be represented, even though the purchase decision typically involves multiple roles and functions.</li>
<li><strong>Provide incentives.</strong> Monetary gifts are nice, but the general rule is that professionals need to feel valued and appreciated. A sincere thank you along with specifics on how their participation will ultimately benefit their own business goes a long way.</li>
<li><strong>Be sensitive to privacy concerns.</strong> Having competing businesses in the same group can become problematic if participants aren’t comfortable discussing their challenges or successes in front of the competition.</li>
</ul>
<p>For B2B, consider factors including job title, role, and company size. It’s possible that multiple groups will be needed to achieve the correct balance of sample representation and commonalities for a productive discussion.</p>
<blockquote><p>One of FVM’s large telecom clients segmented its audience into two buckets: enterprise and SMB. These two groups both faced challenges when it came to telecomm needs but approached them from very different contexts. Our client needed to engage with both audiences and sought to determine the best way to approach each.</p>
<p>So we conducted two separate focus groups: varying participants’ job titles, longevity with our client, and industries represented between both groups.</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Craft the Discussion Guide<br />
</strong>Realistically, a B2B focus group will be 2.5 hours total, including time for introductions, breaks, and closing remarks. It’s important to be realistic about what can and cannot be accomplished in this window. Plan for five to six main topics, with probing questions or workshop-style exercises to spur dialogue. Remember: the guide, while important, is merely a tool. It’s up to the group and moderator to engage in dialogue that covers the key topics.</p>
<p>Allow participants to dictate the flow and pace of the conversation by crafting a fluid guide that starts out broader and moves into more specific lines of questioning. Let participants determine the length and depth of each conversation, highlighting which topics are most important.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-7341" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/fvm-034-focus-group-image.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="745" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-034-focus-group-image.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-034-focus-group-image-220x164.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-034-focus-group-image-768x572.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<h6>A nonlinear guide format helps the moderator follow the room, rather than being restricted to a predetermined order of events.</h6>
<p>Use the objectives discussed above as the key starting points for your discussion guides.</p>
<p><u>Understanding broad, common topics<br />
</u>Include open-ended questions that ask participants about their roles, challenges, and competition.</p>
<p><u>Validating or refuting themes<br />
</u>Carefully choose topics that require further explanation. Plan to discuss each one, allowing enough time to hear from each participant and follow up on responses. Don’t waste time on topics that can be explored elsewhere.<strong> </strong></p>
<p><u>Testing creative<br />
</u>Share creative directions to determine how certain images, concepts, and colors make the participants feel. In B2B, focus groups are the perfect opportunity to establish which industry themes are most expected, needed, or overused.</p>
<blockquote><p>For example, we used a focus group to test one industry’s most common uses of imagery: blurred lights, moving traffic, and stock photography of smiling business people. When we ran these tropes by group participants, we discovered that the photos of smiling people were problematic. Group members asked, “Are the people supposed to represent me or the vendor?” On the other hand, the images denoting speed resonated well.</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Moderate the Discussion<br />
</strong>Skilled moderators are able to elicit information beyond “top of mind” responses, uncovering rational, behavioral, and emotional drivers. In order to reach this second and third-level information, keep these functions in mind while moderating:</p>
<ul>
<li>Understand the objective and enough about the subject matter to speak intelligently on it.</li>
<li>Make no assumptions and remain unbiased, maintaining an open mind to all opinions and thoughts.</li>
<li>Demonstrate respect for the participants, proving their time is valuable and their voices are being heard.</li>
<li>Maintain a high energy level throughout varied tasks and question types, including open-ended questions and questions that allow participants to jot down answers.</li>
<li>Manage the conversation, diving deeper where necessary and tactfully cutting off irrelevant topics or commentary.</li>
</ul>
<p>Stay tuned for a follow-up piece with more on moderating B2B focus groups, including a breakdown of the most common B2B focus group participants.</p>
<p><strong>Analyze the Results<br />
</strong>Focus groups represent just one facet of discovery, so it’s important to integrate your findings with data from all other sources. By comparing and contrasting results with interviews, web analytics, and other discovery methods, you’ll find that themes and trends will emerge.</p>
<p>Keep an eye out for these common clues in focus group output:</p>
<ul>
<li>Polarizing conversations that left participants on different sides of the issues often indicate topics that need further exploration and validation.</li>
<li>Topics on which participants spent more time are most likely hot-button issues.</li>
<li>Conversations among the participants could suggest areas where there is a desire to learn more from peers. It could also signify a place for the client to enter the conversation as a thought leader.</li>
</ul>
<p>Focus groups can provide valuable information in a short amount of time. With the appropriate preparation, participant mix, moderation, and analysis, you can gain valuable understanding of your client’s industry, competitors, audience, and challenges laying the foundation for a powerful brand or campaign.</p>
<p><em> </em><strong>Learn More about B2B Focus Groups</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.b2binternational.com/publications/what-is-the-future-for-b2b-focus-groups/">https://www.b2binternational.com/publications/what-is-the-future-for-b2b-focus-groups/</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.quirks.com/articles/qualities-of-a-master-moderator">https://www.quirks.com/articles/qualities-of-a-master-moderator</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.research-live.com/article/features/playing-hard-to-get/id/5006752">https://www.research-live.com/article/features/playing-hard-to-get/id/5006752</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.circle-research.com/2014/b2b-market-research/">http://www.circle-research.com/2014/b2b-market-research/</a></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FVM named top B2B agency</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/12/2017/fvm-named-top-b2b-agency/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 21:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alex Chapin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=7187</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a list?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who doesn’t love a list? We sure do – especially when we’re named as one of the leading B2B Brand Engagement agencies in the U.S.</p>
<p>The Chief Marketer 200 – the publication’s first comprehensive editorial list of the nation’s top 200 marketing agencies – highlights the best engagement and activation agencies based on several criteria, including client testimonials, case studies, creative concepts and executions, caliber of work, and thought leadership. The program has been created to help marketing professionals navigate to the most suitable agencies for their brands.</p>
<p>Needless to say, we’re delighted to be recognized for the work that our team does in creating and fostering brands, and connecting them with B2B audiences. And of course, none of this would be possible without our incredible clients who inspire us every day.</p>
<p>You can see the <a href="http://www.chiefmarketer.com/cm200/?q=winners" target="_blank" rel="noopener">full list here</a>.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-7188" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Chief-Marketer-200-_600.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="556" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Chief-Marketer-200-_600.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Chief-Marketer-200-_600-220x204.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>B2B, coast to coast</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/05/2017/our-30th-birthday-and-some-exciting-news/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 04:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Cohen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6930</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[FVM is 30 years old!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FVM is 30 years old! Finally, we’re mature, sensible adults. So happy birthday to us. And our big news is that we’re opening a second location in beautiful Portland, OR to expand our B2B brand and marketing offering and better serve west coast businesses.</p>
<p>Portland is a city with thriving tech and B2B industries, top creative talent, and without a doubt one of the best food cart scenes we’ve ever binged on. Looking right at you <a href="https://www.yelp.com/biz/nongs-khao-man-gai-portland">Nong’s</a>. <em>And,</em> Portland is well connected to other major business hubs like Seattle and San Francisco. For us, the expansion is an opportunity to do more of what we’re passionate about: working with savvy clients to build and sustain standout brands. We’ll seek out companies to partner with in complex and competitive B2B industries and help position them to compete, grow, and win, just like we always have.</p>
<p>But apart from spreading out to the west coast, it’s business as usual. We’ll keep on keepin’ on with the same hard working, forward thinking approach that got us this far.</p>
<p>Here’s to the next 30 years! And welcome to the world FVM Portland.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Developing internal culture, while launching an external brand</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/03/08/2017/developing-internal-culture-while-launching-an-external-brand/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 14:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Paul Fleming]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6580</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We’ve enjoyed a great relationship with the Archdiocese of Philadelphia and the Office of Catholic Education for over a decade now — supporting them in the important work they do for the schools, students, and parents across our awesome city and suburbs.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We’ve enjoyed a great relationship with the Archdiocese of Philadelphia and the Office of Catholic Education for over a decade now — supporting them in the important work they do for the schools, students, and parents across our awesome city and suburbs.</p>
<p>The most exciting initiative during this time started in 2015 and continues today; <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/portfolio/aop-schools/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">creating the new Archdiocese of Philadelphia Schools (AOPS) brand</a> and building it out through a new website, outbound, and inbound marketing.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6599" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/AOPS-logo-1-1.png" alt="" width="796" height="265" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/AOPS-logo-1-1.png 796w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/AOPS-logo-1-1-220x73.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/AOPS-logo-1-1-768x256.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 796px) 100vw, 796px" />It’s been a journey of transformation designed to unify our special education, elementary, and secondary schools and advance Catholic education in the area. It began with an internal culture reboot led by <a href="http://www.thepacificinstitute.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Pacific Institute</a> and evolved into an external brand overhaul with FVM. And it’s showing real results for the Arch today.</p>
<p>Here, we share an article on the initiative written by Nick Regina, AOPS Deputy Secretary, Enrollment Management, published in the latest issue of <a href="https://www.ncea.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">National Catholic Educational Association’s (NCEA)</a> magazine, <em>Momentum</em>.</p>
<p><a href="http://read.nxtbook.com/ncea/momentum/2017_winter/index.html#a_lesson_plan_for_developing" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A Lesson Plan for Developing Internal Culture While Launching an External Brand</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You have a branding problem – Now what?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/12/2017/you-have-a-branding-problem-now-what/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Tran]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6466</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Listening for a brand that resonates</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/12/2016/listening-for-a-brand-that-resonates/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 23:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6480</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We have a deceptively simple solution for creating strong B2B brands: listening.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have a deceptively simple solution for creating strong B2B brands: listening. That’s why it’s 90% of our brand discovery process. We listen to uncover every angle, perspective, and nuance so that the brand we create <em>truly</em> resonates with the people who matter most: buyers.</p>
<p>Content audits, digital reviews, and competitive research play a major role in brand discovery, too (and there’ll be more posts to follow on those), but here’s a little insight into how we break down the “question and answer” side and how each tactic informs the branding process.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6491 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_84GOP2OAKR.jpg" alt="Startup Stock Photos" width="1000" height="662" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_84GOP2OAKR.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_84GOP2OAKR-220x146.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_84GOP2OAKR-768x508.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Group Strategy Sessions</span></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>What are they?</em></strong></p>
<p>A chance to hear about the business and brand from the client’s perspective. And it’s not necessarily just about the CEO and CMO. We want to hear from leaders and key employees within as many departments as possible, from sales to finance to customer service. Because a brand isn’t just what the leadership says it is; the brand lives in the people who represent it.</p>
<p><strong><em>What do we listen for? </em></strong></p>
<p>Through conversation and customized brand exercises, we’re looking for a holistic view of where the brand is currently sitting, what challenges and competition it is facing, what the business aims are, and what the brand needs to achieve for the company.<strong><em> </em></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>How does it inform the branding process?</em></strong></p>
<p>A strong internal perspective creates a reliable brand benchmark. From here, we cast a wider net and see how other perspectives measure up.</p>
<p><strong><u>Personal Interviews</u></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>What are they?</em></strong></p>
<p>Interviews usually happen next after a strategy session. They present the opportunity to talk one-on-one — in-person or by phone — with key stakeholders: the client (again), their customers, and their partners. Client (or “internal”) interviews give us a chance to dig deeper into key issues uncovered during the strategy session, while customer (or “external”) interviews focus on our client’s brand, offering, and the ways their products and services are used. But more importantly, the interviews also focus on the customer’s <em>own</em> business: challenges they face on a regular basis, their wants and needs, solutions they love or hate, and their perspectives on the industry.</p>
<p><strong><em>What do we listen for?</em></strong></p>
<p>First, we compare what we heard internally and externally, asking: Is what our client says about themselves the same as what their customers say? Second, we use this more intimate conversation as an opportunity to get past surface-level responses and uncover the true emotions surrounding a business, industry, and brand.</p>
<p><strong><em>How does it inform the branding process?</em></strong></p>
<p>A brand must connect with its audience. A company might believe they know the right way to differentiate their brand, but the attributes they’re calling out may not matter to target audiences. One-on-one interviews help us identify where the current brand succeeds and fails in connecting, as well as where opportunities exist to build a brand strategy that is true to both the client — and to customers’ needs.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6494 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/iStock-483395705-copy.jpg" alt="man having presentation at seminar" width="1000" height="667" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/iStock-483395705-copy.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/iStock-483395705-copy-220x147.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/iStock-483395705-copy-768x512.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p><strong><u>Focus Groups</u></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>What are they?</em></strong></p>
<p>Focus groups are a great <em>qualitative</em> research weapon. We guide a small group representing a sample of our client’s audience through conversations, interactions, and exercises so they can discuss a client’s brand and provide feedback on any initial brand strategy routes or creative concepts.</p>
<p><strong><em>What do we listen for?</em></strong></p>
<p>We’re looking to gain a deep understanding of experiences and perceptions, listening for common trends and points of agreement and disagreement. At its best, a focus group points­­­­­­ us straight towards brand and industry hot spots, showing what issues make people the most passionate, either in a good way, or bad way.</p>
<p><strong><em>How does it inform the branding process?</em></strong></p>
<p>Focus groups add another layer of depth to our findings and help hone strategy. We test strengths and weaknesses in our findings and ideas, identify points where more clarification or research is needed, and confirm pitfalls the brand should avoid. And with the right mix of people in the room, we can feel good knowing we’ve heard from all potential audience groups.</p>
<p><strong><u>Surveys</u></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>What are they?</em></strong></p>
<p>Low-cost, quick, and completely scalable, surveys are our go-to quantitative data approach. Since surveys are anonymous, they present a chance to collect very open and honest input from stakeholders and encourage a more straightforward, rational response.</p>
<p><strong><em>What do we listen for?</em></strong></p>
<p>The standardized format of surveys allow us to ask pointed questions, enabling easy identification of trends across broad groups.</p>
<p><strong><em>How does it inform the branding process?</em></strong></p>
<p>A survey can be useful early in discovery to get a broad view of opinions on multiple key issues. Surveys are also valuable as a final checkpoint so we can take the temperature and confirm we’re heading in the right direction.</p>
<p><strong><u>The truth will emerge</u></strong></p>
<p>Asking questions and listening intently allows us create a brand that aligns a company’s performance and aspirations with the needs and expectations of its customers. It’s that simple.</p>
<p>We take all of the insights we hear — hold them up against findings from a client’s greater marketplace — and distill them into authentic, compelling brand attributes, which can then be interpreted, tested, and tweaked with certainty.</p>
<p>A brand that truly resonates really is just a few conversations away. All we have to do is listen.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Does your B2B brand have personality?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/14/2016/does-your-b2b-brand-have-personality/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 14:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4349</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If your organization magically transformed into a person, what would he or she be like?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If your organization magically transformed into a person, what would he or she be like? Would they be the kind of person you’d like to go out for coffee with? Would they be helpful or interesting? Would you trust the things they said?</p>
<p>It may seem odd to think of your company as a person, especially in the world of B2B. But this exercise is key to discovering your brand personality—a set of human traits closely associated with your brand. It’s a roadmap for adding a vital, relatable dimension that helps engage with customers.</p>
<p>The consumer world is bustling with big brand personalities. There’s energetic, adventurous Red Bull; positive, feminine Dove; cool, intuitive Apple; and the list goes on. These brands convey a distinct personality across every touchpoint, from website and advertising to packaging and sponsorships. Consumers identify with what these brands stand for, and make decisions accordingly.</p>
<p>Granted, B2B marketing is a different beast altogether. A business decision to invest millions in manufacturing equipment is hardly an emotional one. But we B2B marketers can still benefit from the use of brand personality. Because people power all those businesses you’re targeting—and a clear, consistent brand personality will engage them.</p>
<p>Of course, unlike people, brands aren’t born with personalities. They need to be created from scratch to connect with certain audiences and stand apart from the competition. So don’t worry if your organization has zero personality today – you can start crafting an effective one for tomorrow.</p>
<h2><strong>Get a personality</strong></h2>
<p>Put simply, brand personality is the way a brand looks and sounds—it sets the tone of all communications, and shapes audience perception. A typical brand personality is a set of adjectives—E.g. “bold,” “sophisticated” and “approachable”—that, together, create a unique point of view. Here’s how you can start making one for yourself.</p>
<h3><strong>Step 1: Make it relevant</strong></h3>
<p>Before you start the personality journey, consider the following:</p>
<p><strong>• Your audience<br />
</strong>What are they like? What matters to them? Why do they turn to your brand? The more you define your audience, the easier it will be to think of personality traits that appeal to them. For example, if your industry is characterized by down-to-earth people, then a genuine and grounded personality might be received well.</p>
<p><strong>• Your competition<br />
</strong>What do they look like and sound like in the market? How might you set your brand apart? Say you’re a technology provider, and all your competitors use technical language and cold imagery. Your personality could stand out from the crowd by being simple, or playful.</p>
<p><strong>• Your culture<br />
</strong>What are your people like? What are your organization’s guiding principles? If &#8220;above-and-beyond&#8221; customer service is part of your company’s DNA, then a vibrant, helpful personality would bring that to life for the wider world.</p>
<h3><strong>Step 2: Words and themes</strong></h3>
<p>Creative exercises are a great way to come up with brand personality traits. Most importantly, they’re fun and yield a wide variation of ideas. So arm yourselves with flipchart paper, caffeine and snacks, and try these on for size.</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>If my brand were a dog</strong> – Associations are a great way to think differently about your brand. What would your brand be if it was a car? A superhero? A famous actor? A plant? A color?</li>
<li><strong>Meet Mr. Brand </strong>– Back to imagining your brand as a person. What does it look and sound like? How does it dress? Where is it from, and where is it going?</li>
<li><strong>Today vs. tomorrow</strong> – Write down adjectives that describe how your brand is perceived today. Next, write down adjectives that say how you want to be perceived 10 years from now.</li>
</ol>
<p>Once you have all your words on paper, start grouping them together. Similarities and themes will emerge. Rank them according to importance and/or relevancy.</p>
<h3><strong>Step 3: Choose words you can draw</strong></h3>
<p>With your top themes outlined, choose 3-5 adjectives that best encapsulate them. Brand personality traits guide the creation of touchpoints like web copy, ads, graphic design, and business collateral. So it’s important that your personality traits are “words you can draw.” For example, “passionate” comes to mind because your team is so enthusiastic. But how do you design a “passionate” banner ad? Turn to the thesaurus and explore synonyms like “lively” or “vibrant.” These words are more visually descriptive; you can picture a vibrant design or lively web copy.</p>
<h2><strong>You have personality. Now what?</strong></h2>
<p>Creating a brand personality is just the beginning—bringing it to life is an ongoing pursuit. In the short term, it can act as a checklist for your communications. Hold those words next to any email, copy or design to make sure they align. Keep true to it, and your brand personality will naturally shine.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Irrational plays: fantasy football and brand equity</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/14/2016/irrational-plays-fantasy-football-and-brand-equity/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 01:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coleman Rigg]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6311</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The dominant Monday night performances of the Steelers and 49ers brought week 1 of the NFL season to a close.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The dominant Monday night performances of the Steelers and 49ers brought week 1 of the NFL season to a close. It was a great start to the season, and I found it hard to take my eyes off of the TV (and <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/blog/09/04/2014/fantasy-football-head-to-head-yahoo-vs-espn/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fantasy football app</a>) all weekend.</p>
<p>But in the midst of “participating” in my fantasy leagues this past Sunday, my attention turned to the top players who were NOT on the field: Le’Veon Bell, Tom Brady, and Josh Gordon. All three of these players had been ruled out — with multi-game suspensions — far in advance of week 1.</p>
<p>Despite the guaranteed weeks of inactivity, their “% owned” statistics were still rock solid:</p>
<ul>
<li>Le’Veon Bell —100% owned</li>
<li>Tom Brady — 98% owned</li>
<li>Josh Gordon — 91% owned</li>
</ul>
<p>All of these players were early draft picks in my leagues. — but why? They’re out for almost a third of the fantasy season, there’s no certainty of performance when they do return, and you could have selected a guaranteed week 1 starter. Some fantasy experts would tell you that it just doesn’t make statistical sense. The answer: these players have strong brand equity.</p>
<p>Brand equity is a consumer’s perceived value of a product, or in this case, a fantasy football player. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EIKqupYOR48" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Associations with past glory</a> and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FpKduqYmALw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">flashy commercials</a> are enough for people to take a chance, despite these players being handicaps to the team as a whole.</p>
<p>Fantasy team owners believe these inactive players with strong brand equity will generate more points in later weeks of the season, and that this higher, yet delayed point payout is more valuable than drafting a currently active player who will most likely generate fewer fantasy points.</p>
<p>So, whether they knew it or not, most team owners made decisions based on brand equity while drafting this year. Only time will tell if these owners made good decisions, or if they are just suckers for the big name.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting the story straight: communicating a client’s compelling value</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/12/2016/getting-the-story-straight-communicating-a-clients-compelling-value/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 13:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Tran]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6155</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It’s not every day that someone can honestly say their work will advance the field of oncology.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1></h1>
<p>It’s not every day that someone can honestly say their work will advance the field of oncology. Yet in the first few minutes of our project briefing with the clients, it was clear they had built something truly revolutionary.</p>
<p>Proscia had created a digital pathology platform with unprecedented capabilities for professional collaboration. And it was being brought together by a team of brilliant young minds with multidisciplinary expertise.</p>
<p>This underlying story was strong and inspiring.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, it was almost completely absent from the existing Proscia website.</p>
<p>Elements of the Proscia story were scattered and hidden beneath technical details and obscured by layers of navigation. As a result, visitors could not quickly understand the value Proscia offered, and were therefore likely to leave the site with a bias against an otherwise impressive concept.</p>
<h2>The hard part — questioning everything</h2>
<p>For a biomedical startup like Proscia, a website has to convey very specific information in an efficient and digestible manner.</p>
<p>Our work began as it always does, by posing critical strategic questions to our clients and to ourselves about the nature and purpose of the project.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>What is the value of the product or service?</strong></li>
<li><strong>Who are our intended audiences?</strong></li>
<li><strong>What do we want those people to do?</strong></li>
</ul>
<h3>What is the value of the product or service?</h3>
<p>The value, as outlined above, was relatively clear to us, but needed to be brought to the surface for new site visitors.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6250" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Prosica_old_home.png" alt="Prosica_old_home" width="1181" height="1147" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Prosica_old_home.png 1181w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Prosica_old_home-220x214.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Prosica_old_home-768x746.png 768w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Prosica_old_home-1024x995.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 1181px) 100vw, 1181px" /></p>
<p>People who entered Proscia.com without a brief on the technology might be hard-pressed to say what Proscia as an organization did, or what kind of products and services they offered.</p>
<p>There was language about Proscia as a company, but also as a service. There was a platform with several sub-modules, but it wasn’t obvious how they worked together, or in what configurations they could be purchased. We needed to untangle these issues and present an understandable hierarchy of information to every visitor.</p>
<h3>Who are our intended audiences?</h3>
<p>Speaking of visitors, Proscia had several important audiences. On the scientific side, they had to reach clinicians, researchers, and educators simultaneously. But as a startup, Proscia was also looking to generate interest among potential investors.</p>
<p>The scientific group was already served with deep technical material diffused across a few pages (including specialized segmented content). But investors and journalists who weren’t already fluent in this kind of technology would most likely be lost.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6290" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/screencapture-web-archive-org-web-20150704213308-http-proscia-com-explore-1471012964412.png" alt="screencapture-web-archive-org-web-20150704213308-http-proscia-com-explore-1471012964412" width="1000" height="1290" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/screencapture-web-archive-org-web-20150704213308-http-proscia-com-explore-1471012964412.png 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/screencapture-web-archive-org-web-20150704213308-http-proscia-com-explore-1471012964412-171x220.png 171w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/screencapture-web-archive-org-web-20150704213308-http-proscia-com-explore-1471012964412-768x991.png 768w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/screencapture-web-archive-org-web-20150704213308-http-proscia-com-explore-1471012964412-794x1024.png 794w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Details on Proscia’s business model were also hard to find. It wasn’t obvious how much the company intended to charge for its services, or what the general sales process was. We were also concerned this could hinder interest among potential customers who couldn’t gauge if Proscia’s products fit into their budget , or how the products would integrate into their existing workflows.</p>
<h3>What do we want those people to do?</h3>
<p>Relating directly to our concerns about hidden costs, we wanted to know what the ideal action path of a Proscia.com visitor would be.</p>
<p>Immediate spot-conversion subscriptions wouldn’t make sense; this was an advanced suite of pathology services that could potentially be used by hundreds of people within a purchasing organization. Our clients knew the focus should be on familiarizing people with the software and opening channels for in-person dialog.</p>
<p>Proscia.com did have CTAs relating to free demos and contact points, some were redundant (multiple buttons that seemingly did the same thing), and others were relegated to the bottom of unrelated pages. The thinking was right, but it needed polish to drive conversions.<img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6271" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2016-08-11-at-4.49.37-PM.png" alt="Screen Shot 2016-08-11 at 4.49.37 PM" width="1056" height="691" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2016-08-11-at-4.49.37-PM.png 1056w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2016-08-11-at-4.49.37-PM-220x144.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2016-08-11-at-4.49.37-PM-768x503.png 768w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2016-08-11-at-4.49.37-PM-1024x670.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 1056px) 100vw, 1056px" /></p>
<h6>With essentially five CTAs grouped together, there is no clear action path to drive visitors towards conversions</h6>
<h2>The easy part — Reimagining the entire website</h2>
<p>It might seem odd to consider <em>completely making over a site’s architecture</em> the easy part of the creative process.</p>
<p>But as an agency, we pride ourselves in digging deep into our clients’ business. We do the heavy lifting up front — all the due diligence and homework necessary to wrap our heads around not just the project at hand, but every factor affecting the client’s brand.</p>
<p>So at this point in the process, we had very clear understandings of what Proscia.com needed to accomplish, the value it proposed, and the audiences it would serve. What few questions remained about their business model and product hierarchy were cleared up after a few extremely productive client meetings.</p>
<p>We were ready to answer the questions we had previously asked, in the form of a new Proscia website.</p>
<h3>What is the value of the product or service?</h3>
<p>With the new Proscia.com, the very first thing visitors see is a clear explanation of exactly what the company offers and how it benefits medical professionals.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6253 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_home.png" alt="Proscia_new_home" width="800" height="367" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_home.png 800w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_home-220x101.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_home-768x352.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></p>
<p>We don’t expect anyone to be instantly swayed by this introduction, even as compelling as it is. So we give them three avenues to follow.</p>
<p><strong>1. DISCOVER OUR PLATFORM<br />
</strong>This CTA takes visitors to the more technical <em>/platform</em> page, which sells the features of Proscia’s software and outlines exactly what buyers at different levels of organization will get with their subscriptions. From there, they can request a quote.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6263 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_platform-1.png" alt="Proscia_new_platform" width="1139" height="2170" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_platform-1.png 1139w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_platform-1-115x220.png 115w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_platform-1-768x1463.png 768w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_platform-1-537x1024.png 537w" sizes="(max-width: 1139px) 100vw, 1139px" /></p>
<p><strong>2. EXPLORE SAMPLE DATA<br />
</strong>Visitors who are ready can dive into Proscia’s free online trial, seeded with sample data from the National Cancer Institute. There’s no time limit on the demo —users can take as long as they want to fall in love with the software.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6269 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_exploreF-1.png" alt="Proscia_new_exploreF" width="965" height="640" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_exploreF-1.png 965w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_exploreF-1-220x146.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_exploreF-1-768x509.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 965px) 100vw, 965px" /></p>
<p><strong>3. </strong><strong>NAVIGATE THE SITE<br />
</strong>Anyone who isn’t moved to immediately consider features or a demo can still absorb a great deal through organic exploration. Further down the page, users learn about the team behind Proscia and their long-term vision for their technology. Journalists also gain fast access to company history and contact information.</p>
<h3>Who are our intended audiences?</h3>
<p>In both the top-level navigation and directly under the introductory homepage content, we’ve included paths for Proscia’s three primary scientific audiences: researchers, clinicians, and educators.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6262" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_segments.png" alt="Proscia_new_segments" width="800" height="210" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_segments.png 800w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_segments-220x58.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_segments-768x202.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" />Each group gets its own page explaining exactly how the Proscia platform can supplement and enhance daily work. Both tangible examples and futuristic visions are included to convince and inspire readers.</p>
<p>These brief pages then drill down to CTAs that invite users to explore sample data, create their own repositories, or learn more about a Proscia partnership.</p>
<p>We didn’t forget about Proscia’s secondary audiences in investment and the media. But instead of giving these groups their own content, which would feel out of place, we focused on keeping the language accessible throughout the site so these visitors wouldn’t get lost. Language is also peppered with memorable talking points that can be easily underscored by Proscia representatives in sales pitches or one-on-one interviews.</p>
<h3>What do we want those people to do?</h3>
<p>More so than any other objective, Proscia needs visitors to believe in the power of its technology. Once that belief is established, it is not unreasonable to initiate conversation with individual prospects about how Proscia can solve their pathology needs.</p>
<p>So every element of the site — the visuals, the story, and the software itself — need to convey unprecedented technological functionality while overcoming potential concerns about workflow disruption or the company’s credentials as a startup.</p>
<p>By now you understand some of the narrative we solidified for our clients (for the full story, see <a href="http://www.Proscia.com">the Proscia website</a>.) A great deal of the remaining work was getting people to interact with that narrative and explore Proscia.com.</p>
<p>FVM’s designers really pulled through here. You can of course compare the site’s previous and final aesthetics, but even that would not do their work justice.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6260" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_DesignF3.png" alt="Proscia_new_DesignF3" width="800" height="542" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_DesignF3.png 800w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_DesignF3-220x149.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_DesignF3-768x520.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></p>
<h6>About page</h6>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6251" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_design-F2.png" alt="Proscia_new_design F2" width="800" height="354" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_design-F2.png 800w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_design-F2-220x97.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Proscia_new_design-F2-768x340.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></p>
<h6>Demo CTA</h6>
<p>Here is just some of what they accomplished:</p>
<ul>
<li>Cleaner, more digital-friendly Proscia logo</li>
<li>Simpler, more consistent color application</li>
<li>Compelling type with high readability</li>
<li>Strategic photography to draw users in</li>
<li>Icons that intuitively define features</li>
<li>Highly visible yet unobtrusive CTAs</li>
</ul>
<p>Working cohesively with the new website narrative, its design cements Proscia as an inviting, capable, and modern company poised to advance cancer research.</p>
<h2>The moral of the story</h2>
<p>With Proscia, we were honored to have the opportunity tell a moving story about people and technology that truly impressed us. Our clients were individuals who had an expertise in biometrics, data analysis, and network dynamics. For <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/portfolio/proscia/" target="_blank">branding</a> and marketing, they turned to FVM. Our experience telling stories and building websites was of course a major factor in their agency selection.</p>
<p>Every business and website is different, but on a fundamental level, our process is not. It lives and dies by our ability to understand at a strategic level how our clients operate and what role their websites play in achieving specific objectives.</p>
<p>The transformation of Proscia.com is an excellent example of what we can achieve when we get the opportunity to immerse ourselves in our clients’ business. And we like to believe our hard work (and yes, our easy work) will pay off for Proscia, for medical professionals, and for the patients they treat every day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Branding in the bathtub</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/27/2016/branding-in-the-bathtub/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 23:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6160</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When a friend of mine bought a set of Crayola bath toys for my daughter, I was pretty psyched.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When a friend of mine bought a set of Crayola bath toys for my daughter, I was pretty psyched.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-6161 size-full alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/390608_xF8w7xphUyNJwxkZQzPTFDmQR.jpg" alt="390608_xF8w7xphUyNJwxkZQzPTFDmQR" width="700" height="700" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/390608_xF8w7xphUyNJwxkZQzPTFDmQR.jpg 700w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/390608_xF8w7xphUyNJwxkZQzPTFDmQR-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/390608_xF8w7xphUyNJwxkZQzPTFDmQR-220x220.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></p>
<p>Of course we already had a <em>seemingly</em> identical set of bath squirters lying around the house, but these were going to be different… somehow. They were made by Crayola, and I was convinced they were special in some hidden way.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-6162 size-full alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/81y2cUIgxlL._SL1500_-e1465340731286.jpg" alt="81y2cUIgxlL._SL1500_" width="800" height="721" /></p>
<p>My family didn’t understand — they couldn’t figure out why I was scrutinizing the packaging, or why I was studying the toys so closely. “They’re just animals that float and squirt water, Alex,” they told me.</p>
<p>But I knew they were wrong. There had to be something about this product that tied into color — it was Crayola after all.</p>
<p>Sure enough, I found the line I was looking for on the package: <em>Watch for the color-changing stripes. </em>It was the key factor that made these bath squirters different.</p>
<p>It’s surprising how often we get asked the question “what do you mean by brand?” And Crayola provides a perfect example.</p>
<p>Crayola has so closely associated itself with color that <em>you just know</em> any product they produce will be defined by the colors it makes, identifies, or becomes. It seems obvious, but this unwavering focus allows them to extend the brand beyond core products like crayons and markers.</p>
<p>The tie is so strong that, even when moving into the market of rubber bath toys, the user’s colorful expectations persist. How many brands can boast this kind of achievement?</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6163 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/original_390608_juIpmIklOPlwLHBi0c5ffGqOd-1.jpg" alt="original_390608_juIpmIklOPlwLHBi0c5ffGqOd (1)" width="768" height="296" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/original_390608_juIpmIklOPlwLHBi0c5ffGqOd-1.jpg 768w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/original_390608_juIpmIklOPlwLHBi0c5ffGqOd-1-220x85.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" /></p>
<p>A brand is so much more than a logo or even its visual identity. It&#8217;s also the promises, explicit and inherent, that brand has made to users. “This product is all about color” may not be an impressive statement — but the fact that it can go unstated and still be conveyed… that’s impressive.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
