<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Digital &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/digital/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>FVM wins two W3 Awards for web excellence</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/26/2017/fvm-wins-two-w3-awards-for-web-excellence/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 23:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=7037</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Wow!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wow! FVM is beyond proud to have been recognized with two Silver 2017 W3 Awards for our work on behalf of digital pathology startup Proscia and campus safety non-profit Clery Center.</p>
<p>The W3s — which are judged by the Academy of Interactive and Visual Arts (AIVA) and honor creative excellence on the web — awarded <a href="https://proscia.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Proscia.com</a> for copywriting and <a href="https://clerycenter.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CleryCenter.org</a> for non-profit website.</p>
<p>So a big pat on the back to FVM’s storytellers, designers, and developers who work passionately and skillfully to connect B2B brands to their audiences. And a HUGE thank you to our clients whose incredible businesses and trusting partnerships challenge and inspire us every day to come up with truly creative solutions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Easter eggs hidden in classic media</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/03/03/2016/10-easter-eggs-a-history-of-hidden-humor/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 17:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5949</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Yes, we&#8217;re finely tuned coding machines.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yes, we&#8217;re finely tuned coding machines. Some call us nerds. But we have a sense of humor, you know?</p>
<p>&#8220;Knock, knock.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Who&#8217;s there?&#8221;<br />
Very long pause&#8230;<br />
&#8220;Java.&#8221;</p>
<p>See? Hilarious.</p>
<p>Developers like to have a little joke, too. And with the shelves of my local Target spilling with bunnies, baskets, and candy, it got me thinking about Easter eggs. Not the chocolaty-goodness kind; the media kind. Easter eggs are the sweet extra features, messages, gags or artwork hidden in plain sight in any work of media — from websites to movies to <a class="incognito" href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/404" target="_blank">games</a> to software.</p>
<p>While most Easter eggs are good for a quick laugh and a little procrastination, the best eggs are a way for brands to connect with audiences on a different level. Done well, they are an opportunity to move beyond the standard narrative and predictable user experience to create a surprising, playful interaction that connects, shows personality, and builds brand loyalty.</p>
<p>There are plenty of <a href="http://www.eeggs.com/" target="_blank">sites dedicated to documenting ALL the Easter eggs</a>, but, just for fun, here are 10 classic Easter eggs, straight from the memory banks of my brain.</p>
<h3><strong>#1. The Rocky Horror Picture Show (1975)</strong></h3>
<p>The origins of the Easter egg phenomenon are murky. HOWEVER, it is rumored that on the set of the Rocky Horror Show the crew had a literal Easter egg hunt for cast members (because of course they did!). Not all the eggs were found though, and some made it into the final frames. Fans of the show now search for the hidden easter eggs in the movie, and this <em>may</em> be what coined the term &#8220;Easter egg.&#8221;</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-6035" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/o-SONG-OF-THE-LARK-570.jpg" alt="o-SONG-OF-THE-LARK-570" width="725" height="343" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/o-SONG-OF-THE-LARK-570.jpg 570w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/o-SONG-OF-THE-LARK-570-220x104.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 725px) 100vw, 725px" /></p>
<h3><strong>#2. Atari&#8217;s Adventure (1979)</strong></h3>
<p>After the game Adventure was distributed, players alerted Atari of a secret message hidden in the Black Castle Catacombs area. The message simply read &#8220;created by Warren Robinett.&#8221; So what, right? But back in the 70s, Atari didn&#8217;t credit its programmers, so this was Warren&#8217;s self-referential protest to his employers and a way to gain recognition. That recognition turned to fame, as Warren became the first ever known creator of a video gaming Easter egg.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-6056 aligncenter" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/warren-1-1.jpg" alt="warren" width="725" height="499" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/warren-1-1.jpg 959w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/warren-1-1-220x151.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/warren-1-1-768x529.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 725px) 100vw, 725px" /></p>
<h3><strong>#3. Video Whizball (1978)</strong></h3>
<p>This Easter egg actually predates Atari&#8217;s Adventure game, but was only discovered in 2004, making it one of the longest hidden eggs ever. Like Adventure, one of the programmers hid their name in the game. A rather complicated 3-step process creates an indestructible obstacle in the middle of the playing field spelling out &#8220;Reid-Selth.&#8221; Nice one, Reid.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-6032 aligncenter" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/download-3.jpeg" alt="download (3)" width="725" height="548" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/download-3.jpeg 258w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/download-3-220x166.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 725px) 100vw, 725px" /></p>
<h3><strong>#4. Jazzy Jeff and The Fresh Prince</strong></h3>
<p>NBA Jam Tournament Edition. For those who played it in the mid-90s, just mere mention of its name will put a smile on your face. The roster of real-life players was thrilling, but secret codes could take things to a whole new level with the introduction of <a href="http://www.gamefaqs.com/snes/588512-nba-jam-tournament-edition/cheats" target="_blank">40 extra characters</a> including Philly&#8217;s own Jazzy Jeff, Will Smith and Randall Cunningham. Bill Clinton dribbling past Hilary, and Prince Charles slam-dunking. Take me back!</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-6026" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/37051d2e10ca86b_ywxXZtT.jpg" alt="37051d2e10ca86b_ywxXZtT" width="725" height="410" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/37051d2e10ca86b_ywxXZtT.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/37051d2e10ca86b_ywxXZtT-220x124.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 725px) 100vw, 725px" /></p>
<h3><strong>#5. A113</strong></h3>
<p>One of the longest running Easter eggs was started by California Institute of the Arts alumni. A113 refers to the classroom many pioneering graphic design and character animation students used; many of whom went on to have massive, influential careers in TV and movies. You can find the characters &#8220;A113&#8221; EVERYWHERE from The Simpsons to The Hunger Games. If you have 11 minutes to spare, here&#8217;s every single egg from Chief Creative Officer of Pixar, John Lasseter, including a bunch of references to his old study room.</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ejgaEbKT1sA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<h3><strong>#6. Strongbad Emails</strong></h3>
<p>Back in the early 2000&#8217;s homestarunner.com gave fans an opportunity to look for new Easter eggs each week. Strongbad Emails (AKA sbemails) featured several eggs at the end of each of their weekly cartoons It also popularized the <a class="incognito" href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/404" target="_blank">mouse-over</a> Easter egg where the mouse curser changed when it was hovering over an Easter egg.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-6057" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/sbmonitor3.jpg" alt="sbmonitor3" width="725" height="544" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/sbmonitor3.jpg 1024w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/sbmonitor3-220x165.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/sbmonitor3-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 725px) 100vw, 725px" /></p>
<h3><strong>#7. All of Google</strong></h3>
<p>Overall, Easter eggs are playful. So it&#8217;s no surprise that a company like Google is responsible for hundreds of elaborate eggs across dozens of different products. And by elaborate, I mean they build entire, fully functioning video games. For example, if you go to Google image search and type <a href="http://images.lmgtfy.com/?q=atari+breakout" target="_blank">&#8220;atari breakout&#8221;</a> it turns the search result into the <a class="incognito" href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/404" target="_blank">classic arcade game</a>.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-6023" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2016-02-24-at-3.19.43-PM.png" alt="Screen Shot 2016-02-24 at 3.19.43 PM" width="725" height="288" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2016-02-24-at-3.19.43-PM.png 800w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2016-02-24-at-3.19.43-PM-220x87.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2016-02-24-at-3.19.43-PM-768x305.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 725px) 100vw, 725px" /></p>
<h3><strong>#8. PacMan</strong></h3>
<p>While not technically an Easter egg, many artists and programmers have secretly slipped 1980s mega munching arcade hero PacMan into their work. Google&#8217;s done it at least twice, once on PacMan&#8217;s 30th birthday and another time in Google Maps. References to the game are also found in the popular Elder&#8217;s Scrolls game Skyrim, and also had a brief cameo in the sci-fi classic Tron.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-6055" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/tron-2.jpg" alt="tron" width="725" height="288" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/tron-2.jpg 498w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/tron-2-220x87.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 725px) 100vw, 725px" /></p>
<h3><strong>#9. The Easter Egg You Never Wanted to Find</strong></h3>
<p>If you were surfing the Internet circa 2008 and found something that was too good to be true, chances are you were about to be &#8220;Rick-Rolled.&#8221; <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=STl3eifhkm4" target="_blank">No one was safe</a>. Clicking on a link to what you thought was the official trailer for a Legend of Zelda movie brought you red-headed Rick and his 1987 wonder hit, leaving you wishing it had just been a broken link instead. Haha, get it? Zelda. A <a class="incognito" href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/404" target="_blank">broken Link</a>. HA!</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-6024" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Rick-Astley.png" alt="Rick-Astley" width="725" height="408" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Rick-Astley.png 620w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Rick-Astley-220x124.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 725px) 100vw, 725px" /></p>
<h3><strong> <a class="incognito" href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/404">#10</a>&#8230;</strong></h3>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scream SEO without losing your voice</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/28/2016/scream-seo-without-losing-your-voice/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 16:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5775</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[SEO — those three magic letters have for some time seemed like the catchall solution to all your marketing problems.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SEO — those three magic letters have for some time seemed like the catchall solution to all your marketing problems. Throw extra budget its way, toss in some more keywords, and <em>presto: </em>forms are filled in, emails flood inboxes, phones ring off the hook, and you&#8217;re swimming in new customers! It’s the one-size-fits all solution. Marketing magic.</p>
<p>Obviously, that perception is wrong. And yet this oversimplified and exaggerated mindset is still a commonly held assumption in marketing departments across America. We&#8217;ve seen many companies focus so strongly on SEO (trying to keep up with every Panda, Penguin, Hummingbird, or Pirate that Google releases into the wild) that their websites are a mess.</p>
<p>What’s worse, conflict between site-optimized copy, positioning, and key messaging is actually damaging their brands.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-5777" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/giphy.gif" alt="giphy" width="320" height="240" /></p>
<p>But it doesn’t have to be like this — SEO and brand can live in harmony. Here, we outline some areas to focus your SEO efforts without weakening your brand and losing your voice.</p>
<h3><strong>Before You Get Started</strong></h3>
<p>Let’s just be clear: SEO is about your website traffic and ranking. On the other hand, brand is everything — social, advertising, content, sales, customer service, events, <em>and</em> website — it&#8217;s just so much bigger. SEO is a marketing tactic, and like all tactics, it’s worth very little without a clear, consistent and authentic brand.</p>
<p>So, in order for you to nail your SEO strategy, you need a full understanding of your brand&#8217;s position, purpose, and values. With those elements in your back pocket, the right keywords will come.</p>
<h3><strong>Basic Research</strong></h3>
<p>If you aren’t already doing the basic due-diligence for SEO, start now. Make sure you know what your brand keywords are and any alternative phrasing your potential customer base would use. This research can be an intensive process, but it’s invaluable. It will benefit traffic and ranking in the long run, and it may also lead you to discover valuable search phases that could influence ideas for messaging moving forward. Keep that list handy and check it often.</p>
<p>And about that content. Make sure that with every new blog post, whitepaper, press release, or service offering that makes it onto your website has a title tag, meta tags, image alt attributes, and H tags. If you don’t know what those are, read up <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/tags/tag_title.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>, <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/tags/tag_meta.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>, <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/tags/att_img_alt.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>, and <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/tags/tag_hn.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<h3><strong>The New Kids on the Block</strong></h3>
<p>Search engines like Google have one simple goal (well, maybe a few <a href="http://mashable.com/2012/03/01/google-privacy-data-policy/#OgkMWsLSHZqj" target="_blank" rel="noopener">more</a>, but we’re not going into that here) and that is to provide <em>what</em> the user is looking for <em>when</em> they ask for it. It’s as simple as that.</p>
<p>In SEO’s infancy, that meant keyword stuffing a business-to-business marketing website with brand-positioning digital services online advertising copy that focuses on the digital development and brand marketing services that a brand manager for a B2B and B2C business might be looking for on a search engine optimization search platform.</p>
<p>You see what I did there?</p>
<p>Today, a lot of that keyword-stuffing-for-the-sake-of-keyword-stuffing is identified and either demoted to the dregs of search results, or cast aside and evaluated for the merits of newer search ranking criteria:</p>
<p><em><strong>Responsive design</strong></em><br />
Google made waves <a href="https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/6196932?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener">last year</a> when they announced that websites that weren’t mobile friendly might take a hit in their search rankings. This of course only reflected searches made on mobile devices, but since <a href="http://searchengineland.com/its-official-google-says-more-searches-now-on-mobile-than-on-desktop-220369" target="_blank" rel="noopener">more Google searches take place on mobile devices than on computers</a>, it’s a pretty big deal.</p>
<p>When it comes time to create a shiny new website, make sure it’s designed responsively. And be responsible about image file size, JavaScript load time, and user interface design. That means you shouldn’t try and serve up a 2mb marquee image, or load a script on every page if it’s only used once, or have a form’s submit and cancel buttons be so small a thumb can’t find them.</p>
<p>To find out where you rank in terms of mobile-friendly usability, check out <a href="https://www.google.com/webmasters/tools/mobile-friendly/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google’s helpful online tool</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>Video transcription<br />
</strong></em>Google loves websites that contain rich media. They also love it when you make it easier to determine the relevancy of a video against the keywords your website targets. Make sure you have a transcript of a video’s content linked with a subtitles or captions tag to enhance your ranking.</p>
<p><em><strong>Structured data markup</strong></em><br />
Arguably the most important element of all, Structured Data is becoming more and more important as Google and other search engines place an increasing amount of focus on semantic search.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-5887 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Google-data.jpg" alt="Google data" width="800" height="828" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Google-data.jpg 800w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Google-data-213x220.jpg 213w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Google-data-768x795.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></p>
<p>By identifying key components of your business — your company name, telephone, address, business hours — you’re helping Google to identify its DNA. The search engine then matches that up with the content on your website to provide more accurate results for all those folks searching for, say, a business-to-business marketing agency with brand-positioning digital services.</p>
<p>Google’s <a href="https://www.google.com/webmasters/markup-helper/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Structured Data Markup Helper</a> and <a href="http://schema.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Schema.org</a> are great places to start. You can also feel free to have a <a href="mailto:*protected email*">conversation with us</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>The Social Network<br />
</strong></em>You’ve no doubt heard it before, but the impact of social media is real — even in B2B. More than just a place where your neighbor posts status updates before, during, and after his amazing crock-pot chicken dinner, social platforms are where we explore, discover, and connect with others&#8230; including in the professional world.If you’ve uploaded a blog post recently and never bothered to let your Twitter followers know, please go do that right now. I’ll wait.</p>
<p>Every time you have valuable insight to customers (and potential customers) make sure you’re doing your part to spread the word. Make sure you’re paying attention to other experts in your field and follow their insight as well.</p>
<p>That way, when you reference your latest bit of wisdom, the community gets an opportunity to digest what you have to offer and share it with their friends. And then maybe they can rave about an amazing crock-pot chicken recipe they just found.</p>
<h2><strong>Marketing magic</strong></h2>
<p>SEO is a vital part of any digital marketing strategy; it can add huge value, so it’s important you follow the steps discussed above. But it is a tactic, and it should be treated as one. In the time of the educated, informed, and engaged B2B buyer who is doing research and forming opinions, being in the first position on the first page of Google is nowhere near a clincher. You might score a few clicks because you’re highly visible, but then what? If nobody likes what they see, your search ranking is a wasted opportunity.</p>
<p>If the leads aren’t coming in as you’d like and your conversions are down, it&#8217;s probably not due to SEO woes. It’s more likely that your messaging is muddled, you’re not putting the right kind of content in the right place at the right time, or you’re not communicating the most relevant information to prospects.</p>
<p>The best way to support your SEO efforts is to establish a strong and consistent brand. The clearer your position and messaging becomes, the more familiar and more consistent those search queries will be. That’s how branding and marketing can really solve your SEO problem.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Farm and the laws of Searchism</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/07/08/2015/google-farm-and-the-laws-of-searchism/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 14:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEO]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5037</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[All webpages are equal All webpages are equal, but some webpages are more equal than others &#160; Those lines are a play on Animal Farm, George Orwell’s dystopian satire of Stalin’s dictatorship. On August 17th, it will be 70 years since the book was first published, and I was planning on waiting until that anniversary to post [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><del>All webpages are equal</del></p>
<p>All webpages are equal, but some webpages are more equal than others</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5211" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Google-Farm_Searchism-e1428504081180.jpg" alt="Google-Farm_Searchism-e1428504081180" width="600" height="474" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Google-Farm_Searchism-e1428504081180.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Google-Farm_Searchism-e1428504081180-220x174.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Those lines are a play on <em><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Animal_Farm" target="_blank">Animal Farm</a></em>, George Orwell’s dystopian satire of Stalin’s dictatorship. On August 17th, it will be 70 years since the book was first published, and I was planning on waiting until that anniversary to post this blog, but I&#8217;m impatient.</p>
<p>If you haven’t read it, the book is about a farm of talking animals led by the pigs, who make laws and paint them on the wall for all to see. As things start to change on the farm, so do the laws. Stay with me here.</p>
<p>If the Internet is our farm, then Google are the pigs making and changing the rules. Sure, other search engines exist, but Google is the only one that matters. (Just Ask Jeeves.) Don’t worry, this blog isn’t about Google being fascist pigs—far from it. It’s about Searchism, my term for a new ideology about all things search in this Google Farm we live in. Searchism is about accepting a truth, keeping your eyes open, and adapting techniques with changing rules. We Searchists embrace Google’s ever-evolving algorithms in the pursuit of becoming optimal search engine marketers.</p>
<p>While many of Google’s laws are hidden in algorithms, some are written on the wall for all to see. Here are five of the latest.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>Law 1: All webpages are equal, but some are more equal than others</strong></h2>
<p>(Or they bid a helluva lot more than others, at least.)<strong> </strong></p>
<p>It’s a hard truth to face but it’s one you can’t ignore: you’re competing and you will be outbid by bigger budgets. There are approximately <a href="http://www.internetlivestats.com/one-second/#google-band" target="_blank">45,000 Google searches every second and counting</a> and getting yourself on the first page is going to cost some dough. Start with the first page. Get there, and then worry about the top result.</p>
<p>Bidding is an easy place to start. If you’re spread thin, then you need to be crafty. If you can’t bid rich, bid smart. Pick a small set of the most searched for keywords and put your chips there. Forget about all the other variations and outliers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>Law 2: All users want what they want</strong></h2>
<p>What are the most searched keywords? Google Analytics tools can help you find these metrics. You have to put your ego aside and learn how users think they should be searching for you, not what you think they should be typing in. And the next day, start all over again. Adjust your top keywords and bids on them regularly. The fluctuation will blow you away.</p>
<p>That said, your page copy and SEO methods need to stay in sync with your bids or you’re nothing but a liar. Or so it will seem when users see your high-page search result, click, and see that the text and phrasing they used in their search is nowhere on your page. That brings us to Law 3 of Searchism.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>Law 3: Treat every user like a friend, no matter their search query</strong></h2>
<p>All that research you’re doing on all those top-rated, hot, popular, buzzy words, and phrases is not just so you know where to bid, it’s also so you know how to optimize your own content. Keyword-rich content is essential to maximizing the efficacy of all that smart PPC bidding you’re doing.</p>
<p>And so you snag a user. They’re on your page and now they’re a friend! So, treat them like one and give them what they came for. This does not have to mean a complete warping of your messaging. It simply means some time spend adjusting copy and sub-heads, primarily.</p>
<p>Consider how Alan Rabinowitz, CEO of SEO Image puts it: “The idea is to identify the primary keyword(s) that you will be targeting for the page or website and then support those keywords with semantically and topically related keywords and phrases.”</p>
<p>Your treasured taglines, the headlines that are the roots of your brilliant campaigns do not have to change. You just need to make sure that you’re speaking the language that your customers and prospects are, because that’s how they’re searching. Then reflect that language somewhere in your copy in an appropriate frequency.</p>
<p>“WAIT!” I hear you say. “These laws are just like any set of commandments!”</p>
<p>Well, you can’t just pick and choose. Law 2 is important, but so often digital marketers obsess over this rule and cannibalize themselves and their companies when they ignore Law 3.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>Law 4: No Searchist shall kill a lead</strong></h2>
<p>Why would anyone want to kill a lead? The fact of the matter is these deaths often take place without intent. There are many ways modern Searchists can kill a lead. However, a prominent cause is death by exposure to SEO-laced copy. What was once targeted, strategic, naturally-flowing, user-friendly, relevant, focused, and appropriate copy can often be poisoned by short-sighted marketing professionals who focus solely on the Law 2 portion of SEO and nothing else.</p>
<p>The idea is to write your best copy that represents you, your product or service, and develops your campaigns. Then attempt to incorporate and swap-in the latest industry speak and changing buzz into your original messaging. Do not contaminate your messaging with SEO, SEO, and more SEO.</p>
<p>Users are not like they once were. They know copy that was web-mastered to ensnare a searcher. Even if they don’t recognize the tainted copy, their experience is going to be less than ideal, and it’s likely the lead will be killed.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>Law 5: No anti-Social behavior</strong></h2>
<p>Social media is a noisy beast and, in keeping with form, Google hears everything. Yes, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=udqtSM-6QbQ" target="_blank">the search gods have spoken</a> to deny any direct relationship between social actions and higher ranking content, but they have also admitted to attempting to factor social signals into their algorithms, and they may do so again. While Google many not directly count all of your Likes and Tweets, a well executed social media strategy has all kinds of indirect benefits on SEO, such as higher rankings for brand profiles and more targeted traffic with personalized search results.</p>
<p>A few key tactics are proving to be integral methods in improving your rankings. And yes, this may be simple stuff and insulting to some, but Searchists should never forget the basics (and should always leave their pride at the barn door). Firstly, the goals: increase followers, friends, connections and circles; increase the number of sites linking to your site (and remember to return the favor!); and increase the high-authority mentions or links to your content or sites. Next, the tactics: create branded social pages across various platforms; produce content worth sharing; make sharing easy with easy UX, social buttons, mobile responsiveness and easy linkage; and have a human tone of voice, not a robotic one.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>Back on the Farm</strong></h2>
<p>OK, this may not be “a complete system of thought.” But, to quote journalist Carole Cadwalladr: “The future, in ways we can’t even begin to imagine, will be Google’s.” So, it’s something to familiarize yourself with. Keep watching, keep listening, keep adjusting, and keep rewriting your laws until you’re an expert in Searchism. And most importantly, keep your eyes on the barn wall. Unlike the pigs in Animal Farm, Google creates and changes these laws, both those on the wall and those hidden, for the overall good of Searchism, not for power. The battle for power has long been over.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Words by Andy Sproule<br />
Illustration by Mark Parker</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Internet of Things</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/02/09/2015/the-internet-of-things/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 17:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4909</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Internet of Things.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Internet of Things. The buzzword that has replaced Big Data. Now widely known, but often misunderstood, the IoT is the idea that our lives are becoming exponentially more interconnected. It promises to transform daily life, serving as the impetus for new technological innovation, and ushering older devices into the digital age. Previously “dumb” technology like thermostats and refrigerators are now becoming enlightened, connecting even the most mundane aspects of our lives to the vast personal data network already occupied by devices like mobile phones, tablets, and wearable tech. Here’s a bit more info in a handy video summary from Intel:</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q3ur8wzzhBU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>In a recent study conducted by IDC, the <a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/gilpress/2014/08/22/internet-of-things-by-the-numbers-market-estimates-and-forecasts/" target="_blank">market size for IoT solutions alone could reach $7.1 trillion dollars by 2020</a>, compared to a 2013 estimate of $1.9 trillion. Some companies are forecasting even higher numbers (Cisco says $14.4 trillion) for the IoT’s total impact on economic growth.</p>
<p>Those staggering projections are based on disruption in just about every industry one could imagine. Many companies are already scrambling to get ahead of the curve and capitalize on smarter data grids of customer information and business automation. <a href="http://www.gxsblogs.com/morleym/2013/10/how-the-internet-of-things-will-impact-b2b-and-global-supply-chains.html" target="_blank">Major corporations like GE</a> have set up entire divisions dedicated solely to figuring out how best to position themselves as leaders in this emerging market.</p>
<h2><strong>Internet of insight</strong></h2>
<p>Where the IoT promises to streamline every aspect of life for end users, the result for advertisers is a bumper crop of useable data that yields a wealth of information.</p>
<p>As more aspects of consumers’ lives become quantifiable, the less volatile and erratic these business processes become, presenting marketers with the mouthwatering prospect of knowing exactly where to focus their dollars, possibly on a granular level.</p>
<p>For B2Bs dealing with a considered purchase and long sales cycles, one chief benefit the IoT promises is better insight into customer behavior during various touch points in the lead-nurturing process. Instead of sending a cookie cutter follow-up email to a prospective buyer, advertisers will now have a wider menu of richer event-based options to reach the prospect’s pipeline. With more knowledge and choice, comes the opportunity to deliver more meaningful, targeted messaging. The IoT will not only impact high-level brand strategy, but how companies approach media planning as well.</p>
<p>Just look at the campaign Netflix launched in France, where <a href="http://www.digitalbuzzblog.com/netflix-real-time-reactive-gif-campaign/" target="_blank">digital billboards played animated GIFs reacting to local weather</a> and other topical events. Imagine the remarketing value this could represent to a company like FedEx Small Business or Stamps.com when one these interactive ads is located just a few steps away from the entrance to the local post office.</p>
<h2><strong>Better connected</strong></h2>
<p>A major challenge, especially for B2B companies looking to capitalize on this rising trend, is that there are very few unifying platforms that link all of these internet-connected devices together. What good would it be for a manufacturer to provide its suppliers with real-time order management technology if each end user has a different, incompatible sales platform?</p>
<p>The usual suspects, such as the aforementioned Cisco and GE, as well as IBM, are all building products to bring these networks together. How quickly the IoT becomes a practical business investment will largely be determined by the ability of these massive networks to integrate products from small software and hardware manufacturers.</p>
<h2><strong>Walking a fine line</strong></h2>
<p>The IoT promises to bring 20<sup>th</sup> century things into the 21<sup>st</sup> century; linking them to an impossibly large grid of interconnected data and making daily chores more efficient.</p>
<p>Such a bevy of  data and user demographics will have the advertising world champing at the bit. The challenge will be that—on the inevitable march towards progress and innovation—marketers must find new and creative ways to deliver personalized messaging <a href="http://fedscoop.com/the-internet-of-things-convenient-and-creepy/" target="_blank">without being so invasive</a> that the user opts out completely. The mantra is: “Be personal, not creepy. Remember <em>Minority Report</em>.&#8221;</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7bXJ_obaiYQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting sentimental with interactive video</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/11/2015/spark-of-digital-getting-sentimental-with-interactive-video/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 15:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4435</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Attention spans are decreasing at an alarming rate.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://blogs.sap.com/innovation/sales-marketing/thanks-social-media-average-attention-span-now-shorter-goldfish-01251966" target="_blank">Attention spans are decreasing at an alarming rate</a>. Not only does your content need to pique interest and attract visitors; it has to keep them hooked, too. With Web 2.0 came the advent of amazing new interactive tools for marketers to reach audiences, and videos are no exception. It’s not enough to be the visually stimulating alternative to boring old text anymore, video has to promise a payoff and offer a reason to stay.</p>
<p>Enter the folks at <em><a href="http://www.raptmedia.com/" target="_blank">Rapt Media</a></em>, who have created something awesome. Their platform allows users to easily create interactive videos with a smart and simple interface. And it even has SEO capabilities baked right in. Check out how they were able to help <em>Deloitte</em> gamify their recruiting process with a slickly designed video that plays out like one of those <em>Choose Your Own Adventure</em> books from when you were a kid.</p>
<p><iframe src="http://cdn1.raptmedia.com/projects/j2Nu6adZ/embed?autoplay=false&amp;controls=overlay#http://www.raptmedia.com/project/deloitte" width="100%" height="300" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Iframes are required to view this content.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Interactive videos aren’t necessarily new; clickable links and embedded popups are common across the web, especially on sites like <em>YouTube</em> and <em>Vimeo</em>. What <em>Rapt</em> has done is produce interactive videos that demand viewer attention. That’s why they can tout longer user engagement and higher CTRs.</p>
<p>So how does it all work? <em>Rapt’s</em> platform is simple yet elegant in its design.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-4437 alignright" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Untitled21.png" alt="Untitled2" width="900" height="532" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled21.png 900w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled21-220x130.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></p>
<p>An interactive layer is placed over the main video with clickable hotspots linking to other clips at strategic points. This allows marketers to create videos with multiple outcomes, depending on a viewer’s preference. The result is almost like a built-in A/B test (or A/B/C/D…) showing which path each user took.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.prdaily.com/Main/Articles/The_role_of_sentiment_in_social_data_analysis__16072.aspx" target="_blank">Brand sentiment</a> has become an increasingly important aspect of digital marketing. The ability to understand an audience at a granular level is invaluable to marketers. So building rich, interactive videos that hold viewer attention and demand genuine engagement is no small thing, and worth our attention.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The &#8220;Forgotten Few&#8221;: 3 key elements to video marketing ROI</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/30/2014/the-forgotten-few-3-key-elements-to-video-marketing-roi/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 19:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4391</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There has always been a lot of “good stuff” out there.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There has always been a lot of “good stuff” out there. When I first joined the video production scene a few years ago, I looked at what others were doing and was attracted to the beautifully designed videos with high-end production, all brought to life with seemingly-expensive animation, blends of talking-head and technical graphics, expert footage capture, catchy music, perfectly casted talent and voiceovers. Good design and great stories are wonderful, but experience has taught me that without implementing some simple key elements, your videos will not deliver the ROI you (or your client) are looking for.</p>
<p>These elements can be <em>proven</em> to drive ROI and are what performance analytics are based on. I call them the “Forgotten Few,” and it’s surprising how many marketing videos are without them.</p>
<p>My “Forgotten Few” are:</p>
<ol>
<li>Call-to-Action</li>
<li>SEO</li>
<li>Localization/translation</li>
</ol>
<h3><strong>1. Call-to-Action</strong></h3>
<p>“That’s a wrap and…fade to logo and now fade to black.”</p>
<p>No! That’s not a wrap. Do NOT just fade to logo to black. You should always have a call to action. This is a traffic and lead-generating tactic that is so often forgotten. This guy just made it through your video, he’s interested, and unfortunately for him, he didn’t find the video on your site, but rather on YouTube. You faded to black and now he’s slipping from your grasp and into the hands of the competition.</p>
<p>CTA possibilities don’t stop there. Pop-ups or references can be included throughout the video. This tactic is especially important if you’re producing a product demo or other type of content for a low-funnel prospect. They’re probably going to be trigger-happy, clicking through various content, so offer them every opportunity to delve deeper through a clear CTA as soon as possible.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a little example:</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nR3nCJIIkjo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Never bank on them making it all the way through the video, because it’s unlikely. And a strong strategy would include at least three ways for the buyer to reach you: visit the homepage, contact a rep, tweet us, for example.</p>
<h3><strong>2. SEO</strong></h3>
<p>SEO is a monster in today’s marketing world. There’s a lot to it, but with video, here’s one simple thing you can do to help your prospect find the content. Embed the video’s transcript in the meta-data OR launch a blog post to support the video (it’s important not to do both, because Google doesn’t like that!). Suddenly, your video is searchable, and maybe it’s a blog that’s worth not only viewing, but also sharing.</p>
<h3><strong>3. Localization</strong></h3>
<p>This final element speaks primarily to global marketers, but is an excellent way for anyone to grow exposure of video content in regions that your analytics tell you have potential. Translate and provide sub-text for your video as you market in international theaters. But also take the time to apply localized voiceovers and edit some graphics so they are region-specific. You don’t need to produce 12 different videos for 12 different cultures, but taking those extra steps to tailor a current video for a specific region will make an impact.</p>
<h2><strong>ROI</strong></h2>
<p>It’s one thing to produce “good stuff,” but it’s another to create a true asset, equal in beauty and effectiveness. Yes, there are many variables in video marketing: types, styles, formats, budgets, audiences and more. But the “Forgotten Few” should be considered in all cases to keep the conversation flowing, carry the message further, improve ROI, and give the video a reason for being.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cross-browser testing: how to live with Internet Explorer</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/24/2014/cross-browser-testing/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 15:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4251</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Ask a group of web designers what they think of Internet Explorer and you&#8217;ll get a fair share of groans.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ask a group of web designers what they think of Internet Explorer and you&#8217;ll get a fair share of groans. Most will grumble about CSS hacks and quasi-transparency support, and the rest will make hilarious jokes like &#8220;Internet Explorer is only good for downloading other browsers.&#8221;</p>
<p>What&#8217;s really at the heart of all this hostility—to a once industry-leading product—is simply the aggravation of writing code that isn&#8217;t always accepted by all browsers (and the need to have to troubleshoot in so many different potential environments).</p>
<p>While there are <a href="http://www.w3.org/standards/webdesign/htmlcss" target="_blank">HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Mobile</a> coding standards, a browser that doesn&#8217;t support the new &#8220;whiz bang&#8221; techniques becomes a headache for designers (think transparency and rounded corners). On top of that, the user experience that morphs from a desktop hit to a mobile hit can dramatically alter the performance of a website (much like drop down menus and hover effects on touch screen devices).</p>
<h3>The Players</h3>
<p>We&#8217;ve gone from a world in which everyone used Netscape to steal Metallica MP3s, to one in which a user&#8217;s browser may change as they transition from their desk to their car to their couch. Even if you could control what browsers people use, it&#8217;s nearly impossible to control what versions they have (or have not) updated to. In fact, it has become such a problem that a few big names have launched <a href="https://www.modern.ie/en-us/ie6countdown" target="_blank">campaigns to stop using their own products</a>. There&#8217;s just no guarantee which browser your visitors will be viewing your content in, so you need to optimize for them all.</p>
<p>At ThinkFVM.com, we see that our visitors use the usual suspects:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-4256 size-full alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM.png" alt="FVM Browsers by Type" width="822" height="532" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM.png 822w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM-220x142.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 822px) 100vw, 822px" /></a></p>
<p>A full 15% of our visitors are on IE, which immediately raises flags. Will all of them be able to handle our Parallax? Do we have border radius styles that are going to look good when they&#8217;re downgraded? How many of these visitors are using versions of IE that can&#8217;t handle background sizing?</p>
<p>So, since Internet Explorer is the biggest culprit in behind-the-times-itis, we usually keep an eye on visitors&#8217; IE browsers:</p>
<div id="attachment_4257" style="max-width: 825px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-4257 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM.png" alt="FVM Browsers by IE Version" width="815" height="522" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM.png 815w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM-220x140.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 815px) 100vw, 815px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text"><em>Seriously? There are still IE6 users out there?</em></p></div>
<p>Right out of the gate we know that almost 8% of our visitors have IE8 or earlier. Those are the biggest culprits we&#8217;re seeing today, and to them, our website may not look as spectacular as we intended it to. We&#8217;re used to this and we incorporate that thinking into our concepts, but we don&#8217;t always want to sacrifice design for a troubled few. So we build what we want to and test accordingly. However, short of owning a 1980s-esque room full of computers and outdated operating software, what&#8217;s a coder to do?</p>
<p>Well, there are tools to help us out.</p>
<h3>The Solution</h3>
<p>Our personal favorite browser testing website is <a href="http://www.crossbrowsertesting.com" target="_blank">CrossBrowserTesting.com</a>. We joined this subscription-based service when it first launched, at a time when coders were lost for quality tools, and it has grown with the market ever since. Although no matter which browser testing software you use—<a href="http://www.browserstack.com/" target="_blank">BrowserStack</a>, <a href="https://saucelabs.com/" target="_blank">SauceLabs</a>, <a href="http://browsershots.org/" target="_blank">BrowserShots</a>, <a href="http://www.ranorex.com/blog/cross-browser-test-automation" target="_blank">Ranorex</a>, and <a href="http://smartbear.com/products/qa-tools/automated-testing-tools/" target="_blank">SmartBear</a> all have their own products—the tools are straightforward: plug in a URL and see how pages are rendered on the screen, in various browsers, and in multiple operating systems.</p>
<p>CrossBrowserTesting.com offers two methods for its troubleshooting: screenshots and live tests. We typically run all new websites and landing pages through the screenshots application, running IE7-IE11, a current and legacy version of Firefox, Chrome, Opera, and even iOS and Android mobile browsers. With a few clicks, we can test each layout design and check back later to compile a punch list of CSS miscreants.</p>
<p>If there are any active elements on the page—say scrolling marquees, dynamic drop down lists, or unique hover states—we can click from the screenshot result to view a live test of the website. This also helps when troubleshooting a CSS fix to make sure it was effective.</p>
<h3>Use Case In Action</h3>
<p>When we built our website, we took advantage of full-bleed images, which came at a cost to lesser capable browsers. We knew that IE8 and 7 did not support the background-width property, so we started right out with a failsafe image placement. Still, our website looked like this:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1.png" class="swipebox"><img class="alignleft wp-image-4279 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1.png" alt="Screen Shot 2014-09-24 at 1.46.33 PM" width="973" height="710" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1.png 973w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1-220x160.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 973px) 100vw, 973px" /></a></p>
<p>IE 9, 10, and 11 look great, as does IE7. IE8 however, doesn&#8217;t scale the background image properly, and the failsafe image that IE7 displays isn&#8217;t rendering in IE8 like it should. <em>Sorry to our one user who visits in IE6, but we don&#8217;t bother testing for that browser anymore. You need to upgrade!</em></p>
<p>Yeesh. Luckily we ran into this problem before and implemented an easy <a href="https://github.com/louisremi/background-size-polyfill" target="_blank">hack</a>.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1.png" class="swipebox"><img class="alignleft wp-image-4281 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1.png" alt="Screen Shot 2014-09-24 at 2.17.10 PM" width="968" height="679" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1.png 968w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1-220x154.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 968px) 100vw, 968px" /></a></p>
<p>Now, our pages look as uniform as they can be. Sure, the transparent black behind our bios is nicer than the solid grey, but that&#8217;s life. There&#8217;s probably a transparency hack out there somewhere, but the design didn&#8217;t warrant the extra scripting for the expected payout. The point is that no matter what browser a visitor uses to view your website, they can still view the website. And, with the cross-browser testing tools that we have at our disposal, we didn&#8217;t spend a lot of time guaranteeing a uniform user experience.</p>
<p>After all, we have a lot of <a href="https://www.facebook.com/video.php?v=530140273781498" target="_blank">other stuff going on</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Some humbling stats about banner ads</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/07/2014/some-humbling-stats-about-banner-ads/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4120</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I can count on one hand the number of times I’ve clicked on banner ads in the past year.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I can count on one hand the number of times I’ve clicked on banner ads in the past year. That is to say, once.</p>
<p>If you asked me how many times I’ve clicked on them in the 24 years before that (16 of which have been spent on the internet), that number doesn’t change. And I’m willing to bet that’s one more than most people.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4122" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/apple-ipad-mini-billboard-cursor.jpg" alt="apple ipad mini billboard-cursor" width="1280" height="957" /></p>
<p>I spend a few hours a week writing banner ads, and on joining the agency in the later half of last year, I did some research. One of the first articles I came across was from DigiDay, who had <a href="http://digiday.com/publishers/15-alarming-stats-about-banner-ads/">compiled stats from several studies on just how few people are clicking on banner ads.</a> Here are some of the more striking ones:</p>
<ul>
<li>Over 5.3 trillion display ads were served to U.S. users in 2012</li>
<li>The typical user is served 1,707 banner ads per month. For 25-34 year olds, that number rises to 2,094 per month</li>
<li>Click-through rates are 0.1%</li>
<li>The 468 x 60 banner has a 0.4% CTR</li>
<li>8% of internet users account for 85% of clicks</li>
<li>Up to 50% of clicks on mobile banner ads are accidental</li>
</ul>
<p>In another set of stats, this time from a Solve Media study, the list of things you’re more likely to do than click on a banner ad includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Surviving a plane crash (475.28 times more likely)</li>
<li>Climbing Mount Everest  (279.64x)</li>
<li>Signing up for, and completing Navy SEAL training (112.50x)</li>
<li>Applying to, and getting into Harvard (87.80x)</li>
</ul>
<p>Its research also claimed that clicks on banners <a href="http://www.cmo.com/articles/2012/4/24/banner-ads-past-present-and--future.html">are decreasing every year.</a></p>
<p>For someone just beginning in copywriting for banner ads, these stats were quite worrying. Does my “unique” CTA really make a difference? When I stress over the slide progression in a flash banner, am I just wasting my time? Are banner ads totally ineffective?</p>
<p>I shared my fears with a colleague, who causally rebuffed the significance of those numbers. “I’m guessing they’re consumer stats, and we’re B2B. And everyone knows they’re low. Banner ads aren’t about click-through-rates anyway; they’re about awareness,” she said.</p>
<p>It turns out, she was right. And it inspired me to become a defender of banner ads – the misunderstood, unfairly treated black sheep of the advertising game (not the ones that sit across your screen for 15,14,13, 12 seconds – they’re totally annoying).</p>
<p>Banners are used as an awareness tactic and are unfairly judged on clicks, simply because clicks are track-able. We can’t click on a print, radio, TV or billboard ad, but it doesn’t mean they’re not effective as an overall marketing mix.</p>
<p>They’re awesome for brand recognition, re-targeting, and re-engagement. If they’re targeted properly, which B2B ads are, they provide relevant and helpful content, and can make a big difference to an integrated campaign where paid, earned and owned tactics work together.</p>
<p>So here’s my current philosophy. When I write a banner, it doesn’t matter if it gets clicks of not. That really comes down to whether that person is interested in the product, service, or brand. And even if they are interested, they probably won’t click-through there and then. They may wait a week, or a month, and then search for it directly. What’s important is that these ads are well targeted and seen, because at that point, research has already told us that the message is wanted and needed.</p>
<p>Some have pointed to statistics like the ones above as a portent of <a href="http://techcrunch.com/2009/03/22/why-advertising-is-failing-on-the-internet/">the death of digital advertising</a>. And when you see those terrible, predatory ads that look like they’ll instantly infect your hard drive, it’s easy to see why. While I don’t believe banner ads have any reason to fear the reaper just yet, advertisers should look at the DigiDay stats and be humbled, and inspired to make better ads and improve whatever’s under their control.</p>
<p>What’s under my control is the quality of the copy. To me, that means honest, succinct, well judged, and well written. And if I achieve all those things, I know our designers will make it beautiful, and our B2B marketers will put the ad in the right place at the right time.</p>
<p>The digital world we live in creates a real challenge for banner ads, but if we’re respectful, relevant, and helpful, they’ll tolerate us. If we keep it up, they’ll trust us, and if we don’t exploit that, they’ll dialogue with us.</p>
<p>It might be that I only click on one more ad during the next 24 years of my life, but that doesn’t mean they’re not doing their job.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>User experience and the iPhone</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/05/09/2014/ux-smartphone-design/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 13:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UX]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3778</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I have a little secret to admit.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I have a little secret to admit. I really, really, really, really hate how people organize their smartphones. Take a look at someone&#8217;s phone nowadays and it&#8217;s screen after screen after screen of app icons, usually with no logic in place as to how they&#8217;re organized or arranged. As someone who has an eye towards UX, this drives me batty.</p>
<div id="attachment_3786" style="max-width: 110px" class="wp-caption alignright"><img class="wp-image-3786" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image1-146x220.png" alt="Exhibit A" width="100" height="150" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image1-146x220.png 146w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image1.png 640w" sizes="(max-width: 100px) 100vw, 100px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Exhibit A</p></div>
<p>Take for example, my wife&#8217;s phone—riddled with games, social media apps, and utilities—but in no discernible order. Ask her and she&#8217;ll gladly tell you that &#8220;everything is where it should be,&#8221; but I can tell it&#8217;s not. Having to flip through screens when using apps related to each other or even pausing to think about which screen an app might be on is straight up, a poor user experience.</p>
<p>Typically, a person thinks about user experience when they&#8217;re using a product that&#8217;s shared with the community—a company&#8217;s website, a piece of software, a methodology for ordering sandwiches at Whole Foods—but they don&#8217;t always equate user experience when they are the only user to experience it.</p>
<p>Just as I think about organizing website content, I think about organizing my devices. There are some client preferences (I don&#8217;t like too many rows of icons), some usability standards (reduce the number of clicks needed to open an app, organize content by themes), and some inherent properties (for example, how a person would use a phone as compared to a tablet). These are all things I think about when organizing my stuff.</p>
<p>Luckily for me, Apple has taken care to design their products to function in similar ways. They even migrated their computer OS to keep &#8220;apps&#8221; instead of programs, which I will admit was a little tough to process at first. So, as someone who loves to organize website data into something anyone could understand, Apple let me easily organize my devices and keep them consistent across the board.</p>
<p>Take for example, my iPhone:</p>
<div id="attachment_3779" style="max-width: 133px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Unknown.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-3779 size-medium" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-123x220.png" alt="Unknown" width="123" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-123x220.png 123w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-576x1024.png 576w" sizes="(max-width: 123px) 100vw, 123px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Exhibit B</p></div>
<p style="text-align: left;">I organized my apps into a few main buckets: Office (for those administrative things like email and calculator), Games (that&#8217;s pretty self-explanatory), Library (for pictures, books, and news), and A/V (for the camera, Pandora, and Roku). Apps that I use the most often are placed on their own, out of the folder structure. This includes some visual items like the calendar and the clock, both of which display the date and time so I can get visual info at-a-glance if I need to.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">And I take a similar approach to my iPad:</p>
<div id="attachment_3781" style="max-width: 175px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo1.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-3781 size-medium" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo1-165x220.png" alt="photo" width="165" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo1-165x220.png 165w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo1-768x1024.png 768w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo1.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 165px) 100vw, 165px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Exhibit C</p></div>
<p style="text-align: left;">Most of the same old culprits are there—Office, Games, Library, and A/V—but I&#8217;ve organized some of my go-to apps differently, based upon how I used my tablet compared to my phone. Email is front and center (I try not to check my email in the elevator), and I use my tablet most often for notes and to-dos, where I use my phone for music and GPS.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">The thread that holds the devices together, is that all of the other many, many, many apps that I have are housed in the same folders on my phone, my tablet, and even my computer. My news apps can be found in the Library, my Dropbox is always in the Office, and if I want to pull up <a href="http://www.wxpn.org" target="_blank">WXPN</a>, I know the radio will be under A/V.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">A lot of our clients have more than one website, and use cases on each website are different, much like that of a phone and tablet. <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/tag/brand-strategy/">Brand strategy</a> is extremely important for our clients, for obvious reasons. What some people forget about, is that a logo isn&#8217;t the only thing users use to identify a brand. Knowing where to look for content on a website and seeing your expectations pleasantly met will help increase your brand name and lower frustration.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Here at FVM we love to reorganize a website. Classification, card sorting, and qualitation—this is our bag, baby. There&#8217;s nothing like the feeling of redesigning a website that&#8217;s more organized, more efficient, and more streamlined than it was before. Except of course, diving into the analytics and user testing to see where else you can improve.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Some people might make fun of my smart device habits, but I know that the user experience on my iPhone is 100%. Of course if you ask my wife, she&#8217;ll probably tell you, &#8220;I can never find anything on this phone.&#8221;</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Oh well, time to take another look at the analytics&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
