<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>YouTube &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/youtube/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>YouTube had me at &#8220;Hello&#8221;</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/07/05/2013/youtube-had-me-at-hello/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2013 14:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[YouTube]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3056</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There are a handful of great social media platforms out there, but I’ve always been an advocate for YouTube.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are a handful of great social media platforms out there, but I’ve always been an advocate for YouTube. I read somewhere that on average, people watch four more hours of online video than regular TV every week. When you think about it, YouTube can be a pretty powerful thing. Take Bieber for example. This pint-sized crooner made it out of small-town Canada and into our hearts, all thanks to YouTube. Other teenage talents, like comedian Bo Burnham, songstress Esmee Denters, and the lovable Gaga-singing <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bxDlC7YV5is" target="_blank">Greyson Chance</a> have all had similar success.</p>
<p>So I know what you’re thinking. “Yeah, YouTube is great and fun to watch, but what’s in it for me?” My advice to you? Throw your hat in the ring. It only takes one video to go viral and your world can be turned upside down. Whether you’re a small business looking for a creative way to advertise, or a large corporation looking to attract a new generation of customers—YouTube could be the answer you’ve been looking for. It just takes one idea: one funny, thought provoking, interesting idea to get the attention of the hundreds of thousands of people who visit YouTube every day. So what have you got to lose? Grab a camera, draw up a storyboard and get started!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
