<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Research &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/research/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>4 market research trends shaping brand strategies</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/03/08/2018/4-market-research-trends-shaping-brand-strategies/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 23:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=7462</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Research is playing an increasingly larger role in brand and marketing strategy, so it’s important we stay on top of trends and new technologies.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Research is playing an increasingly larger role in brand and marketing strategy, so it’s important we stay on top of trends and new technologies. That’s why I recently attended the <a href="http://www.thequirksevent.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Quirk’s Event</a> in Brooklyn ⎯ a conference dedicated to all things market research ⎯ to meet with vendors, demo software, talk with peers, and listen to industry experts.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-7497" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Quirks-1.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="457" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Quirks-1.jpg 800w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Quirks-1-220x126.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Quirks-1-768x439.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></p>
<p>Here are four trends that marketers need to be aware of, and what they mean for B2B brands and marketing strategies.</p>
<h3>1: Man vs. machine</h3>
<p>Technology around market research is rapidly advancing. Digital behavior tracking, AI, and even neuroscience can provide real-time glimpses into audience behaviors, decision-making processes, and paths to purchase. But just because you can utilize these tools doesn’t necessarily mean you should.</p>
<p>Keeping goals and objectives in focus remains the most crucial aspect of crafting an effective approach. Being clear on the goals the research needs to accomplish, the questions you want to answer, the perspectives you have to uncover, as well as the behavioral data already at your disposal, will help you be selective with the technology you need, if any. Knowing exactly how the insights will inform the brand or marketing strategy will help protect timelines and budgets, too.</p>
<h3>2: More data, more depth</h3>
<p>Marketers are already struggling with what to do with the abundance of research data and analytics at our fingertips… and yet more data keeps coming.</p>
<p>Don’t be daunted!</p>
<p>It’s important to remember that the point isn’t to indiscriminately gather every data point under the sun. Yes, there’s a responsibility to understand and then harness relevant data, but the real challenge is to identify the story within, and shape a narrative that offers direction to a brand or marketing initiative.</p>
<h3>3: It’s not just a numbers game</h3>
<p>Technology and data are only really there to help us understand what drives audiences to make the decisions they do. It’s the human behind the number that we’re trying to get to ⎯ uncovering their worldviews, emotions, and needs.</p>
<p>And B2B audiences are famously complex, with one purchase typically requiring approval from a mix of influencers, users and decision-makers ⎯ often disconnected from one another ⎯ all dealing with different pressures. So it’s easy to miss crucial subtleties and nuances when relying solely on numbers and quantitative sources.</p>
<p>For that reason, it’s still vital for marketers to have direct, open dialogue ⎯ like one-on-one interviews ⎯ which remains core to any B2B research. That’s where tone is conveyed, human connections are formed, and deeply insightful conversations about audience drivers can (and usually do) happen.</p>
<h3>4: Stop, collaborate, and listen</h3>
<p>Insights and analytics professionals have become integral to many organizations, with more and more companies investing in and growing internal departments to help inform business strategy.</p>
<p>So marketers now have more owned data and insight than ever before, and can increasingly utilize it to identify challenges the brand is facing, verticals or channels that need the most attention, and areas where outside agencies can help.</p>
<p>This trend has ushered in era of greater collaboration between internal and external research, with more data being understood, shared, and used to shape strategy.</p>
<h3>Looking ahead</h3>
<p>Market research is a more valuable resource for B2B brands than ever before ⎯ technology is bringing us closer to audiences, and businesses are integrating more insights and analytics to drive business growth. As an agency, we’re seeing more B2B companies reach out to us recognizing the value of research in informing brand and marketing efforts.</p>
<p>It’s our job to understand the new tech, embrace the data, learn fresh methods, and collaborate more. But to be truly effective marketers, it is crucial that we never lose sight of the overall strategy and goals.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting more out of your B2B focus groups</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/17/2018/getting-more-out-of-your-b2b-focus-groups/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 18:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=7322</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Focus groups often get an unfair rap.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Focus groups often get an unfair rap. In high-stakes B2B environments, the phrase can conjure up images of wasted time and wasted money.</p>
<p>But focus groups provide a valuable opportunity to learn firsthand from customers and prospects about the issues that matter most. As a primary, qualitative research tool, focus groups can be used to uncover the emotional and rational reasons behind behavior, brand loyalty, and the buyer journey.</p>
<p>Extracting value from focus groups requires proper prep work, skilled moderating, and a detailed analysis integrated with other discovery work. This ensures that the time, effort, and resources required for a B2B focus group pay off in insights that drive results.</p>
<p>Here are the critical steps you can take to make sure that your focus group pays off for your business, and how to demonstrate the value of a focus group.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-7344 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Focus-Group-e1516894509534.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="533" /></p>
<p><strong>Set Objectives<br />
</strong>A clear, distinct objective allows for a more focused discussion, leading to deeper understanding of the issues at hand. Defining a clear-cut purpose can filter out surface-level findings and helps avoid leaving a negative impression among participants (who are likely customers).</p>
<p>The objective depends on the progress made during the discovery process, but typically falls into one of three categories:</p>
<p><u>Understanding broad, common topics</u><br />
Early in discovery work, focus groups provide a wide view of the industry, audience, and issues, revealing overarching trends. This approach usually requires extensive follow-up and isn’t recommended for B2B, where these themes can be discovered elsewhere.</p>
<p><u>Validating or refuting themes</u><br />
A focus group that occurs sometime in the middle of discovery work can confirm or deny previously uncovered findings among a broader set of customers. This is likely the best use of a B2B group.</p>
<p><u>Testing creative<br />
</u>Towards the end of discovery and into brand development, you can test the industry tropes and customer preferences uncovered during prior discovery work. The focus group can tell you which directions resonate and which fall flat.</p>
<p><strong>Recruit Participants<br />
</strong>The right mix of participants can make or break a focus group. It’s important that the group is representative of the audience as a whole, but with enough commonalities that the conversation will be productive. Group participants also need to be able to talk openly and honestly among peers.</p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Recruiting for Focus Groups: B2B vs. B2C</strong></span><span style="color: #000000;"><strong><br />
</strong></span>Participant recruiting is probably where B2B focus groups differ most from traditional B2C. Keep these tips in mind when you begin your recruiting process:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Be persistent.</strong> Targeted audiences make for a much smaller pool of possible participants. Professionals are often busy, making them difficult to reach and unlikely to participate.</li>
<li><strong>Beware of biases.</strong> Most participants are recommended and recruited by the sales force because they’re already fans of the brand meaning results could be positively skewed.</li>
<li><strong>Remember the bigger picture.</strong> Only one person from a given customer type or prospect may be represented, even though the purchase decision typically involves multiple roles and functions.</li>
<li><strong>Provide incentives.</strong> Monetary gifts are nice, but the general rule is that professionals need to feel valued and appreciated. A sincere thank you along with specifics on how their participation will ultimately benefit their own business goes a long way.</li>
<li><strong>Be sensitive to privacy concerns.</strong> Having competing businesses in the same group can become problematic if participants aren’t comfortable discussing their challenges or successes in front of the competition.</li>
</ul>
<p>For B2B, consider factors including job title, role, and company size. It’s possible that multiple groups will be needed to achieve the correct balance of sample representation and commonalities for a productive discussion.</p>
<blockquote><p>One of FVM’s large telecom clients segmented its audience into two buckets: enterprise and SMB. These two groups both faced challenges when it came to telecomm needs but approached them from very different contexts. Our client needed to engage with both audiences and sought to determine the best way to approach each.</p>
<p>So we conducted two separate focus groups: varying participants’ job titles, longevity with our client, and industries represented between both groups.</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Craft the Discussion Guide<br />
</strong>Realistically, a B2B focus group will be 2.5 hours total, including time for introductions, breaks, and closing remarks. It’s important to be realistic about what can and cannot be accomplished in this window. Plan for five to six main topics, with probing questions or workshop-style exercises to spur dialogue. Remember: the guide, while important, is merely a tool. It’s up to the group and moderator to engage in dialogue that covers the key topics.</p>
<p>Allow participants to dictate the flow and pace of the conversation by crafting a fluid guide that starts out broader and moves into more specific lines of questioning. Let participants determine the length and depth of each conversation, highlighting which topics are most important.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-7341" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/fvm-034-focus-group-image.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="745" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-034-focus-group-image.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-034-focus-group-image-220x164.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-034-focus-group-image-768x572.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<h6>A nonlinear guide format helps the moderator follow the room, rather than being restricted to a predetermined order of events.</h6>
<p>Use the objectives discussed above as the key starting points for your discussion guides.</p>
<p><u>Understanding broad, common topics<br />
</u>Include open-ended questions that ask participants about their roles, challenges, and competition.</p>
<p><u>Validating or refuting themes<br />
</u>Carefully choose topics that require further explanation. Plan to discuss each one, allowing enough time to hear from each participant and follow up on responses. Don’t waste time on topics that can be explored elsewhere.<strong> </strong></p>
<p><u>Testing creative<br />
</u>Share creative directions to determine how certain images, concepts, and colors make the participants feel. In B2B, focus groups are the perfect opportunity to establish which industry themes are most expected, needed, or overused.</p>
<blockquote><p>For example, we used a focus group to test one industry’s most common uses of imagery: blurred lights, moving traffic, and stock photography of smiling business people. When we ran these tropes by group participants, we discovered that the photos of smiling people were problematic. Group members asked, “Are the people supposed to represent me or the vendor?” On the other hand, the images denoting speed resonated well.</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Moderate the Discussion<br />
</strong>Skilled moderators are able to elicit information beyond “top of mind” responses, uncovering rational, behavioral, and emotional drivers. In order to reach this second and third-level information, keep these functions in mind while moderating:</p>
<ul>
<li>Understand the objective and enough about the subject matter to speak intelligently on it.</li>
<li>Make no assumptions and remain unbiased, maintaining an open mind to all opinions and thoughts.</li>
<li>Demonstrate respect for the participants, proving their time is valuable and their voices are being heard.</li>
<li>Maintain a high energy level throughout varied tasks and question types, including open-ended questions and questions that allow participants to jot down answers.</li>
<li>Manage the conversation, diving deeper where necessary and tactfully cutting off irrelevant topics or commentary.</li>
</ul>
<p>Stay tuned for a follow-up piece with more on moderating B2B focus groups, including a breakdown of the most common B2B focus group participants.</p>
<p><strong>Analyze the Results<br />
</strong>Focus groups represent just one facet of discovery, so it’s important to integrate your findings with data from all other sources. By comparing and contrasting results with interviews, web analytics, and other discovery methods, you’ll find that themes and trends will emerge.</p>
<p>Keep an eye out for these common clues in focus group output:</p>
<ul>
<li>Polarizing conversations that left participants on different sides of the issues often indicate topics that need further exploration and validation.</li>
<li>Topics on which participants spent more time are most likely hot-button issues.</li>
<li>Conversations among the participants could suggest areas where there is a desire to learn more from peers. It could also signify a place for the client to enter the conversation as a thought leader.</li>
</ul>
<p>Focus groups can provide valuable information in a short amount of time. With the appropriate preparation, participant mix, moderation, and analysis, you can gain valuable understanding of your client’s industry, competitors, audience, and challenges laying the foundation for a powerful brand or campaign.</p>
<p><em> </em><strong>Learn More about B2B Focus Groups</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.b2binternational.com/publications/what-is-the-future-for-b2b-focus-groups/">https://www.b2binternational.com/publications/what-is-the-future-for-b2b-focus-groups/</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.quirks.com/articles/qualities-of-a-master-moderator">https://www.quirks.com/articles/qualities-of-a-master-moderator</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.research-live.com/article/features/playing-hard-to-get/id/5006752">https://www.research-live.com/article/features/playing-hard-to-get/id/5006752</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.circle-research.com/2014/b2b-market-research/">http://www.circle-research.com/2014/b2b-market-research/</a></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Listening for a brand that resonates</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/12/2016/listening-for-a-brand-that-resonates/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 23:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6480</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We have a deceptively simple solution for creating strong B2B brands: listening.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have a deceptively simple solution for creating strong B2B brands: listening. That’s why it’s 90% of our brand discovery process. We listen to uncover every angle, perspective, and nuance so that the brand we create <em>truly</em> resonates with the people who matter most: buyers.</p>
<p>Content audits, digital reviews, and competitive research play a major role in brand discovery, too (and there’ll be more posts to follow on those), but here’s a little insight into how we break down the “question and answer” side and how each tactic informs the branding process.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6491 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_84GOP2OAKR.jpg" alt="Startup Stock Photos" width="1000" height="662" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_84GOP2OAKR.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_84GOP2OAKR-220x146.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_84GOP2OAKR-768x508.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Group Strategy Sessions</span></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>What are they?</em></strong></p>
<p>A chance to hear about the business and brand from the client’s perspective. And it’s not necessarily just about the CEO and CMO. We want to hear from leaders and key employees within as many departments as possible, from sales to finance to customer service. Because a brand isn’t just what the leadership says it is; the brand lives in the people who represent it.</p>
<p><strong><em>What do we listen for? </em></strong></p>
<p>Through conversation and customized brand exercises, we’re looking for a holistic view of where the brand is currently sitting, what challenges and competition it is facing, what the business aims are, and what the brand needs to achieve for the company.<strong><em> </em></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>How does it inform the branding process?</em></strong></p>
<p>A strong internal perspective creates a reliable brand benchmark. From here, we cast a wider net and see how other perspectives measure up.</p>
<p><strong><u>Personal Interviews</u></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>What are they?</em></strong></p>
<p>Interviews usually happen next after a strategy session. They present the opportunity to talk one-on-one — in-person or by phone — with key stakeholders: the client (again), their customers, and their partners. Client (or “internal”) interviews give us a chance to dig deeper into key issues uncovered during the strategy session, while customer (or “external”) interviews focus on our client’s brand, offering, and the ways their products and services are used. But more importantly, the interviews also focus on the customer’s <em>own</em> business: challenges they face on a regular basis, their wants and needs, solutions they love or hate, and their perspectives on the industry.</p>
<p><strong><em>What do we listen for?</em></strong></p>
<p>First, we compare what we heard internally and externally, asking: Is what our client says about themselves the same as what their customers say? Second, we use this more intimate conversation as an opportunity to get past surface-level responses and uncover the true emotions surrounding a business, industry, and brand.</p>
<p><strong><em>How does it inform the branding process?</em></strong></p>
<p>A brand must connect with its audience. A company might believe they know the right way to differentiate their brand, but the attributes they’re calling out may not matter to target audiences. One-on-one interviews help us identify where the current brand succeeds and fails in connecting, as well as where opportunities exist to build a brand strategy that is true to both the client — and to customers’ needs.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6494 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/iStock-483395705-copy.jpg" alt="man having presentation at seminar" width="1000" height="667" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/iStock-483395705-copy.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/iStock-483395705-copy-220x147.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/iStock-483395705-copy-768x512.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p><strong><u>Focus Groups</u></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>What are they?</em></strong></p>
<p>Focus groups are a great <em>qualitative</em> research weapon. We guide a small group representing a sample of our client’s audience through conversations, interactions, and exercises so they can discuss a client’s brand and provide feedback on any initial brand strategy routes or creative concepts.</p>
<p><strong><em>What do we listen for?</em></strong></p>
<p>We’re looking to gain a deep understanding of experiences and perceptions, listening for common trends and points of agreement and disagreement. At its best, a focus group points­­­­­­ us straight towards brand and industry hot spots, showing what issues make people the most passionate, either in a good way, or bad way.</p>
<p><strong><em>How does it inform the branding process?</em></strong></p>
<p>Focus groups add another layer of depth to our findings and help hone strategy. We test strengths and weaknesses in our findings and ideas, identify points where more clarification or research is needed, and confirm pitfalls the brand should avoid. And with the right mix of people in the room, we can feel good knowing we’ve heard from all potential audience groups.</p>
<p><strong><u>Surveys</u></strong></p>
<p><strong><em>What are they?</em></strong></p>
<p>Low-cost, quick, and completely scalable, surveys are our go-to quantitative data approach. Since surveys are anonymous, they present a chance to collect very open and honest input from stakeholders and encourage a more straightforward, rational response.</p>
<p><strong><em>What do we listen for?</em></strong></p>
<p>The standardized format of surveys allow us to ask pointed questions, enabling easy identification of trends across broad groups.</p>
<p><strong><em>How does it inform the branding process?</em></strong></p>
<p>A survey can be useful early in discovery to get a broad view of opinions on multiple key issues. Surveys are also valuable as a final checkpoint so we can take the temperature and confirm we’re heading in the right direction.</p>
<p><strong><u>The truth will emerge</u></strong></p>
<p>Asking questions and listening intently allows us create a brand that aligns a company’s performance and aspirations with the needs and expectations of its customers. It’s that simple.</p>
<p>We take all of the insights we hear — hold them up against findings from a client’s greater marketplace — and distill them into authentic, compelling brand attributes, which can then be interpreted, tested, and tweaked with certainty.</p>
<p>A brand that truly resonates really is just a few conversations away. All we have to do is listen.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
