<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>marketing &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/marketing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>FVM named top B2B agency</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/12/2017/fvm-named-top-b2b-agency/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 21:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alex Chapin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=7187</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a list?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who doesn’t love a list? We sure do – especially when we’re named as one of the leading B2B Brand Engagement agencies in the U.S.</p>
<p>The Chief Marketer 200 – the publication’s first comprehensive editorial list of the nation’s top 200 marketing agencies – highlights the best engagement and activation agencies based on several criteria, including client testimonials, case studies, creative concepts and executions, caliber of work, and thought leadership. The program has been created to help marketing professionals navigate to the most suitable agencies for their brands.</p>
<p>Needless to say, we’re delighted to be recognized for the work that our team does in creating and fostering brands, and connecting them with B2B audiences. And of course, none of this would be possible without our incredible clients who inspire us every day.</p>
<p>You can see the <a href="http://www.chiefmarketer.com/cm200/?q=winners" target="_blank" rel="noopener">full list here</a>.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-7188" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Chief-Marketer-200-_600.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="556" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Chief-Marketer-200-_600.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Chief-Marketer-200-_600-220x204.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>B2B, coast to coast</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/05/2017/our-30th-birthday-and-some-exciting-news/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 04:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jon Cohen]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6930</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[FVM is 30 years old!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FVM is 30 years old! Finally, we’re mature, sensible adults. So happy birthday to us. And our big news is that we’re opening a second location in beautiful Portland, OR to expand our B2B brand and marketing offering and better serve west coast businesses.</p>
<p>Portland is a city with thriving tech and B2B industries, top creative talent, and without a doubt one of the best food cart scenes we’ve ever binged on. Looking right at you <a href="https://www.yelp.com/biz/nongs-khao-man-gai-portland">Nong’s</a>. <em>And,</em> Portland is well connected to other major business hubs like Seattle and San Francisco. For us, the expansion is an opportunity to do more of what we’re passionate about: working with savvy clients to build and sustain standout brands. We’ll seek out companies to partner with in complex and competitive B2B industries and help position them to compete, grow, and win, just like we always have.</p>
<p>But apart from spreading out to the west coast, it’s business as usual. We’ll keep on keepin’ on with the same hard working, forward thinking approach that got us this far.</p>
<p>Here’s to the next 30 years! And welcome to the world FVM Portland.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Of Pastries and Products: How to Find a Common Language</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/13/2017/of-pastries-and-products-how-to-find-a-common-language/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 21:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Calvin Son]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6746</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Quick — what’s the difference between a funnel cake, a beignet, and a zeppole?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Quick — what’s the difference between a funnel cake, a beignet, and a zeppole?</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6764" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/beignets.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="468" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/beignets.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/beignets-220x103.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/beignets-768x359.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>At FVM, we spend a lot of time discussing (and eating) snacks. That recently led to a conversation about our favorite deep-fried, sugar-dusted pastries. Some of us knew them as beignets. Others insisted they were zeppoles. A third group rounded out Team Funnel Cake.</p>
<p>Naturally, we Googled it. It turns that while the three pastries might seem similar at first, each has its own distinct characteristics and history. And each of us had assumed that everyone else had grown up eating the same sweet treats we had.</p>
<p>The same kind of assumption happens in businesses all the time. In fact, we recently helped a client — a new-to-market technology company — whose employees were all over the place in terms of what the company had to offer, and who the company was looking to serve.</p>
<p>One group of employees viewed the company through the lens of one particular capability, while another faction emphasized a different product altogether. Different products were at different stages of completion. Words like “solution” and “tool” were used interchangeably. There was a lack of certainty as to whether the people <em>using</em> the products were the same people <em>buying</em> the products. The developer probably sighed a lot.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft wp-image-6758 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_16VYGB9PG5.jpg" width="1000" height="468" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_16VYGB9PG5.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_16VYGB9PG5-220x103.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/StockSnap_16VYGB9PG5-768x359.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>That’s where we came in. FVM’s task was to facilitate a daylong product planning session that would bring clarity to our client’s products and services, building the foundation for their go-to-market plan.</p>
<p>First, we did our homework. The subject matter was complex, but we took the time to reach our own understanding of the client’s products, technologies and audiences. We’re a naturally curious bunch.</p>
<p>Then we built creative exercises from scratch. While we have reliable favorites, we don’t use a cookie-cutter approach for our clients. Even within the same industry, no two companies are identical.</p>
<p>In this case, our goal was to trigger discussion. The exercises were cumulative — beginning with customers and their issues, then identifying the services that solve those issues, the delivery of those services, and their value, and finally ending with overall prioritization.</p>
<p>On the day of the session, we met with our client’s senior leadership. We created teams by mixing members from different roles across the company. Then we guided them through the exercises we created to cover four Ps of product language.<strong> </strong></p>
<ol>
<li><strong> Personas</strong></li>
</ol>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6757" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/jon_papers-1.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="468" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/jon_papers-1.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/jon_papers-1-220x103.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/jon_papers-1-768x359.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>We created social media-style profiles for our client’s target customers based on the background information available, including brief bios and status updates. Who were they? What would they be excited about? What would they tweet in frustration? Together, the teams not only completed these cards, but their discussion also revealed entirely new groups of buyer and user personas to target.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li><strong> Products</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Next, we led the teams through a customized game of Taboo. Players had to get teammates to guess the product or feature listed on their card. The catch was, they couldn’t say the word itself, or the five related words listed on the card.</p>
<p>Participants were forced to cut the jargon they’d previously leaned on, instead describing their offerings in simple, everyday language. They successfully identified areas where they were confusing internal and external language — what they did, versus what they delivered — and where they were overusing, and therefore watering down, certain key words.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li><strong> Positioning</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>This is where the bigger picture began to take shape. For each product, the teams discussed and answered four key questions.</p>
<ul>
<li>What do I get and how do I get it?</li>
<li>What will it help me do?</li>
<li>Which features and capabilities should I be most excited about?</li>
<li>What other products and services are required and/or recommended?</li>
</ul>
<p>This exercise was especially enlightening for everyone in the room. It became clear that there were overlaps and inconsistencies in terms of what features were being highlighted, and to whom. The group began identifying redundancies and slashing unnecessary products on the spot.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li><strong> Prioritization</strong></li>
</ol>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6756" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/paper-1.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="468" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/paper-1.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/paper-1-220x103.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/paper-1-768x359.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Finally, we had participants fill out scorecards for their core products, using only their gut reactions to assign values based on four metrics:</p>
<ul>
<li>Value to Customer — How valuable is this product to its audience?</li>
<li>Market Demand — How large is the need in the near term?</li>
<li>Capability — How good are we at this today?</li>
<li>Speed to Market — How fast can you go, and what are the barriers?</li>
</ul>
<p>We used a rubric to see where everyone’s scores landed. By this point, the wall was filled with a linear map of the client’s products and offerings. We could see at a glance what was working and what wasn’t.</p>
<p>Finally, we pushed products through a bracket, March Madness-style, to determine which products could be crowned champion. Each group still had a favorite, but we were able to reach an agreement on overall hierarchy.</p>
<p><strong>Finding Resolution</strong></p>
<p>Our client had developed incredible technology to create an impressive range of products. But our exercises allowed them to untangle their language to reach a common understanding. We created a neutral space where everyone could voice his or her opinions, identify where progress needed to be made, and reach important strategic decision points.</p>
<p>Today, this client is much further along in its product marketing process. The company’s leadership is aligned to make their business more competitive — which is always our ultimate goal. Because getting everyone on the same page is a sweet, sweet deal — regardless of what you want to call it.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What they don’t teach you in college: working advice from a first year AE</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/15/2016/what-they-dont-teach-you-in-college-working-advice-from-a-first-year-ae/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 23:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coleman Rigg]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6169</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I just finished presenting a project to our client, I have three deadlines to meet by the end of the week, and I still need a more creative title for this blog post.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I just finished presenting a project to our client, I have three deadlines to meet by the end of the week, and I still need a more creative title for this blog post. I’m swimming in strategies, spreadsheets, tasks, and processes.</p>
<p>To think, just 365 moons ago I was waking up in my college bed, groggy from yet another Senior Week adventure, days away from graduation, living the millennial dream without a responsibility in the world.</p>
<p>I’ve been a Junior AE at FVM for around ten months now and it’s been a rollercoaster. In some ways I feel seasoned; in others I feel novice. But through it all, I’ve learned a lot.</p>
<p>So this blog is for the bleary-eyed, 21 year-old, college student I once was. Here’s some insight and advice on how to wake up and enjoy the ride.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6174 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload.jpg" alt="slack_for_ios_upload" width="1000" height="668" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload-220x147.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload-768x513.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<h5><strong><em>Day one</em></strong></h5>
<h2>Week one wake up call</h2>
<p>My first week at FVM was pretty typical: Read the employee handbook, learn everyone’s names, and communicate directly with a senior designer to finalize a piece of creative. It didn’t get any easier from there. By day four I was contributing on important marketing projects for our clients. You could call it a steep learning curve.</p>
<p><em>Tip #1: This is a real job, not a baby-sitters club.</em></p>
<h2>Diving in head first</h2>
<p>The “deep end” is something we talk about a lot. Metaphorically, the deep end represents something beyond surface-level thinking. In marketing, the deep end is the research, questions, answers, and analysis that are required to burrow into a client’s challenges.</p>
<p>My own personal deep end is balancing varied responsibilities at what seems like hyper-speed at first. During these nine months, I’ve gone from inexperienced college grad to fresh-faced pair of hands, to frequent contributor, to wing-man of our EVP of Client Services on key accounts. Oddly enough, I’m even growing a beard like him, although mine is not quite as “experienced.”</p>
<p><em>Tip #2: Dive in head first, because you can’t learn to swim with your feet still touching the bottom.</em></p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6176 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438.jpg" alt="IMG_1438" width="1631" height="713" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438.jpg 1631w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438-220x96.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438-768x336.jpg 768w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438-1024x448.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 1631px) 100vw, 1631px" /></p>
<h2></h2>
<h5><strong><em>The deep end</em></strong></h5>
<h2>Questions, questions, questions</h2>
<p>I used to think that if I didn’t know about something mentioned in a meeting or conversation, it was better just to nod along and then look it up later.</p>
<p>I wouldn’t risk asking stupid questions like, “Will this need to be printed?” or “Is this strictly a digital piece?”</p>
<p>But when that one question I never asked came back to bite me in the ass, I stopped thinking that way.</p>
<p>Guess what? It turns out that everyone in the room is more knowledgeable and experienced than you. They like it when you ask questions. And their answers provide far more first-hand insight than anything you’ll find in a search engine.</p>
<p>Yes, from the moment you enter school as a child you are taught to ask questions, receive answers, and (hopefully) learning will follow. But for some inexplicable reason, when I entered the working world I thought I was expected to know it all.</p>
<p>There <em>are</em> such things as dumb questions, but asking them is key, because not knowing the dumb answers is worse than not asking the dumb question. Duh.</p>
<p><em>Tip #3: If you want to learn as quickly as possible, speak up, because no one will speak up for you.</em></p>
<p><img class="alignleft wp-image-6173 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload.jpeg" alt="slack_for_ios_upload" width="750" height="555" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload.jpeg 750w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload-220x163.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>
<h5><strong><em>It even says it on the wall</em></strong></h5>
<h2>Everybody has their days</h2>
<p>“I’m the man.”</p>
<p>“That was dumb.”</p>
<p>“I have such a good idea!”</p>
<p>“THAT WAS A STUPID IDEA. WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?! IN A MEETING?! REALLY!? Nice job, idiot.”</p>
<p>The highs and lows I’ve experienced are the second most exhilarating part of working in advertising (the first is dominating on the ping pong table, day in and day out). There are days when everything goes perfectly; all work receives high praise and positive feedback. There are also days I can’t even remember to attach documents to an email.</p>
<p>It’s all about balance. Don’t beat yourself up all week about one mistake, and don’t bask in the glory of a small victory for too long.</p>
<p><em>Tip #4: Briefly enjoy the highs, learn from your lows, and move on because there’s work to be done. </em></p>
<h2>Agency life is “the life”</h2>
<p>“I love my job” was a statement that always troubled me. I mean can anyone really <em>love</em> his or her job? Is that a real feeling? Or is this just something people say to cope with the idea that they have to spend 40+ hours a week doing something for money? The idea had always been blurry to me.</p>
<p>I refuse to write a mushy bit that declares I have the greatest job in the world and all other jobs aren’t as fun or cool as mine. But with that being said, agency life rocks! The daily routine does not involve sipping whiskey, smoking Lucky Strikes, or throwing lavish office parties, but it is way more lively than I ever imagined an “adult” job could be.</p>
<p>Cooking competitions, existential debates, acoustic guitar serenades (by me), flying drones, wearing pajamas, playing darts, and shooting hoops are all part of the mix. No stuffy small talk, power/ego trips, or menial work intended to haze the new guy. Needless to say, I really like my job.</p>
<p><em>Tip #5: With the right company, right people, hard work, and a little time, you’ll find yourself saying those four silly words, too.</em></p>
<h5><img class="alignleft wp-image-6172 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Coleman2.jpg" alt="Coleman2" width="1000" height="534" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman2.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman2-220x117.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman2-768x410.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><strong><em>I got this</em></strong></h5>
<h5><img class="alignleft wp-image-6171 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Coleman1.jpg" alt="Coleman1" width="1000" height="570" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman1.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman1-220x125.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman1-768x438.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><strong><em>If you can&#8217;t chug a gallon of apple cider or wear a choker for a week, don&#8217;t lose the bet</em></strong></h5>
<h2><strong>Get out of bed</strong></h2>
<p>While my roles and responsibilities are challenging and constantly changing, I’m just happy to be swimming in the deep end here at FVM. I’m learning, I’m enjoying, and I’m growing…a beard. What more could I want?</p>
<p><em>One last tip: Get out of bed, eat a proper meal, and start working on your ping-pong game. </em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Social media advertising: Extending your targeted reach</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/04/2015/social-media-advertising-extending-your-targeted-reach/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 08:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5133</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[LinkedIn, Twitter and Facebook are still babies.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LinkedIn, Twitter and Facebook are still babies. Not even teenagers. Social media appeared quickly. It was fun, but hard to trust, as your favorite platforms disappeared just as quickly as they had arrived (I’m looking at you, Friendster). Many wrote it off as a passing fad; some market trend that would people would tire of eventually. And few early adopters would have seen its business potential.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-5202 size-full alignright" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/social.jpg" alt="social" width="810" height="470" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/social.jpg 810w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/social-220x128.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 810px) 100vw, 810px" /></p>
<p>But growth continued, advertising opportunities were created and in 2014 social media advertising spend hit <a href="http://www.emarketer.com/Article/Social-Network-Ad-Spending-Hit-2368-Billion-Worldwide-2015/1012357" target="_blank">$7.71BN in N. America; 56% growth on the previous year. This year it’s predicted to break $10BN, and by 2017 it will smash $15BN</a>. Why? Because ad dollars follow eyeballs; one third of the world’s internet users are on Facebook. And because social platforms harness incredible data to identify a myriad of audiences to target.</p>
<p>Yes, social media’s a great way to share helpful content, inform and engage followers, and keep your organization top of mind as a thought leader. It’s been this for a while, and improves almost on a monthly basis. LinkedIn, for example, continues to grow as it transforms from social network to B2B content publishing platform.</p>
<p>But here’s a thing; organic reach is not what it once was. As of a couple of years ago, Facebook updated its algorithm so brand page posts became more “relevant.” Or less visible, in that not even <em>all</em> followers see updates. That equals fewer interactions, leads and customers.</p>
<p>Even if all of your posts<em> were</em> visible to your entire follower base, you’d still only reach people who already know and like you enough to have hit your “follow” button at some point. Preaching to the choir, you could argue.</p>
<p>More than ever, utilizing social media’s real power lies in advertising and reach <em>outside</em> your follower-base. Here are a few reasons why.</p>
<p><strong>Killer targeting</strong></p>
<p>The targeting capabilities within social media advertising are simply unparalleled and go deeper than any other online digital platform. What it all means is that marketers have the opportunity to increase an ad’s relevance to users, and to know that certain demographics will receive the ad.</p>
<p>Facebook ads allow marketers to target by geography, interests, behaviors, and parental status (even expectant parents!). Twitter offers advertisers targets based on who they follow—your competitors, industry publications, or market analysts, perhaps. The possibilities are pretty much endless. But here’s how they break down:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Interests/Skills<br />
</strong>Social users share—it’s what they do. The nature of the beast. With every self-reported skill or interest or engagement, users identify themselves as a certain audience, and one that can be targeted. LinkedIn—the world’s largest professional network—has <a href="https://press.linkedin.com/about-linkedin" target="_blank">115million users in the US (364million globally)</a> and aims to reach <a href="http://venturebeat.com/2013/10/23/linkedin-ceo-by-next-year-50-of-our-traffic-will-be-mobile/" target="_blank">3 billion</a> in the long-term, with the vast majority offering their industry, job title, employer, skills and location. Every B2B marketer’s dream.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Behavioral/Connections<br />
</strong>With every purchase made, device utilized, page liked, app used, group joined or event attended, Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn are analyzing continued behavior and intent. Think retargeting, but nicely packaged up in social. While search is reactive, this kind of targeting is proactive.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Custom/Tailored<br />
</strong>Great data exists outside of social media too, of course. If you have email addresses, phone numbers or other user IDs, Twitter and Facebook will take them, match them to users and advertise directly.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Lookalikes<br />
</strong>LinkedIn and Facebook know your audience’s doppelganger. If a business has served ads to all custom audiences and is looking for greater reach, where is there left to go? Well, based on that data, the platforms will identify and generate similar, relevant audiences who “look like” your existing ones.</li>
</ul>
<p>So the targeting’s awesome, but what else is there to think about?</p>
<p><strong>Conversion tracking</strong><br />
Conversions are the Holy Grail in media campaigns. Driving a user to act in a certain way—signing up for a webinar or buying something, for example—is a conversion, and essential to measure for performance and proving your ad’s value.</p>
<p>It’s always been possible for marketers to measure certain metrics through their own sites, but social media has upped its game with conversion tracking. While it’s possible to track social interactions by setting up Goals in Google Analytics, the level of detail pales in comparison to the insights offered by the social networks themselves. Now you can attribute conversions on your site to social ads in real time—allowing you to adjust and optimize where needed.<strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>Modest budgets welcome</strong></p>
<p>Small budgets can get eaten up quickly when using a cost per thousand impression (CPM) bid strategy on the Google Display Network and other similar platforms, but almost all social media platforms offer pay-per-click options. The PPC model means marketers with all sizes of budget can start reaching their target social audience straight away. Not to mention the insights gained from a small PPC test. Which job title responded to my ads the most? Which headline was the attention-grabber? The answers are here, and they won’t break the bank.</p>
<p><strong>Going mobile</strong></p>
<p>Social media and mobile are smitten. The power couple continues to create new audiences, expand reach and generate more ad opportunities.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.cio.com/article/2453934/social-media/mobile-advertising-will-dominate-social-networks.html" target="_blank">Facebook and Twitter are two of the three biggest players in mobile advertising in the U.S.</a> (the other’s Google (not Google+)). That’s right, Facebook made <a href="http://investor.fb.com/releasedetail.cfm?ReleaseID=908022" target="_blank">$3.32 billion in Q1 2015</a> and almost three-quarters of that revenue came from mobile advertising—meaning they control over <a href="http://www.cio.com/article/2453934/social-media/mobile-advertising-will-dominate-social-networks.html" target="_blank">70% of all social ad spend</a>. Twitter announced a <a href="https://investor.twitterinc.com/releasedetail.cfm?releaseid=909177" target="_blank">Q1 2015 ad revenue of $388 million</a> with mobile ads accounting for 89% of total ad revenue—a 72% jump from last year.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.emarketer.com/Article/2-Billion-Consumers-Worldwide-Smartphones-by-2016/1011694" target="_blank">It’s estimated that over a third (2.56Bn) of the world’s population will have a smartphone by 2018</a>. <a href="http://www.businessinsider.com/chart-of-the-day-americans-spend-more-time-using-mobile-devices-than-tv-2014-11" target="_blank">Having already overtaken desktop browsing and TV viewing hours in the U.S.</a>, mobile advertising now represents the best opportunity to reach people going about their daily lives, and social is leading that charge. <strong><br />
</strong></p>
<p><strong>Know your audience</strong></p>
<p>Engaging with followers and targeting the right people is what it’s all about. But it’s important not to lose sight of the fact that you must <em>first</em> know that audience inside and out. Social media sites are most likely one place they hang out, but where else do they spend their time—online and offline? What kinds of offers appeal to them? What types of keywords are they searching?</p>
<p>Marketers who take a one-shot approach with Facebook advertising, for example, and say it failed, are taking too narrow of a view. Social media advertising needs to be just one avenue to reach your prospect base and part of a larger marketing communications strategy.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting sentimental with interactive video</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/11/2015/spark-of-digital-getting-sentimental-with-interactive-video/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 15:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tom O'Brien]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4435</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Attention spans are decreasing at an alarming rate.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://blogs.sap.com/innovation/sales-marketing/thanks-social-media-average-attention-span-now-shorter-goldfish-01251966" target="_blank">Attention spans are decreasing at an alarming rate</a>. Not only does your content need to pique interest and attract visitors; it has to keep them hooked, too. With Web 2.0 came the advent of amazing new interactive tools for marketers to reach audiences, and videos are no exception. It’s not enough to be the visually stimulating alternative to boring old text anymore, video has to promise a payoff and offer a reason to stay.</p>
<p>Enter the folks at <em><a href="http://www.raptmedia.com/" target="_blank">Rapt Media</a></em>, who have created something awesome. Their platform allows users to easily create interactive videos with a smart and simple interface. And it even has SEO capabilities baked right in. Check out how they were able to help <em>Deloitte</em> gamify their recruiting process with a slickly designed video that plays out like one of those <em>Choose Your Own Adventure</em> books from when you were a kid.</p>
<p><iframe src="http://cdn1.raptmedia.com/projects/j2Nu6adZ/embed?autoplay=false&amp;controls=overlay#http://www.raptmedia.com/project/deloitte" width="100%" height="300" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Iframes are required to view this content.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Interactive videos aren’t necessarily new; clickable links and embedded popups are common across the web, especially on sites like <em>YouTube</em> and <em>Vimeo</em>. What <em>Rapt</em> has done is produce interactive videos that demand viewer attention. That’s why they can tout longer user engagement and higher CTRs.</p>
<p>So how does it all work? <em>Rapt’s</em> platform is simple yet elegant in its design.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-4437 alignright" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Untitled21.png" alt="Untitled2" width="900" height="532" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled21.png 900w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled21-220x130.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></p>
<p>An interactive layer is placed over the main video with clickable hotspots linking to other clips at strategic points. This allows marketers to create videos with multiple outcomes, depending on a viewer’s preference. The result is almost like a built-in A/B test (or A/B/C/D…) showing which path each user took.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.prdaily.com/Main/Articles/The_role_of_sentiment_in_social_data_analysis__16072.aspx" target="_blank">Brand sentiment</a> has become an increasingly important aspect of digital marketing. The ability to understand an audience at a granular level is invaluable to marketers. So building rich, interactive videos that hold viewer attention and demand genuine engagement is no small thing, and worth our attention.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The &#8220;Forgotten Few&#8221;: 3 key elements to video marketing ROI</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/30/2014/the-forgotten-few-3-key-elements-to-video-marketing-roi/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 19:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4391</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There has always been a lot of “good stuff” out there.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There has always been a lot of “good stuff” out there. When I first joined the video production scene a few years ago, I looked at what others were doing and was attracted to the beautifully designed videos with high-end production, all brought to life with seemingly-expensive animation, blends of talking-head and technical graphics, expert footage capture, catchy music, perfectly casted talent and voiceovers. Good design and great stories are wonderful, but experience has taught me that without implementing some simple key elements, your videos will not deliver the ROI you (or your client) are looking for.</p>
<p>These elements can be <em>proven</em> to drive ROI and are what performance analytics are based on. I call them the “Forgotten Few,” and it’s surprising how many marketing videos are without them.</p>
<p>My “Forgotten Few” are:</p>
<ol>
<li>Call-to-Action</li>
<li>SEO</li>
<li>Localization/translation</li>
</ol>
<h3><strong>1. Call-to-Action</strong></h3>
<p>“That’s a wrap and…fade to logo and now fade to black.”</p>
<p>No! That’s not a wrap. Do NOT just fade to logo to black. You should always have a call to action. This is a traffic and lead-generating tactic that is so often forgotten. This guy just made it through your video, he’s interested, and unfortunately for him, he didn’t find the video on your site, but rather on YouTube. You faded to black and now he’s slipping from your grasp and into the hands of the competition.</p>
<p>CTA possibilities don’t stop there. Pop-ups or references can be included throughout the video. This tactic is especially important if you’re producing a product demo or other type of content for a low-funnel prospect. They’re probably going to be trigger-happy, clicking through various content, so offer them every opportunity to delve deeper through a clear CTA as soon as possible.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a little example:</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nR3nCJIIkjo?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Never bank on them making it all the way through the video, because it’s unlikely. And a strong strategy would include at least three ways for the buyer to reach you: visit the homepage, contact a rep, tweet us, for example.</p>
<h3><strong>2. SEO</strong></h3>
<p>SEO is a monster in today’s marketing world. There’s a lot to it, but with video, here’s one simple thing you can do to help your prospect find the content. Embed the video’s transcript in the meta-data OR launch a blog post to support the video (it’s important not to do both, because Google doesn’t like that!). Suddenly, your video is searchable, and maybe it’s a blog that’s worth not only viewing, but also sharing.</p>
<h3><strong>3. Localization</strong></h3>
<p>This final element speaks primarily to global marketers, but is an excellent way for anyone to grow exposure of video content in regions that your analytics tell you have potential. Translate and provide sub-text for your video as you market in international theaters. But also take the time to apply localized voiceovers and edit some graphics so they are region-specific. You don’t need to produce 12 different videos for 12 different cultures, but taking those extra steps to tailor a current video for a specific region will make an impact.</p>
<h2><strong>ROI</strong></h2>
<p>It’s one thing to produce “good stuff,” but it’s another to create a true asset, equal in beauty and effectiveness. Yes, there are many variables in video marketing: types, styles, formats, budgets, audiences and more. But the “Forgotten Few” should be considered in all cases to keep the conversation flowing, carry the message further, improve ROI, and give the video a reason for being.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The art of illustration in web design</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/15/2014/the-art-of-illustration-in-web-design/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 13:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4135</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I’ve always tried to be an individualist when it comes to design.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I’ve always tried to be an individualist when it comes to design. From the 3-year-old child who drew a giant fish on our family rug while no one was watching, right through to my current status as grey-haired designer, the greatest outlet for this expression of independent thought has been illustration.</p>
<p>For me, the written word felt incomplete at times without an image to support it. Illustration – the visual or pictorial companion to words – helps me understand an idea more completely. It also can be a hook that pulls you into a story.</p>
<p>Makes sense in terms of web design, doesn’t it? But it can be a hard sell. The commercial world’s easy solution is to reach for stock photos and use tidy, linear design. Illustration seems to have been relegated to something that stands for arty-vagueness, abstraction, decoration, and is often seen as risky. But this just isn’t the case, and it’s time for more brands to take a leap.</p>
<h2></h2>
<h2><strong>Top 5</strong></h2>
<p>Not every brand or web design is suited to illustration, but when there is an opportunity, you should try it. Here’s five reasons why.</p>
<h3><strong>1. This time, it’s personal</strong></h3>
<p>In the saturation of samey-samey stock imagery, it’s good to stand out as a personality, as something exclusive. Is your message different? Is your product? Are your people? They should be. And so should your imagery. It is probably easier and cheaper to go with stock imagery or even stock illustration, then add a logo, a tag, some copy, and go live, all in time for dinner. It can be effective and achieve results, but it’s design by numbers, and may leave your brand invisible. What do polished, airbrushed, generic images of fake people give the impression of? You’ve got it! And some other site has it too.</p>
<div id="attachment_4141" style="max-width: 490px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4141" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/k4lab.jpg" alt="http://www.k4lab.info/" width="480" height="320" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/k4lab.jpg 480w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/k4lab-220x146.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://www.k4lab.info/</p></div>
<h3><strong>2. Never underestimate the importance of having fun</strong></h3>
<p>People want to relate to brands, and adding even a hint of playfulness can make you more approachable. Fun, lively imagery can energize a brand, messaging, or copy and make you more exciting. Illustrations can be a joy to create, and the feel-good emotion coming from this process can transfer to the reader/viewer.</p>
<div id="attachment_4142" style="max-width: 625px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4142" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/22.jpg" alt="https://booki.sh/ " width="615" height="429" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/22.jpg 615w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/22-220x153.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 615px) 100vw, 615px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">https://booki.sh/</p></div>
<p>Even using illustrated elements in something as standard as website bios, for example, can add character.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4175" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/cv-biopics-3.jpg" alt="" width="5513" height="2161" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/cv-biopics-3.jpg 5513w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/cv-biopics-3-220x86.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/cv-biopics-3-1024x401.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 5513px) 100vw, 5513px" /></p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4176" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/sean3.jpg" alt="" width="1656" height="2016" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/sean3.jpg 1656w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/sean3-180x220.jpg 180w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/sean3-841x1024.jpg 841w" sizes="(max-width: 1656px) 100vw, 1656px" /><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4177" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/fvm-biopics-3.jpg" alt="Print" width="5004" height="2161" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-biopics-3.jpg 5004w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-biopics-3-220x95.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-biopics-3-1024x442.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 5004px) 100vw, 5004px" /></p>
<p>And fun doesn’t have to mean unsophisticated.</p>
<div id="attachment_4156" style="max-width: 469px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4156" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/537e1f5356d3b.jpeg" alt="http://pioneers.brancottestate.com/" width="459" height="328" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/537e1f5356d3b.jpeg 459w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/537e1f5356d3b-220x157.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 459px) 100vw, 459px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://pioneers.brancottestate.com/</p></div>
<h3><strong>3. We’re engaged!</strong></h3>
<p>In the Internet age our attention spans are shorter, calendars have become more packed, blah, blah, blah. You’ve heard it before, and it’s true. Everyone online has a short amount of time to grab your attention. Make an impact with something unique and interesting that enhances your visibility.</p>
<div id="attachment_4178" style="max-width: 976px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-4178 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Untitled1.png" alt="http://summer.tcm.com/" width="966" height="657" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled1.png 966w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled1-220x149.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 966px) 100vw, 966px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://summer.tcm.com/</p></div>
<div id="attachment_4179" style="max-width: 976px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-4179 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Untitled2.png" alt="http://whiterabbitbeer.com.au/" width="966" height="600" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled2.png 966w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled2-220x136.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 966px) 100vw, 966px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://whiterabbitbeer.com.au/</p></div>
<p>From a more technical perspective, illustration can be more striking by eliminating background distractions and zeroing in on the point. The use of color can influence mood, and a reduced palette can simplify, as it requires less thought from the reader.</p>
<div id="attachment_4146" style="max-width: 467px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4146" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/enjoythis2.jpg" alt="http://enjoythis.co.uk/" width="457" height="250" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/enjoythis2.jpg 457w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/enjoythis2-220x120.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 457px) 100vw, 457px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://enjoythis.co.uk/</p></div>
<h3><strong>4. Beyond boundaries</strong></h3>
<p>With the ability to alter reality, illustration can pique interest. Distorting reality to suit your needs can make people think differently. Your website can be an interactive storybook; your landing page can be its own world; your CEO can be an alien (!). You can truly break the rules, create a different experience, stand apart, and deliver your message in an unconventional way.</p>
<div id="attachment_4145" style="max-width: 469px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4145" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/53e216d80e9f3.jpeg" alt="http://www.rtolymp.ru/" width="459" height="328" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/53e216d80e9f3.jpeg 459w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/53e216d80e9f3-220x157.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 459px) 100vw, 459px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://www.rtolymp.ru/</p></div>
<div id="attachment_4148" style="max-width: 469px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4148" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/537a7426aea97.jpeg" alt="http://www.bevisionare.com/" width="459" height="328" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/537a7426aea97.jpeg 459w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/537a7426aea97-220x157.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 459px) 100vw, 459px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://www.bevisionare.com/</p></div>
<h3><strong>5. Break it down now</strong></h3>
<p>Rather than trying to digest a large expanse of gray copy, people prefer to be given information in colorful, tasty, bite-size pieces. Expressive, creative visualization can help create punctuation and add clarity to even the most complicated messages and technical information. Take something as basic as statistics. In this example, the typography becomes the illustration and survey percentages take center stage, telling the story visually.</p>
<div id="attachment_4153" style="max-width: 2073px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4153" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/CV-cio-data-woes-infographic.jpg" alt="CommVault 'Data Woes' infographic" width="2063" height="4276" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/CV-cio-data-woes-infographic.jpg 2063w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/CV-cio-data-woes-infographic-106x220.jpg 106w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/CV-cio-data-woes-infographic-494x1024.jpg 494w" sizes="(max-width: 2063px) 100vw, 2063px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">CommVault &#8216;Data Woes&#8217; infographic</p></div>
<h2></h2>
<h2><strong>Danger! Hand-crafted</strong></h2>
<p>Clients presented with the idea of illustration are concerned about cost, control, and breaking from the norm. Unless you’re hiring Milton Glazer (not that he’d agree to it, even if you did have the money), there’s no shortage of talent at a reasonable price, who will give the client control, refine until everyone is happy, and produce something memorable that sets the brand apart.</p>
<h2></h2>
<h2><strong>Get the best out of your illustrator</strong></h2>
<p>Still fazed? Don’t be. A good illustrator is only a good illustrator because they’re a good interpreter, so try to have some questions answered and ideas formed before you sit down and open a dialogue. Who is the audience? What message do you want to convey? What do you want people to experience? How do you want them to feel? What is your goal? What are you trying to do? Can the illustration be whimsical or humorous? Can it be a literal representation or an abstraction? Has a precedent been set in terms of color, style, mood, or is it wide open?</p>
<p>Bring examples or a “mood board” of websites, photography, or artwork inspiration.</p>
<p>Once the illustrator has a grasp on what you’re looking for, set them free!</p>
<p>They’ll probably create something that you could never have imagined. It may even inspire other elements such as messaging or logo. What is for certain is that custom illustration will make you more distinctive, recognizable, and memorable. It will make you an individualist.</p>
<p><em>Sources: http://www.awwwards.com/websites/illustration/</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Some humbling stats about banner ads</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/07/2014/some-humbling-stats-about-banner-ads/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4120</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I can count on one hand the number of times I’ve clicked on banner ads in the past year.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I can count on one hand the number of times I’ve clicked on banner ads in the past year. That is to say, once.</p>
<p>If you asked me how many times I’ve clicked on them in the 24 years before that (16 of which have been spent on the internet), that number doesn’t change. And I’m willing to bet that’s one more than most people.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4122" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/apple-ipad-mini-billboard-cursor.jpg" alt="apple ipad mini billboard-cursor" width="1280" height="957" /></p>
<p>I spend a few hours a week writing banner ads, and on joining the agency in the later half of last year, I did some research. One of the first articles I came across was from DigiDay, who had <a href="http://digiday.com/publishers/15-alarming-stats-about-banner-ads/">compiled stats from several studies on just how few people are clicking on banner ads.</a> Here are some of the more striking ones:</p>
<ul>
<li>Over 5.3 trillion display ads were served to U.S. users in 2012</li>
<li>The typical user is served 1,707 banner ads per month. For 25-34 year olds, that number rises to 2,094 per month</li>
<li>Click-through rates are 0.1%</li>
<li>The 468 x 60 banner has a 0.4% CTR</li>
<li>8% of internet users account for 85% of clicks</li>
<li>Up to 50% of clicks on mobile banner ads are accidental</li>
</ul>
<p>In another set of stats, this time from a Solve Media study, the list of things you’re more likely to do than click on a banner ad includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Surviving a plane crash (475.28 times more likely)</li>
<li>Climbing Mount Everest  (279.64x)</li>
<li>Signing up for, and completing Navy SEAL training (112.50x)</li>
<li>Applying to, and getting into Harvard (87.80x)</li>
</ul>
<p>Its research also claimed that clicks on banners <a href="http://www.cmo.com/articles/2012/4/24/banner-ads-past-present-and--future.html">are decreasing every year.</a></p>
<p>For someone just beginning in copywriting for banner ads, these stats were quite worrying. Does my “unique” CTA really make a difference? When I stress over the slide progression in a flash banner, am I just wasting my time? Are banner ads totally ineffective?</p>
<p>I shared my fears with a colleague, who causally rebuffed the significance of those numbers. “I’m guessing they’re consumer stats, and we’re B2B. And everyone knows they’re low. Banner ads aren’t about click-through-rates anyway; they’re about awareness,” she said.</p>
<p>It turns out, she was right. And it inspired me to become a defender of banner ads – the misunderstood, unfairly treated black sheep of the advertising game (not the ones that sit across your screen for 15,14,13, 12 seconds – they’re totally annoying).</p>
<p>Banners are used as an awareness tactic and are unfairly judged on clicks, simply because clicks are track-able. We can’t click on a print, radio, TV or billboard ad, but it doesn’t mean they’re not effective as an overall marketing mix.</p>
<p>They’re awesome for brand recognition, re-targeting, and re-engagement. If they’re targeted properly, which B2B ads are, they provide relevant and helpful content, and can make a big difference to an integrated campaign where paid, earned and owned tactics work together.</p>
<p>So here’s my current philosophy. When I write a banner, it doesn’t matter if it gets clicks of not. That really comes down to whether that person is interested in the product, service, or brand. And even if they are interested, they probably won’t click-through there and then. They may wait a week, or a month, and then search for it directly. What’s important is that these ads are well targeted and seen, because at that point, research has already told us that the message is wanted and needed.</p>
<p>Some have pointed to statistics like the ones above as a portent of <a href="http://techcrunch.com/2009/03/22/why-advertising-is-failing-on-the-internet/">the death of digital advertising</a>. And when you see those terrible, predatory ads that look like they’ll instantly infect your hard drive, it’s easy to see why. While I don’t believe banner ads have any reason to fear the reaper just yet, advertisers should look at the DigiDay stats and be humbled, and inspired to make better ads and improve whatever’s under their control.</p>
<p>What’s under my control is the quality of the copy. To me, that means honest, succinct, well judged, and well written. And if I achieve all those things, I know our designers will make it beautiful, and our B2B marketers will put the ad in the right place at the right time.</p>
<p>The digital world we live in creates a real challenge for banner ads, but if we’re respectful, relevant, and helpful, they’ll tolerate us. If we keep it up, they’ll trust us, and if we don’t exploit that, they’ll dialogue with us.</p>
<p>It might be that I only click on one more ad during the next 24 years of my life, but that doesn’t mean they’re not doing their job.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Programmatic media buying for B2B: the pros and cons</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/07/10/2014/programmatic-media-buying-for-btob-the-pros-and-cons/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 03:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4006</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Not a day goes by that I don’t receive an eNewsletter, LinkedIn discussion or webinar invitation about programmatic media buying &#8211; a form of digital advertising that is processed by machines, rather than humans, to put it simply.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not a day goes by that I don’t receive an eNewsletter, LinkedIn discussion or webinar invitation about programmatic media buying &#8211; a form of digital advertising that is processed by machines, rather than humans, to put it simply.</p>
<ul>
<li>It’s everywhere: A recent study by Winterberry Group found that of 260 executive-level marketers, 91% expect to engage in programmatic within the next two years.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>It’s powerful: Ad Age recently reported that Proctor &amp; Gamble, the world’s biggest media spender, plans to buy 70-75% of its US digital media programmatically by the end of 2014.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>It’s complicated: In a March 2014 Association of National Advertisers (ANA) and Forrester Consulting survey of ANA members, just 28% felt they understood programmatic well enough to use it.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/robot.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4017" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/robot.jpg" alt="robot" width="2684" height="4040" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/robot.jpg 2684w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/robot-146x220.jpg 146w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/robot-680x1024.jpg 680w" sizes="(max-width: 2684px) 100vw, 2684px" /></a></p>
<h2><strong>Programmatic in BtoB</strong></h2>
<p>Programmatic, of course, involves tapping into networks of websites that media providers have organized and distilled based on various audience criteria – mostly identified by previous online browsing behavior patterns like geo-location, age and job function. There&#8217;s no doubt that it suits the wide-open-target-market of retail and consumer product, with its bold claims of huge audience reach across interests, income levels, and billions of available impressions. However, it seems in direct odds with us marketers in the BtoB arena, with our ultra-targeted campaigns delivering complex messages to tiny, niche audiences. The planning that goes into knowing their every want, hope and fear in order to pinpoint when and where to make a meaningful connection can’t possibly make programmatic display advertising a viable tactic, right?</p>
<p>Well, not necessarily so. Through understanding, treading carefully and testing, there can be real value in programmatic for BtoB clients. Here are some pros and cons, based on our experience:</p>
<h2></h2>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>The pros</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Cost</strong></h3>
<p>There’s no doubt that impressions on programmatic can be a more cost-effective option than a direct buy. However, it&#8217;s not just a jump-in-and-play scenario because the audience-matching and ad serving “robots” need funding and time to learn and adjust. In my experience, a spend of around $5k and a campaign length of at least five months – long by BtoB standards – is the minimum needed to allow the machines to adjust to what’s working and what’s not.</p>
<h3><strong>Control</strong></h3>
<p>The buyer is definitely in the driver’s seat. The ability to turn off campaigns and switch out creative at the click of a mouse means you can react to results in real time. But be warned, too much tinkering can be a bad thing because, as mentioned previously, the machines need time to gather results and adjust appropriately. So, sometimes it’s best to let the robots do their thing. After all, even bad results are valuable results.</p>
<h3><strong>Reach</strong></h3>
<p>Programmatic networks offer an unparalleled opportunity to place your message in front of people you’ve never been able to touch before<strong>. </strong>The BtoB marketer lives in fear of the rogue prospect: the guy who doesn’t hang out in all the places you think he should. Some people just don’t play by the rules! The net has no doubt widened with programmatic, and if used to supplement your reach, it might just snare you some rogues.</p>
<h3><strong>Reporting</strong></h3>
<p>We’re seeing some amazing stuff in terms of reporting with programmatic partners, specifically around view-through conversions. Here’s an example: an individual is viewing a page, <em>sees</em> your banner ad but <em>doesn’t </em>click through. Four days later he Googles the offeror company namehe saw, completes the desired action and becomes a success story of your campaign. Programmatic offers the data to give credit where credit’s due – it’s not always the last touch that should get the credit – and proves one thing that we marketers have suspected for years: advertising actually works!</p>
<h2></h2>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>The cons</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Quality</strong></h3>
<p>One concern is that you’re getting remnant inventory – you know, the wide, skinny banner alllll the way at the bottom of the site, sandwiched inside five other ad units. In some cases, this is true. Publishers provide any impressions they haven’t already sold to partners. But this isn’t always the case, and it’s the buyer’s responsibility to check with the vendor and determine exactly what kind of inventory you’re getting.</p>
<h3><strong>Click-throughs</strong></h3>
<p>Low click-through rates (CTRs) can be disconcerting. If you’re new to programmatic and your first report shows CTRs down at 0.02% when you’re used to rates more in the 0.14% to 0.17% range, it can be jarring. However, it’s important to remember that it’s becoming less about CTRs and more about reach (as reported in <a href="http://info.quantcast.com/rs/quantcast/images/Quantcast_Whitepaper_Clicks%20and%20Views.pdf"><em>Display Ad Clickers are Not Your Customers</em></a> by the CEO of Quantcast); connecting with people who may be interested in what you have to say, planting a seed and keeping your message in their peripheral vision.</p>
<h3><strong>Transparency</strong></h3>
<p>Transparency is a biggie for us, and has been the deciding factor to whether or not programmatic can be viable in BtoB buying. On many programmatic networks you are not able to see which sites your banner ads are running on, which can be a huge issue in terms of brand quality control. For example:</p>
<ul>
<li>clients that are sensitive to their messaging running alongside undesirable types of content.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>the context in which your message has to reside in order to engage successfully.</li>
</ul>
<p>After all, you are the company you keep, and to risk a brand’s image or message by using an “open network” is not an option in some cases<strong>.</strong></p>
<p>However, transparent networks do exist and in the IT space especially, we’re seeing great results with progressive publishers who are creating networks of their own site visitor “lookalikes.” They know that we want to widen our net and they understand that in BtoB we need a level of transparency that may differ from retail or consumer marketers. What’s more, they know their audience better than any robot or cookie ever will. These private lists have changed the game for many BtoB marketers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>A place for programmatic</strong></h2>
<p>In the end, and most importantly, the use of programmatic buying comes down to knowing your client, your campaign objectives and how you’re going to judge those objectives. Is it getting as many people as possible to view your client’s message? Is it getting the audience to complete an action, like filling out a form for a piece of content, or registering for an event? If it makes sense and you think programmatic tactics may work, then test and test again.</p>
<p>The bottom line is it’s important to understand programmatic. With improving data, expanding inventory, increased targeting options and management platforms, there’s no doubt that it could play an important role in your future BtoB marketing campaigns. Embrace its benefits because it’s everywhere, it’s powerful and it doesn’t have to be complicated.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
