<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Paul Fleming &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/blog/author/pfleming/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Developing internal culture, while launching an external brand</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/03/08/2017/developing-internal-culture-while-launching-an-external-brand/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 14:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Paul Fleming]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6580</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We’ve enjoyed a great relationship with the Archdiocese of Philadelphia and the Office of Catholic Education for over a decade now — supporting them in the important work they do for the schools, students, and parents across our awesome city and suburbs.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We’ve enjoyed a great relationship with the Archdiocese of Philadelphia and the Office of Catholic Education for over a decade now — supporting them in the important work they do for the schools, students, and parents across our awesome city and suburbs.</p>
<p>The most exciting initiative during this time started in 2015 and continues today; <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/portfolio/aop-schools/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">creating the new Archdiocese of Philadelphia Schools (AOPS) brand</a> and building it out through a new website, outbound, and inbound marketing.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-full wp-image-6599" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/AOPS-logo-1-1.png" alt="" width="796" height="265" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/AOPS-logo-1-1.png 796w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/AOPS-logo-1-1-220x73.png 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/AOPS-logo-1-1-768x256.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 796px) 100vw, 796px" />It’s been a journey of transformation designed to unify our special education, elementary, and secondary schools and advance Catholic education in the area. It began with an internal culture reboot led by <a href="http://www.thepacificinstitute.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Pacific Institute</a> and evolved into an external brand overhaul with FVM. And it’s showing real results for the Arch today.</p>
<p>Here, we share an article on the initiative written by Nick Regina, AOPS Deputy Secretary, Enrollment Management, published in the latest issue of <a href="https://www.ncea.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">National Catholic Educational Association’s (NCEA)</a> magazine, <em>Momentum</em>.</p>
<p><a href="http://read.nxtbook.com/ncea/momentum/2017_winter/index.html#a_lesson_plan_for_developing" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A Lesson Plan for Developing Internal Culture While Launching an External Brand</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pleasure in the Job</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/20/2013/pleasure-in-the-job/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 15:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Paul Fleming]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3265</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I recently visited the hallowed ground of Gettysburg to sustain my lifelong interest in the Civil War, and that historic battle in particular.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I recently visited the hallowed ground of Gettysburg to sustain my lifelong interest in the Civil War, and that historic battle in particular.  My wife Judy accompanied me. While my spouse doesn’t share my passion for the tactics of the battle, she thrives on the human interest angle––hearing personal stories of the soldiers and citizens who participated in that critical turning point of the Civil War.  In fact, Judy suggested the trip.</p>
<p>To get the most out of our visit I suggested that we hire a licensed guide to tour the battlefield with us and interpret the 3-day conflict.  His name was Bruce and he inspired us.</p>
<p>Historical perspective aside, the lasting impression I will have from the two hours we spent with our veteran guide was the intensity he brought to his assignment.  Nearly every day of the year, for countless groups and individuals, this man delivers an historic account of the battle.  You could argue that this daily grind could become somewhat of a routine.  After all, he’s been doing it for almost ten years.  But Bruce made us feel like he had something significant to share and that we were an equally special audience.  He was passionate and he was patient.  He listened well and made us feel important.  This guy loved his job.</p>
<p>For Judy he brought clarity to three profound days in July, 1863.  For me, he ignited a fire.  Heading home, I found myself thinking again about the enthusiasm our tour guide displayed for his craft.  It made me think about my own career, and how grateful I am that I love what I do.  I’m equally indebted to our FVM employees––abundantly talented people who could easily go through the motions but instead, like Bruce, bring passion and zeal to every assignment, regardless of size or scope.  Aristotle said, “Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work.”  That sentiment rings true on a 150 year-old battlefield and still resonates every day back in Plymouth Meeting, Pennsylvania.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Introducing Our Newest Client&#8230; Us!</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/11/05/2013/introducing-our-newest-client-us/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Paul Fleming]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3205</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Many of us have shared the old saying, “the son of the shoemaker has no shoes” (“the cobbler’s children go unshod” for those purists out there).]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many of us have shared the old saying, “the son of the shoemaker has no shoes” (“the cobbler’s children go unshod” for those purists out there). The spirit of either phrase is that we spend so much time passionately tending to the needs of others that we sometimes forget our own responsibilities.</p>
<p>Here at FVM, nothing was more illustrative of that mindset than the marketing needs of our own agency. Well-intentioned employees with outstanding creative talents “dabbled” with our communications challenges while they delivered magic for our clients.  The disparity was glaringly obvious.</p>
<p>All of the principles and passion we apply to every client, regardless of size or budget, were missing when it came to our own communications goals &#8212; until this year.  That’s when FVM hired FVM, where every day is an adventure in helping clients communicate creatively, powerfully, and, most of all, strategically.</p>
<p>One outstanding result of this holistic, integrated approach is a brand new FVM web site that rarely saw the back burner during its development. Beyond its aesthetic appeal, it hopefully tells our story, showcases our talents and capabilities, highlights some of our work, and keeps you coming back for more.  In a nutshell, I think we have a pretty nice pair of shoes for the journey ahead.</p>
<p>I’d love to <a href="mailto:*protected email*">hear what you think</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This word is killing your grade</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/08/2013/this-word-is-killing-your-grade/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 11:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Paul Fleming]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3025</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The word was “occurred.” Even today, I hesitate as I carefully consider its correct spelling.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The word was “occurred.” Even today, I hesitate as I carefully consider its correct spelling.</p>
<p>In 1977, I was an aspiring journalism student at Temple University in Philadelphia. Incredibly gifted and passionate teachers who demanded the very best from their students staffed the faculty in Temple’s School of Communications and Theatre. Among those professors was Dr. John Lent, who taught a “History of Journalism” class. One of his assignments was to research an historic figure in journalism, write a comprehensive paper, and deliver an oral report. In turn, we would receive two grades – one for written content and one for the public speaking component.</p>
<p>Dr. Lent presented the ground rules very clearly. True to form, he stressed that spelling errors in the report would not be tolerated. His reasoning was clear. If we wanted to be communications professionals then we needed to develop a proper respect for the written word. This included proofreading our material and delivering grammatically correct work that was flawless. Unfortunately, his mandate to the class failed to resonate with this 20-year old who instead would have to learn a career-defining lesson.</p>
<p>I chose to research newspaperman Joseph Pulitzer. I took the assignment seriously, wrote a comprehensive paper, and made my presentation to the class. I was pretty confident about my performance. Dr. Lent must have agreed. He gave me an A on the spot for my public speaking. A few days letter he returned my written report.</p>
<p>I gazed at the clean sheet of double spaced type on page one – now interrupted by a single word circled in red. I was in trouble. Page two &#8211;the same word was circled again. Serious trouble. The third time, that all too familiar word was accompanied by knee-buckling pithy commentary from my professor, “this word is killing your grade.”</p>
<p>That word was ”occurred.” I managed to misspell it three separate times. Grade killer? Yes, he gave me an F. But over time, that lousy grade nurtured a wake-up call that reintroduced me to Dr. Lent’s demand for excellence. Today, three-plus decades later that passion has not dimmed. Even my text messages lack the typical acronyms, abbreviations and deliberately omitted punctuation that define today’s cryptic communications. Sure, my GPA took a massive hit from Dr. Lent’s harsh lesson, but it was a small price to pay to appreciate true zeal for the written word and ultimate respect for our craft.</p>
<p>Occurred.</p>
<p>O-C-C-U-R-R -E-D</p>
<p>Occurred.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
