<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Karen Murphy &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/blog/author/kmurphy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Social media advertising: Extending your targeted reach</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/04/2015/social-media-advertising-extending-your-targeted-reach/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 08:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5133</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[LinkedIn, Twitter and Facebook are still babies.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LinkedIn, Twitter and Facebook are still babies. Not even teenagers. Social media appeared quickly. It was fun, but hard to trust, as your favorite platforms disappeared just as quickly as they had arrived (I’m looking at you, Friendster). Many wrote it off as a passing fad; some market trend that would people would tire of eventually. And few early adopters would have seen its business potential.</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-5202 size-full alignright" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/social.jpg" alt="social" width="810" height="470" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/social.jpg 810w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/social-220x128.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 810px) 100vw, 810px" /></p>
<p>But growth continued, advertising opportunities were created and in 2014 social media advertising spend hit <a href="http://www.emarketer.com/Article/Social-Network-Ad-Spending-Hit-2368-Billion-Worldwide-2015/1012357" target="_blank">$7.71BN in N. America; 56% growth on the previous year. This year it’s predicted to break $10BN, and by 2017 it will smash $15BN</a>. Why? Because ad dollars follow eyeballs; one third of the world’s internet users are on Facebook. And because social platforms harness incredible data to identify a myriad of audiences to target.</p>
<p>Yes, social media’s a great way to share helpful content, inform and engage followers, and keep your organization top of mind as a thought leader. It’s been this for a while, and improves almost on a monthly basis. LinkedIn, for example, continues to grow as it transforms from social network to B2B content publishing platform.</p>
<p>But here’s a thing; organic reach is not what it once was. As of a couple of years ago, Facebook updated its algorithm so brand page posts became more “relevant.” Or less visible, in that not even <em>all</em> followers see updates. That equals fewer interactions, leads and customers.</p>
<p>Even if all of your posts<em> were</em> visible to your entire follower base, you’d still only reach people who already know and like you enough to have hit your “follow” button at some point. Preaching to the choir, you could argue.</p>
<p>More than ever, utilizing social media’s real power lies in advertising and reach <em>outside</em> your follower-base. Here are a few reasons why.</p>
<p><strong>Killer targeting</strong></p>
<p>The targeting capabilities within social media advertising are simply unparalleled and go deeper than any other online digital platform. What it all means is that marketers have the opportunity to increase an ad’s relevance to users, and to know that certain demographics will receive the ad.</p>
<p>Facebook ads allow marketers to target by geography, interests, behaviors, and parental status (even expectant parents!). Twitter offers advertisers targets based on who they follow—your competitors, industry publications, or market analysts, perhaps. The possibilities are pretty much endless. But here’s how they break down:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Interests/Skills<br />
</strong>Social users share—it’s what they do. The nature of the beast. With every self-reported skill or interest or engagement, users identify themselves as a certain audience, and one that can be targeted. LinkedIn—the world’s largest professional network—has <a href="https://press.linkedin.com/about-linkedin" target="_blank">115million users in the US (364million globally)</a> and aims to reach <a href="http://venturebeat.com/2013/10/23/linkedin-ceo-by-next-year-50-of-our-traffic-will-be-mobile/" target="_blank">3 billion</a> in the long-term, with the vast majority offering their industry, job title, employer, skills and location. Every B2B marketer’s dream.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Behavioral/Connections<br />
</strong>With every purchase made, device utilized, page liked, app used, group joined or event attended, Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn are analyzing continued behavior and intent. Think retargeting, but nicely packaged up in social. While search is reactive, this kind of targeting is proactive.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Custom/Tailored<br />
</strong>Great data exists outside of social media too, of course. If you have email addresses, phone numbers or other user IDs, Twitter and Facebook will take them, match them to users and advertise directly.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Lookalikes<br />
</strong>LinkedIn and Facebook know your audience’s doppelganger. If a business has served ads to all custom audiences and is looking for greater reach, where is there left to go? Well, based on that data, the platforms will identify and generate similar, relevant audiences who “look like” your existing ones.</li>
</ul>
<p>So the targeting’s awesome, but what else is there to think about?</p>
<p><strong>Conversion tracking</strong><br />
Conversions are the Holy Grail in media campaigns. Driving a user to act in a certain way—signing up for a webinar or buying something, for example—is a conversion, and essential to measure for performance and proving your ad’s value.</p>
<p>It’s always been possible for marketers to measure certain metrics through their own sites, but social media has upped its game with conversion tracking. While it’s possible to track social interactions by setting up Goals in Google Analytics, the level of detail pales in comparison to the insights offered by the social networks themselves. Now you can attribute conversions on your site to social ads in real time—allowing you to adjust and optimize where needed.<strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>Modest budgets welcome</strong></p>
<p>Small budgets can get eaten up quickly when using a cost per thousand impression (CPM) bid strategy on the Google Display Network and other similar platforms, but almost all social media platforms offer pay-per-click options. The PPC model means marketers with all sizes of budget can start reaching their target social audience straight away. Not to mention the insights gained from a small PPC test. Which job title responded to my ads the most? Which headline was the attention-grabber? The answers are here, and they won’t break the bank.</p>
<p><strong>Going mobile</strong></p>
<p>Social media and mobile are smitten. The power couple continues to create new audiences, expand reach and generate more ad opportunities.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.cio.com/article/2453934/social-media/mobile-advertising-will-dominate-social-networks.html" target="_blank">Facebook and Twitter are two of the three biggest players in mobile advertising in the U.S.</a> (the other’s Google (not Google+)). That’s right, Facebook made <a href="http://investor.fb.com/releasedetail.cfm?ReleaseID=908022" target="_blank">$3.32 billion in Q1 2015</a> and almost three-quarters of that revenue came from mobile advertising—meaning they control over <a href="http://www.cio.com/article/2453934/social-media/mobile-advertising-will-dominate-social-networks.html" target="_blank">70% of all social ad spend</a>. Twitter announced a <a href="https://investor.twitterinc.com/releasedetail.cfm?releaseid=909177" target="_blank">Q1 2015 ad revenue of $388 million</a> with mobile ads accounting for 89% of total ad revenue—a 72% jump from last year.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.emarketer.com/Article/2-Billion-Consumers-Worldwide-Smartphones-by-2016/1011694" target="_blank">It’s estimated that over a third (2.56Bn) of the world’s population will have a smartphone by 2018</a>. <a href="http://www.businessinsider.com/chart-of-the-day-americans-spend-more-time-using-mobile-devices-than-tv-2014-11" target="_blank">Having already overtaken desktop browsing and TV viewing hours in the U.S.</a>, mobile advertising now represents the best opportunity to reach people going about their daily lives, and social is leading that charge. <strong><br />
</strong></p>
<p><strong>Know your audience</strong></p>
<p>Engaging with followers and targeting the right people is what it’s all about. But it’s important not to lose sight of the fact that you must <em>first</em> know that audience inside and out. Social media sites are most likely one place they hang out, but where else do they spend their time—online and offline? What kinds of offers appeal to them? What types of keywords are they searching?</p>
<p>Marketers who take a one-shot approach with Facebook advertising, for example, and say it failed, are taking too narrow of a view. Social media advertising needs to be just one avenue to reach your prospect base and part of a larger marketing communications strategy.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Programmatic media buying for B2B: the pros and cons</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/07/10/2014/programmatic-media-buying-for-btob-the-pros-and-cons/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 03:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4006</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Not a day goes by that I don’t receive an eNewsletter, LinkedIn discussion or webinar invitation about programmatic media buying &#8211; a form of digital advertising that is processed by machines, rather than humans, to put it simply.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not a day goes by that I don’t receive an eNewsletter, LinkedIn discussion or webinar invitation about programmatic media buying &#8211; a form of digital advertising that is processed by machines, rather than humans, to put it simply.</p>
<ul>
<li>It’s everywhere: A recent study by Winterberry Group found that of 260 executive-level marketers, 91% expect to engage in programmatic within the next two years.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>It’s powerful: Ad Age recently reported that Proctor &amp; Gamble, the world’s biggest media spender, plans to buy 70-75% of its US digital media programmatically by the end of 2014.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>It’s complicated: In a March 2014 Association of National Advertisers (ANA) and Forrester Consulting survey of ANA members, just 28% felt they understood programmatic well enough to use it.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/robot.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4017" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/robot.jpg" alt="robot" width="2684" height="4040" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/robot.jpg 2684w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/robot-146x220.jpg 146w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/robot-680x1024.jpg 680w" sizes="(max-width: 2684px) 100vw, 2684px" /></a></p>
<h2><strong>Programmatic in BtoB</strong></h2>
<p>Programmatic, of course, involves tapping into networks of websites that media providers have organized and distilled based on various audience criteria – mostly identified by previous online browsing behavior patterns like geo-location, age and job function. There&#8217;s no doubt that it suits the wide-open-target-market of retail and consumer product, with its bold claims of huge audience reach across interests, income levels, and billions of available impressions. However, it seems in direct odds with us marketers in the BtoB arena, with our ultra-targeted campaigns delivering complex messages to tiny, niche audiences. The planning that goes into knowing their every want, hope and fear in order to pinpoint when and where to make a meaningful connection can’t possibly make programmatic display advertising a viable tactic, right?</p>
<p>Well, not necessarily so. Through understanding, treading carefully and testing, there can be real value in programmatic for BtoB clients. Here are some pros and cons, based on our experience:</p>
<h2></h2>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>The pros</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Cost</strong></h3>
<p>There’s no doubt that impressions on programmatic can be a more cost-effective option than a direct buy. However, it&#8217;s not just a jump-in-and-play scenario because the audience-matching and ad serving “robots” need funding and time to learn and adjust. In my experience, a spend of around $5k and a campaign length of at least five months – long by BtoB standards – is the minimum needed to allow the machines to adjust to what’s working and what’s not.</p>
<h3><strong>Control</strong></h3>
<p>The buyer is definitely in the driver’s seat. The ability to turn off campaigns and switch out creative at the click of a mouse means you can react to results in real time. But be warned, too much tinkering can be a bad thing because, as mentioned previously, the machines need time to gather results and adjust appropriately. So, sometimes it’s best to let the robots do their thing. After all, even bad results are valuable results.</p>
<h3><strong>Reach</strong></h3>
<p>Programmatic networks offer an unparalleled opportunity to place your message in front of people you’ve never been able to touch before<strong>. </strong>The BtoB marketer lives in fear of the rogue prospect: the guy who doesn’t hang out in all the places you think he should. Some people just don’t play by the rules! The net has no doubt widened with programmatic, and if used to supplement your reach, it might just snare you some rogues.</p>
<h3><strong>Reporting</strong></h3>
<p>We’re seeing some amazing stuff in terms of reporting with programmatic partners, specifically around view-through conversions. Here’s an example: an individual is viewing a page, <em>sees</em> your banner ad but <em>doesn’t </em>click through. Four days later he Googles the offeror company namehe saw, completes the desired action and becomes a success story of your campaign. Programmatic offers the data to give credit where credit’s due – it’s not always the last touch that should get the credit – and proves one thing that we marketers have suspected for years: advertising actually works!</p>
<h2></h2>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>The cons</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Quality</strong></h3>
<p>One concern is that you’re getting remnant inventory – you know, the wide, skinny banner alllll the way at the bottom of the site, sandwiched inside five other ad units. In some cases, this is true. Publishers provide any impressions they haven’t already sold to partners. But this isn’t always the case, and it’s the buyer’s responsibility to check with the vendor and determine exactly what kind of inventory you’re getting.</p>
<h3><strong>Click-throughs</strong></h3>
<p>Low click-through rates (CTRs) can be disconcerting. If you’re new to programmatic and your first report shows CTRs down at 0.02% when you’re used to rates more in the 0.14% to 0.17% range, it can be jarring. However, it’s important to remember that it’s becoming less about CTRs and more about reach (as reported in <a href="http://info.quantcast.com/rs/quantcast/images/Quantcast_Whitepaper_Clicks%20and%20Views.pdf"><em>Display Ad Clickers are Not Your Customers</em></a> by the CEO of Quantcast); connecting with people who may be interested in what you have to say, planting a seed and keeping your message in their peripheral vision.</p>
<h3><strong>Transparency</strong></h3>
<p>Transparency is a biggie for us, and has been the deciding factor to whether or not programmatic can be viable in BtoB buying. On many programmatic networks you are not able to see which sites your banner ads are running on, which can be a huge issue in terms of brand quality control. For example:</p>
<ul>
<li>clients that are sensitive to their messaging running alongside undesirable types of content.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>the context in which your message has to reside in order to engage successfully.</li>
</ul>
<p>After all, you are the company you keep, and to risk a brand’s image or message by using an “open network” is not an option in some cases<strong>.</strong></p>
<p>However, transparent networks do exist and in the IT space especially, we’re seeing great results with progressive publishers who are creating networks of their own site visitor “lookalikes.” They know that we want to widen our net and they understand that in BtoB we need a level of transparency that may differ from retail or consumer marketers. What’s more, they know their audience better than any robot or cookie ever will. These private lists have changed the game for many BtoB marketers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>A place for programmatic</strong></h2>
<p>In the end, and most importantly, the use of programmatic buying comes down to knowing your client, your campaign objectives and how you’re going to judge those objectives. Is it getting as many people as possible to view your client’s message? Is it getting the audience to complete an action, like filling out a form for a piece of content, or registering for an event? If it makes sense and you think programmatic tactics may work, then test and test again.</p>
<p>The bottom line is it’s important to understand programmatic. With improving data, expanding inventory, increased targeting options and management platforms, there’s no doubt that it could play an important role in your future BtoB marketing campaigns. Embrace its benefits because it’s everywhere, it’s powerful and it doesn’t have to be complicated.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 5 reasons why working at a suburban agency is awesome</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/04/24/2014/top-5-reasons-why-working-at-a-suburban-agency-is-awesome/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 14:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3772</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s easy to turn your nose up at a small agency in the burbs.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s easy to turn your nose up at a small agency in the burbs. Living outside of the sphere of the center city &#8220;hustle and bustle,&#8221; with big tall buildings, smart-looking people zipping from place to place, trendy shops, eateries and galleries&#8230;.what&#8217;s to love about the safe, predictable old suburbs?  Coming from a gal who was born and raised in the city of Philadelphia &#8211; more than you may think.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve compiled a little list of pros of working at a suburban agency&#8230;and after reviewing it, I’m realizing something – it’s a pretty awesome place to be.</p>
<p><strong>5. Parking</strong>. I&#8217;ve never had to worry once about getting a parking spot at work, my car getting towed for parking in the wrong zone, or paying a fee to park. (Am I always confident that my car will start? Ok maybe not. But at least I know it will be sitting there where I left it!)</p>
<p><strong> </strong><strong>4. Beautiful landscapes</strong>. On my morning stroll into our office building (ok, brisk shuffle), especially this time of year, I am greeted with blooming trees, lovely landscaped gardens, fresh clean air, fragrant flowers&#8230;.ahhh. No better way to start your workday.</p>
<p><strong>3. Decent restaurant options.</strong> This might not apply for all suburban agencies, but we are fortunate enough to be located across the road from a shopping mall surrounded by a nice selection of drama-free restaurants to meet with clients, publishers, etc. Feel like some fancy pizza? Hibachi?  Smoked brisket with amazing corn bread?  We&#8217;ve got it all across the street, just walk right in.</p>
<p><strong>2. Ego-free zone.</strong> Absolutely nothing against downtown agencies, and I&#8217;m just speaking from my own limited experience with our own agency folk here&#8230;.but the people who work here are just, well, nice. They are not here to climb a corporate ladder or to look cool to their friends. They are here to do great work, and have fun doing it. And I don&#8217;t know, I get the sense that our unassuming suburban location might have something to do with that.</p>
<p><strong>1. Geese crossings.</strong> Anyone who knows me well will likely be shocked at this one. (That&#8217;s assuming they read this blog. Let’s be honest, it&#8217;ll probably just Alex.)  Because I. Hate. Birds. However&#8230;I find it so amusing that once every few weeks, I&#8217;ll be driving around our office building, and must come to a dead screeching halt in order to allow a little pack of strutting Canadian geese to slowly cross in front of my car. How can you not laugh out loud, or at least smile, at these quirky creatures who are so completely oblivious to all of us office workers and our needs to get somewhere?  You just have to sit there while they make their way across the parking lot, sometimes honking at each other or just looking around the world around them as they strut.</p>
<p>So there you have it! Agree or disagree, I&#8217;ve discovered some unexpected charms with FVM’s little place in the world. For all its cons, our office location in Plymouth meeting, PA….is pretty awesome.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>So, I&#8217;m a Marketing Nerd!</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/20/2014/so-im-a-marketing-nerd/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 14:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deadliest Catch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TLC]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3300</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[While watching Deadliest Catch on the Discovery Channel with my husband one night a few months ago, I started noticing a pattern.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While watching <i>Deadliest Catch</i> on the Discovery Channel with my husband one night a few months ago, I started noticing a pattern. During every commercial break, we were assaulted with commercials for men’s products: Ford F-150 pickup trucks, razors with four blades for a closer shave, Slim Jims–the list goes on.</p>
<p>I laughed out loud and said, &#8220;Oh man, I guess I&#8217;m not in the target market for <i>this </i>show. I love when that happens! I feel like I&#8217;m beating the system!&#8221; I expected my husband to chuckle and agree. Instead, he looked at me like I had three heads and said, &#8220;What?&#8221;</p>
<p>I realized, then, that not everybody in the world notices or pays attention when they&#8217;re being marketed to. For the first time, I felt special as a professional working in marketing.  Over the next few weeks I noticed that I really do find it fun to determine if I am inside or outside the target market for the products or services I&#8217;m being marketed.</p>
<p>Here are a few examples:</p>
<ul>
<li>On a random weekday home sick, I was watching <i>The Price is Right</i> on CBS. Denture cleaner–Nope!  Nice try, marketers, but thankfully I have all my teeth!  Scooter Store–Nope!  Emergency Life Alert button–Nope!  Pampers Cruisers diapers…OK, you got me on that one.  Touché, marketers.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Checking my Email: Groupon to Niagra Falls–Nope!  Adidas Men&#8217;s Golf Shoes–Nope!  50% off on preschool portraits…wait, let me see that one.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Watching <i>What Not to Wear</i> on TLC, while folding laundry on a Saturday afternoon: OK, I admit, I am 100% in the center circle of TLC&#8217;s target market diagram.  Whatever I see a commercial for, I want to buy, to watch, to check out.  Way to go, TLC, you found me!</li>
</ul>
<p>Marketers have a different way of looking at the world–of breaking down human behavior and trying to understand, at the core, what moves and motivates people. I am happy to consider myself part of this group of professionals. I feel at home in this little world because it&#8217;s really interesting to me. I am also happy that I&#8217;m not tasked with advertising to smart-ass marketers like myself!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Great news for the good online marketers out there</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/14/2013/great-news-for-the-good-online-marketers-out-there/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 15:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[campaign reporting & analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3064</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Although I&#8217;m only halfway through a MarketingProfs University &#8220;Search Marketing School&#8221; online seminar (5 courses down, 5 to go!), the overall theme is already becoming very clear: with its newest SEO updates, Google is attempting to penalize over-optimized websites, and reward sites that are user-friendly, nicely designed, and stocked with helpful information for customers and [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although I&#8217;m only halfway through a MarketingProfs University &#8220;Search Marketing School&#8221; online seminar (5 courses down, 5 to go!), the overall theme is already becoming very clear: with its newest SEO updates, Google is attempting to penalize over-optimized websites, and reward sites that are user-friendly, nicely designed, and stocked with helpful information for customers and prospects.</p>
<p>Yay for common-sense marketing to humans! Boo for back-end Search Engine Optimization trickery!</p>
<p>From what I&#8217;m learning, less emphasis is being placed on excessive link building, keyword stuffing, and meaningless irrelevant content. Instead, things like a quick site load time; a friendly mobile experience; useful, timely multi-media content; quality links; and a strong social presence matter more.</p>
<p>So, if you&#8217;ve been trying to &#8220;do it right&#8221; all along by creating a user-friendly, nicely designed website that attempts to offer customers and potential customers helpful information – you’re in luck! Way to go, Google.</p>
<p>Of course, the basic structural back-end geeky web stuff, like proper meta-tagging, 301 redirects, and HTML site maps are still very necessary. (Do you like how I threw those terms around? Lucky for me, I have our awesome web team on hand to translate into English.)</p>
<p>Next on the list: FINISH the online seminar. Perhaps I&#8217;ll come across some more interesting nuggets to share from the next five courses.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Work/life balance and proud of it</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/11/2013/worklife-balance-and-proud-of-it/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 14:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3061</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[As a working mom, an article in my LinkedIn news feed immediately caught my eye.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As a working mom, an <a href="http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20121211003923-174077701-big-idea-2013-flexibility-without-shame" target="_blank">article in my LinkedIn news feed</a> immediately caught my eye.</p>
<p>Article writer Sallie Krawcheck, former president of the Global Wealth &amp; Investment Management division of Bank of America, illuminated an alarming (but not surprising) fact:</p>
<p><em>Working women who choose to have children are breaking into two broad groups: one works full-time, holding on, exhausted, through their children’s younger years. A full 60% (!) of these moms wish they had a flexible work option. And the other group – 5.4 million of them – steps out of the workforce during those years &#8230; and pays the economic price. On trying to re-enter, 73% report trouble finding a job; and those who successfully do so suffer precipitous drops in income.</em></p>
<p>Sallie goes on to suggest that smart companies will start offering &#8220;flexibility without shame,&#8221; recognizing that certain times in employees&#8217; lives are more trying than others and require different &#8220;workstyles.&#8221; This need for flexibility doesn&#8217;t mean those employees are any less dedicated to their careers.</p>
<p>This particular topic is one thing I have always loved about working at FVM. It&#8217;s clear that this place values its employees, and is willing to enable flexible work hours to make life easier. As long as the work is getting done, and the client is getting the results they expect and deserve, the agency partners are open to non-traditional arrangements (within reason, of course!).</p>
<p>I consider myself lucky to have an extra half hour in the morning to get my 3 year old and 1 year old boys&#8217; day off to a calmer, happier start. Compare my mornings now with when my work day started at 9, and I found myself losing patience and screaming, &#8220;YOU ARE MAKING ME LATE!!&#8221; at a toddler who was feeling great pains and exhibiting desperate behavior at the thought of putting on pants. (I get it, Tom, I like shorts better, too.)</p>
<p>I can now, on weekday mornings, calmly look at the clock approaching 8:30, and handle the pants tantrum with more patience. Not going to lie, we still struggle with clothing choices on some days, but my toddler now has a much saner mom who can work through the issue at hand. And for that, FVM, I am eternally grateful.</p>
<p>Hopefully more companies start recognizing that enabling employees to work flexibly during parts of their careers is a smart long-term investment. It will make for a world filled with happy toddlers wearing seasonal-appropriate clothing, and moms who can start their workdays without tears.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
