<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>web development &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/web-development/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Cross-browser testing: how to live with Internet Explorer</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/24/2014/cross-browser-testing/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 15:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4251</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Ask a group of web designers what they think of Internet Explorer and you&#8217;ll get a fair share of groans.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ask a group of web designers what they think of Internet Explorer and you&#8217;ll get a fair share of groans. Most will grumble about CSS hacks and quasi-transparency support, and the rest will make hilarious jokes like &#8220;Internet Explorer is only good for downloading other browsers.&#8221;</p>
<p>What&#8217;s really at the heart of all this hostility—to a once industry-leading product—is simply the aggravation of writing code that isn&#8217;t always accepted by all browsers (and the need to have to troubleshoot in so many different potential environments).</p>
<p>While there are <a href="http://www.w3.org/standards/webdesign/htmlcss" target="_blank">HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Mobile</a> coding standards, a browser that doesn&#8217;t support the new &#8220;whiz bang&#8221; techniques becomes a headache for designers (think transparency and rounded corners). On top of that, the user experience that morphs from a desktop hit to a mobile hit can dramatically alter the performance of a website (much like drop down menus and hover effects on touch screen devices).</p>
<h3>The Players</h3>
<p>We&#8217;ve gone from a world in which everyone used Netscape to steal Metallica MP3s, to one in which a user&#8217;s browser may change as they transition from their desk to their car to their couch. Even if you could control what browsers people use, it&#8217;s nearly impossible to control what versions they have (or have not) updated to. In fact, it has become such a problem that a few big names have launched <a href="https://www.modern.ie/en-us/ie6countdown" target="_blank">campaigns to stop using their own products</a>. There&#8217;s just no guarantee which browser your visitors will be viewing your content in, so you need to optimize for them all.</p>
<p>At ThinkFVM.com, we see that our visitors use the usual suspects:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-4256 size-full alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM.png" alt="FVM Browsers by Type" width="822" height="532" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM.png 822w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM-220x142.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 822px) 100vw, 822px" /></a></p>
<p>A full 15% of our visitors are on IE, which immediately raises flags. Will all of them be able to handle our Parallax? Do we have border radius styles that are going to look good when they&#8217;re downgraded? How many of these visitors are using versions of IE that can&#8217;t handle background sizing?</p>
<p>So, since Internet Explorer is the biggest culprit in behind-the-times-itis, we usually keep an eye on visitors&#8217; IE browsers:</p>
<div id="attachment_4257" style="max-width: 825px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-4257 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM.png" alt="FVM Browsers by IE Version" width="815" height="522" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM.png 815w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM-220x140.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 815px) 100vw, 815px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text"><em>Seriously? There are still IE6 users out there?</em></p></div>
<p>Right out of the gate we know that almost 8% of our visitors have IE8 or earlier. Those are the biggest culprits we&#8217;re seeing today, and to them, our website may not look as spectacular as we intended it to. We&#8217;re used to this and we incorporate that thinking into our concepts, but we don&#8217;t always want to sacrifice design for a troubled few. So we build what we want to and test accordingly. However, short of owning a 1980s-esque room full of computers and outdated operating software, what&#8217;s a coder to do?</p>
<p>Well, there are tools to help us out.</p>
<h3>The Solution</h3>
<p>Our personal favorite browser testing website is <a href="http://www.crossbrowsertesting.com" target="_blank">CrossBrowserTesting.com</a>. We joined this subscription-based service when it first launched, at a time when coders were lost for quality tools, and it has grown with the market ever since. Although no matter which browser testing software you use—<a href="http://www.browserstack.com/" target="_blank">BrowserStack</a>, <a href="https://saucelabs.com/" target="_blank">SauceLabs</a>, <a href="http://browsershots.org/" target="_blank">BrowserShots</a>, <a href="http://www.ranorex.com/blog/cross-browser-test-automation" target="_blank">Ranorex</a>, and <a href="http://smartbear.com/products/qa-tools/automated-testing-tools/" target="_blank">SmartBear</a> all have their own products—the tools are straightforward: plug in a URL and see how pages are rendered on the screen, in various browsers, and in multiple operating systems.</p>
<p>CrossBrowserTesting.com offers two methods for its troubleshooting: screenshots and live tests. We typically run all new websites and landing pages through the screenshots application, running IE7-IE11, a current and legacy version of Firefox, Chrome, Opera, and even iOS and Android mobile browsers. With a few clicks, we can test each layout design and check back later to compile a punch list of CSS miscreants.</p>
<p>If there are any active elements on the page—say scrolling marquees, dynamic drop down lists, or unique hover states—we can click from the screenshot result to view a live test of the website. This also helps when troubleshooting a CSS fix to make sure it was effective.</p>
<h3>Use Case In Action</h3>
<p>When we built our website, we took advantage of full-bleed images, which came at a cost to lesser capable browsers. We knew that IE8 and 7 did not support the background-width property, so we started right out with a failsafe image placement. Still, our website looked like this:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1.png" class="swipebox"><img class="alignleft wp-image-4279 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1.png" alt="Screen Shot 2014-09-24 at 1.46.33 PM" width="973" height="710" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1.png 973w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1-220x160.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 973px) 100vw, 973px" /></a></p>
<p>IE 9, 10, and 11 look great, as does IE7. IE8 however, doesn&#8217;t scale the background image properly, and the failsafe image that IE7 displays isn&#8217;t rendering in IE8 like it should. <em>Sorry to our one user who visits in IE6, but we don&#8217;t bother testing for that browser anymore. You need to upgrade!</em></p>
<p>Yeesh. Luckily we ran into this problem before and implemented an easy <a href="https://github.com/louisremi/background-size-polyfill" target="_blank">hack</a>.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1.png" class="swipebox"><img class="alignleft wp-image-4281 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1.png" alt="Screen Shot 2014-09-24 at 2.17.10 PM" width="968" height="679" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1.png 968w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1-220x154.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 968px) 100vw, 968px" /></a></p>
<p>Now, our pages look as uniform as they can be. Sure, the transparent black behind our bios is nicer than the solid grey, but that&#8217;s life. There&#8217;s probably a transparency hack out there somewhere, but the design didn&#8217;t warrant the extra scripting for the expected payout. The point is that no matter what browser a visitor uses to view your website, they can still view the website. And, with the cross-browser testing tools that we have at our disposal, we didn&#8217;t spend a lot of time guaranteeing a uniform user experience.</p>
<p>After all, we have a lot of <a href="https://www.facebook.com/video.php?v=530140273781498" target="_blank">other stuff going on</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Great news for the good online marketers out there</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/14/2013/great-news-for-the-good-online-marketers-out-there/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 15:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[campaign reporting & analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3064</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Although I&#8217;m only halfway through a MarketingProfs University &#8220;Search Marketing School&#8221; online seminar (5 courses down, 5 to go!), the overall theme is already becoming very clear: with its newest SEO updates, Google is attempting to penalize over-optimized websites, and reward sites that are user-friendly, nicely designed, and stocked with helpful information for customers and [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although I&#8217;m only halfway through a MarketingProfs University &#8220;Search Marketing School&#8221; online seminar (5 courses down, 5 to go!), the overall theme is already becoming very clear: with its newest SEO updates, Google is attempting to penalize over-optimized websites, and reward sites that are user-friendly, nicely designed, and stocked with helpful information for customers and prospects.</p>
<p>Yay for common-sense marketing to humans! Boo for back-end Search Engine Optimization trickery!</p>
<p>From what I&#8217;m learning, less emphasis is being placed on excessive link building, keyword stuffing, and meaningless irrelevant content. Instead, things like a quick site load time; a friendly mobile experience; useful, timely multi-media content; quality links; and a strong social presence matter more.</p>
<p>So, if you&#8217;ve been trying to &#8220;do it right&#8221; all along by creating a user-friendly, nicely designed website that attempts to offer customers and potential customers helpful information – you’re in luck! Way to go, Google.</p>
<p>Of course, the basic structural back-end geeky web stuff, like proper meta-tagging, 301 redirects, and HTML site maps are still very necessary. (Do you like how I threw those terms around? Lucky for me, I have our awesome web team on hand to translate into English.)</p>
<p>Next on the list: FINISH the online seminar. Perhaps I&#8217;ll come across some more interesting nuggets to share from the next five courses.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Go easy on the eyes</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/05/2013/go-easy-on-the-eyes/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 19:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BBEdit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CSS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HTML]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Notepad++]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TextWrangler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3019</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The other day as I was working on the newly-redesigned Faith In The Future Foundation website, FVM Sr.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The other day as I was working on the <a href="http://www.faithinthefuture.com" target="_blank">newly-redesigned Faith In The Future Foundation website</a>, FVM Sr. Art Director Mark Parker idled for a moment as he strolled past my desk and made the following comment:</p>
<p>&#8220;I can&#8217;t believe you like to code like that.&#8221;</p>
<p>Code like what? I thought I was doing it correctly. Not so. He was of course referring to TextWrangler&#8217;s default color settings, which, though not deal-breaking, do leave something to be desired. I tried to justify my nonchalant (read: negligent) attitude towards optimizing my workspace, but he remained unimpressed and, if I was being honest with myself, my position was defensible only by laziness.</p>
<div id="attachment_3020" style="max-width: 230px" class="wp-caption alignright"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-1.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="size-medium wp-image-3020 " alt="In TextWrangler's factory settings, attribute names and values are actually different colors, but you wouldn't know from looking..." src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-1-220x220.jpg" width="220" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-1-220x220.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-1-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-1.jpg 425w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">In TextWrangler&#8217;s factory settings, attribute names and values are actually different colors, but you wouldn&#8217;t know from looking&#8230;</p></div>
<p>One of the few things I miss about my old Windows-based workstation is <a href="http://notepad-plus-plus.org" target="_blank">Notepad++</a>, with its granular syntax highlighting options and slew of built in color schemes that make changing it up a breeze (although even the default settings look good). TextWrangler ostensibly has but two options: the factory settings, or customizing each color manually. You can, however, add color preference files to the ~/Library/Application Support/TextWrangler/Color Schemes/ directory and then activate them using the preset dropdown in the Text Colors preferences menu from within TextWrangler. In newer versions of OS X, the user Library folder is hidden by default, so you&#8217;ll need to use the Terminal or hit Go &gt; Go to Folder in the Finder.</p>
<p>Overhearing our conversation, our new developer, Kat Sioson, suggested <a href="http://www.andrewhazelden.com/blog/2012/06/midnight-blue-color-scheme-for-textwrangler-and-bbedit/" target="_blank">Andrew Hazelden&#8217;s Midnight Blue color scheme for BBEdit and TextWrangler</a>, and soon I was knee deep in the world of user-created color schemes. You can find a good entry point <a href="http://bbeditextras.org/wiki/index.php?title=Color_Schemes" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<p>I found Midnight Blue to be pretty good though I modified it so that general markup is a different color than plain text. I&#8217;m particularly fond of <a href="http://ethanschoonover.com/solarized" target="_blank">Ethan Schoonover&#8217;s Solarized Dark</a>, which is available, along with a Light counterpart, for a variety of applications beyond those from Bare Bones Software.</p>
<p>In the spirit of giving back, I figured I&#8217;d add my own contribution &#8211; <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FVM-Color-Schemes.zip" target="_blank">FVM Dark</a>, which uses the tones on our newly-redesigned agency website.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FVM-Color-Schemes.zip">FVM-Color-Schemes</a></p>
<p>I spend the bulk of my coding time working with HTML and CSS, so if you spend more time with Javascript, Ruby, Python, etc., you may find it needs some tweaking. Just drag and drop the colors around until you find something that works for you.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-3.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-3021" alt="image-3" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-3-220x220.jpg" width="220" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-3-220x220.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-3-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-3.jpg 425w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a><br />
If you&#8217;re in the mood for a more seasonally appropriate work environment, also included in that archive is an Autumn color scheme I put together as well, inspired by the foliage outside our offices. Happy coding!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Attention all browsers: Testing websites in all conditions</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/29/2013/attention-all-browsers-testing-websites-in-all-conditions/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 19:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AB testing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cross browser]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2818</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Designers all too often understand the frustration of having so many web browsers.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Designers all too often understand the frustration of having so many web browsers. A beautiful looking website works great on modern web browsers like Safari, Firefox, and Chrome, but performs horridly in older versions of Internet Explorer. So what’s the solution? Cross browser testing.</p>
<p>The web is evolving, pretty much every minute of every day. Web browsers are constantly updating their programs to accommodate for new technologies and pushing out updates to their software on a regular basis. Unfortunately that leaves designers and coders at the mercy of their users, some of whom may not have or cannot update to more savvy HTML5 browsers. So cross browser testing is an important step in the development process.</p>
<p>Cross browser testing is exactly what it sounds like. You look at a coded website in one browser, click all the links, view all the page templates, and make sure that everything looks and works as expected. It gets tedious sometimes. There are tools to help you along the way, probably the best is <a href="http://www.crossbrowsertesting.com/" target="_blank">http://www.crossbrowsertesting.com/</a>.</p>
<p>This monthly subscriptions service provides remote machine access to dozens of web browser platforms old and new. Their screenshot feature allows you to submit a URL and automatically scan and save images of your website’s layout in every browser you choose. You can also use their live testing method to select an operating system and web browser to actively navigate a website’s functionality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Using full-bleed photography to make websites pop</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/29/2013/using-full-bleed-photography-to-make-websites-pop/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 19:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[full-bleed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2820</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If you haven’t noticed already, this website is filled with full-bleed photography.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you haven’t noticed already, this website is filled with full-bleed photography. Just see <a title="Home" href="/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="Work" href="/work/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="Jordy Pickel" href="/people/jordy-pickel/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="About" href="/about/" target="_blank">here</a>, and <a title="Contact" href="/contact/" target="_blank">here</a>. This type of coding process allows for hi-resolution images to expand or contract to the frame’s width, resulting in a flawless edge to edge look. There are of course, some things to watch out for:</p>
<h3>1. Have really nice images</h3>
<p>If your photos are hi-resolution, there’s little point in stuffing your design with full-bleed photos. You have to allow for the image to expand to some of the largest browser sizes. On a typical desktop, that could 1,500 pixels wide. New computers such as the MacBook with Retina display or the new iPad have two times the screen resolution as they used to. That means that a standard 1,024 x 768 iPad actually has a resolution of 2,048 x 1,536 pixels.</p>
<p>On our website we use images that are 2,400 pixels wide. For now, that’s probably enough to look good on most every device. However, as resolutions standards continue to increase, the max image size is probably going to have to go up.</p>
<h3>2. Use CSS to format images, not JavaScript</h3>
<p>Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) are code documents that tell your website how to look. It controls column width, typography, colors, and image effects. JavaScript on the other hand is a script that&#8217;s loaded as the page loads, and can alter the look and feel of a website. JavaScript isn&#8217;t horrible in this scenario, but CSS is just an easier way to go.</p>
<p>To allow for images to expand and contract to their frame, just indicate the image&#8217;s full width:</p>
<pre>img { width: 100%; height: auto; }</pre>
<p>This will adjust the image&#8217;s width to 100% of the container it&#8217;s in, and adjust the height proportionally. If you wanted to make the image &#8220;bleed&#8221; off the page (go 100% of the width while <em>also</em> going 100% of the height) you&#8217;ll want to place the image as a background image. In that scenario, you would indicate that the background image have a cover effect:</p>
<pre>div { background-image: url(imagepath.jpg); background-size: cover; }</pre>
<p>This adjusts the background image to fit both horizontally and vertically in the container you specify. If the image is a wide one, it will expand to 100% of the frame&#8217;s height and the sides of them image would be cut off. If it were a skinny image, the width would expand to 100% and the top and bottom would be cut off.</p>
<p>This is of course not an exact science; you website&#8217;s design will look slightly different according to the user&#8217;s browser size. However, with the proper background images, it can look really nice.</p>
<h3>3. Understand that not all browsers are your friend</h3>
<p>As is the case with most HTML5 techniques, image resizing doesn&#8217;t always work in every browser. Namely, Internet Explorer 7 and 8. Rather than loading in a separate page or image for those specific browsers, you can fix their deficiencies with <a href="http://www.modernizr.com" target="_blank">Modernizr</a> or using a <a href="https://github.com/louisremi/background-size-polyfill" target="_blank">Polyfill</a>. Always cross browser check!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
