<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Coleman Rigg &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/blog/author/crigg/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Irrational plays: fantasy football and brand equity</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/14/2016/irrational-plays-fantasy-football-and-brand-equity/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 01:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coleman Rigg]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6311</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The dominant Monday night performances of the Steelers and 49ers brought week 1 of the NFL season to a close.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The dominant Monday night performances of the Steelers and 49ers brought week 1 of the NFL season to a close. It was a great start to the season, and I found it hard to take my eyes off of the TV (and <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/blog/09/04/2014/fantasy-football-head-to-head-yahoo-vs-espn/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">fantasy football app</a>) all weekend.</p>
<p>But in the midst of “participating” in my fantasy leagues this past Sunday, my attention turned to the top players who were NOT on the field: Le’Veon Bell, Tom Brady, and Josh Gordon. All three of these players had been ruled out — with multi-game suspensions — far in advance of week 1.</p>
<p>Despite the guaranteed weeks of inactivity, their “% owned” statistics were still rock solid:</p>
<ul>
<li>Le’Veon Bell —100% owned</li>
<li>Tom Brady — 98% owned</li>
<li>Josh Gordon — 91% owned</li>
</ul>
<p>All of these players were early draft picks in my leagues. — but why? They’re out for almost a third of the fantasy season, there’s no certainty of performance when they do return, and you could have selected a guaranteed week 1 starter. Some fantasy experts would tell you that it just doesn’t make statistical sense. The answer: these players have strong brand equity.</p>
<p>Brand equity is a consumer’s perceived value of a product, or in this case, a fantasy football player. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EIKqupYOR48" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Associations with past glory</a> and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FpKduqYmALw" target="_blank" rel="noopener">flashy commercials</a> are enough for people to take a chance, despite these players being handicaps to the team as a whole.</p>
<p>Fantasy team owners believe these inactive players with strong brand equity will generate more points in later weeks of the season, and that this higher, yet delayed point payout is more valuable than drafting a currently active player who will most likely generate fewer fantasy points.</p>
<p>So, whether they knew it or not, most team owners made decisions based on brand equity while drafting this year. Only time will tell if these owners made good decisions, or if they are just suckers for the big name.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What they don’t teach you in college: working advice from a first year AE</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/15/2016/what-they-dont-teach-you-in-college-working-advice-from-a-first-year-ae/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 23:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Coleman Rigg]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=6169</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I just finished presenting a project to our client, I have three deadlines to meet by the end of the week, and I still need a more creative title for this blog post.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I just finished presenting a project to our client, I have three deadlines to meet by the end of the week, and I still need a more creative title for this blog post. I’m swimming in strategies, spreadsheets, tasks, and processes.</p>
<p>To think, just 365 moons ago I was waking up in my college bed, groggy from yet another Senior Week adventure, days away from graduation, living the millennial dream without a responsibility in the world.</p>
<p>I’ve been a Junior AE at FVM for around ten months now and it’s been a rollercoaster. In some ways I feel seasoned; in others I feel novice. But through it all, I’ve learned a lot.</p>
<p>So this blog is for the bleary-eyed, 21 year-old, college student I once was. Here’s some insight and advice on how to wake up and enjoy the ride.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6174 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload.jpg" alt="slack_for_ios_upload" width="1000" height="668" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload-220x147.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload-768x513.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<h5><strong><em>Day one</em></strong></h5>
<h2>Week one wake up call</h2>
<p>My first week at FVM was pretty typical: Read the employee handbook, learn everyone’s names, and communicate directly with a senior designer to finalize a piece of creative. It didn’t get any easier from there. By day four I was contributing on important marketing projects for our clients. You could call it a steep learning curve.</p>
<p><em>Tip #1: This is a real job, not a baby-sitters club.</em></p>
<h2>Diving in head first</h2>
<p>The “deep end” is something we talk about a lot. Metaphorically, the deep end represents something beyond surface-level thinking. In marketing, the deep end is the research, questions, answers, and analysis that are required to burrow into a client’s challenges.</p>
<p>My own personal deep end is balancing varied responsibilities at what seems like hyper-speed at first. During these nine months, I’ve gone from inexperienced college grad to fresh-faced pair of hands, to frequent contributor, to wing-man of our EVP of Client Services on key accounts. Oddly enough, I’m even growing a beard like him, although mine is not quite as “experienced.”</p>
<p><em>Tip #2: Dive in head first, because you can’t learn to swim with your feet still touching the bottom.</em></p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-6176 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438.jpg" alt="IMG_1438" width="1631" height="713" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438.jpg 1631w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438-220x96.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438-768x336.jpg 768w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/IMG_1438-1024x448.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 1631px) 100vw, 1631px" /></p>
<h2></h2>
<h5><strong><em>The deep end</em></strong></h5>
<h2>Questions, questions, questions</h2>
<p>I used to think that if I didn’t know about something mentioned in a meeting or conversation, it was better just to nod along and then look it up later.</p>
<p>I wouldn’t risk asking stupid questions like, “Will this need to be printed?” or “Is this strictly a digital piece?”</p>
<p>But when that one question I never asked came back to bite me in the ass, I stopped thinking that way.</p>
<p>Guess what? It turns out that everyone in the room is more knowledgeable and experienced than you. They like it when you ask questions. And their answers provide far more first-hand insight than anything you’ll find in a search engine.</p>
<p>Yes, from the moment you enter school as a child you are taught to ask questions, receive answers, and (hopefully) learning will follow. But for some inexplicable reason, when I entered the working world I thought I was expected to know it all.</p>
<p>There <em>are</em> such things as dumb questions, but asking them is key, because not knowing the dumb answers is worse than not asking the dumb question. Duh.</p>
<p><em>Tip #3: If you want to learn as quickly as possible, speak up, because no one will speak up for you.</em></p>
<p><img class="alignleft wp-image-6173 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload.jpeg" alt="slack_for_ios_upload" width="750" height="555" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload.jpeg 750w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/slack_for_ios_upload-220x163.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>
<h5><strong><em>It even says it on the wall</em></strong></h5>
<h2>Everybody has their days</h2>
<p>“I’m the man.”</p>
<p>“That was dumb.”</p>
<p>“I have such a good idea!”</p>
<p>“THAT WAS A STUPID IDEA. WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?! IN A MEETING?! REALLY!? Nice job, idiot.”</p>
<p>The highs and lows I’ve experienced are the second most exhilarating part of working in advertising (the first is dominating on the ping pong table, day in and day out). There are days when everything goes perfectly; all work receives high praise and positive feedback. There are also days I can’t even remember to attach documents to an email.</p>
<p>It’s all about balance. Don’t beat yourself up all week about one mistake, and don’t bask in the glory of a small victory for too long.</p>
<p><em>Tip #4: Briefly enjoy the highs, learn from your lows, and move on because there’s work to be done. </em></p>
<h2>Agency life is “the life”</h2>
<p>“I love my job” was a statement that always troubled me. I mean can anyone really <em>love</em> his or her job? Is that a real feeling? Or is this just something people say to cope with the idea that they have to spend 40+ hours a week doing something for money? The idea had always been blurry to me.</p>
<p>I refuse to write a mushy bit that declares I have the greatest job in the world and all other jobs aren’t as fun or cool as mine. But with that being said, agency life rocks! The daily routine does not involve sipping whiskey, smoking Lucky Strikes, or throwing lavish office parties, but it is way more lively than I ever imagined an “adult” job could be.</p>
<p>Cooking competitions, existential debates, acoustic guitar serenades (by me), flying drones, wearing pajamas, playing darts, and shooting hoops are all part of the mix. No stuffy small talk, power/ego trips, or menial work intended to haze the new guy. Needless to say, I really like my job.</p>
<p><em>Tip #5: With the right company, right people, hard work, and a little time, you’ll find yourself saying those four silly words, too.</em></p>
<h5><img class="alignleft wp-image-6172 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Coleman2.jpg" alt="Coleman2" width="1000" height="534" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman2.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman2-220x117.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman2-768x410.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><strong><em>I got this</em></strong></h5>
<h5><img class="alignleft wp-image-6171 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Coleman1.jpg" alt="Coleman1" width="1000" height="570" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman1.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman1-220x125.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Coleman1-768x438.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><strong><em>If you can&#8217;t chug a gallon of apple cider or wear a choker for a week, don&#8217;t lose the bet</em></strong></h5>
<h2><strong>Get out of bed</strong></h2>
<p>While my roles and responsibilities are challenging and constantly changing, I’m just happy to be swimming in the deep end here at FVM. I’m learning, I’m enjoying, and I’m growing…a beard. What more could I want?</p>
<p><em>One last tip: Get out of bed, eat a proper meal, and start working on your ping-pong game. </em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
