<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>direct marketing &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/direct-marketing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Pay-Per-Gaze: The future of advertising</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/13/2014/pay-per-gaze-the-future-of-advertising/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 19:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google Glass]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marty McFly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mashable]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pay-per-click]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3272</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[&#8220;Advertising is going to change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 100,&#8221; says Chris Taylor of Mashable OP-ED.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Advertising is going to change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 100,&#8221; <a title="says Chris Taylor of Mashable OP-ED." href="http://mashable.com/2013/08/15/the-future-of-advertising-pay-per-gaze-is-just-the-beginning/" target="_blank">says Chris Taylor of Mashable OP-ED. </a>In recent months Google, the world’s largest search engine provider, was granted a patent for a Google Glass-based ad system known as &#8220;pay-per-gaze.”</p>
<p>Google Glass is a wearable computer with an optical head-mounted display, which is being developed by Google as part of a mission to produce a mass-market ubiquitous computer.  To operate Google Glass, wearers simply tilt their head 30 degrees upward or tap the touchpad and say, &#8220;O.K., Glass.&#8221;  After the glasses are activated simple requests can be made such as, &#8220;Take a picture”, &#8220;Record a video&#8221;, or &#8220;Send a message to.”  That&#8217;s where &#8220;pay-per-gaze&#8221; comes in.  Google’s &#8220;pay-per-gaze&#8221; would charge advertisers for the number of times someone looks at their ad through Google Glass, the same way pay-per-click works today when users click on a link.  Google Glass contains technology that would track the direction the wearer’s pupils are pointing, and for how long they are gazing at a message.</p>
<p>This technology could potentially be a major risk for Google as people are infinitely exposed to advertising.  The money would flow in endlessly, and advertisers might second-guess themselves and their decision to invest in &#8220;pay-per-gaze.”  Still, this technology is something not even Marty McFly would have imagined.  Personally, I&#8217;ll stick with my Ray Bans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digesting copy over lunch</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/03/2013/lunchtime-reading/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chipotle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2993</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Lunch at Chipotle is always awesome.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lunch at Chipotle is always awesome. Today, it was especially awesome to see good ole fashioned words on paper telling an effective brand story in this impatient, digital world of ours. The burrito king’s cups and wrapping paper are playfully covered with musings about all-things-Chipotle, from the pleasure of foil licking to the reservoir of deliciousness at the bottom of each burrito. The kind of things that we Chipotle-lovers can relate to—and, more importantly, help to build brand loyalty.</p>
<p>Copy is still a powerful tool. You just need to seek out those rare moments when your audience is happy to read them. Like when they have a big, fat, juicy burrito in their hands.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How a starfish sparked an idea</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/02/2013/how-a-starfish-sparked-an-idea/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 17:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3066</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I was beaming.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="attachment_3104" style="max-width: 175px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img class="size-medium wp-image-3104" alt="Isn't she adorable?!" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-165x220.jpeg" width="165" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-165x220.jpeg 165w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-768x1024.jpeg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 165px) 100vw, 165px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Isn&#8217;t she adorable?!</p></div>
<p>I was beaming. My favorite family member (don’t tell my husband), Macy, had just graduated from Puppy Kindergarten with flying colors, and she was totally into the toy I bought her for a congratulatory present. So into it, in fact, that I immediately logged on to the company’s website to hunt for more. Because, you know, her 5 ½-month birthday is just around the corner.</p>
<p>And there it was: “Become a Dog Toy Tester.” The deal was, sign up to receive four toys a year. Agree to write a review and you get those toys at 40% off. 40% off toys Macy loves? And I get to share stories of my puppy with the entire world? What’s not to love?</p>
<p>At that exact same time, our B2B client was looking to increase reviews of products on their website. The strategy was an Apple product giveaway—always a great incentive, but what about giving the actual products away at a discount in return for a review? You better believe that in the long run, it’s going to sell more product. Here’s why it works:</p>
<p>1. It shows customers you value their opinion, which creates loyalty.<br />
2. It gives customers more of what they need. Sure, an iPad mini is great, but that product I was going to buy anyway? I need that.<br />
3. The discount encourages customers to try new products—if it doesn’t work out, at least they didn’t pay full price.<br />
4. It’s less hassle on your end. No need to run complex sweepstakes giveaways, partner with third parties, jump through legal hoops, or figure out complex rules.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
