<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Jordy Pickel &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/blog/author/jpickel/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Scream SEO without losing your voice</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/28/2016/scream-seo-without-losing-your-voice/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 16:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=5775</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[SEO — those three magic letters have for some time seemed like the catchall solution to all your marketing problems.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SEO — those three magic letters have for some time seemed like the catchall solution to all your marketing problems. Throw extra budget its way, toss in some more keywords, and <em>presto: </em>forms are filled in, emails flood inboxes, phones ring off the hook, and you&#8217;re swimming in new customers! It’s the one-size-fits all solution. Marketing magic.</p>
<p>Obviously, that perception is wrong. And yet this oversimplified and exaggerated mindset is still a commonly held assumption in marketing departments across America. We&#8217;ve seen many companies focus so strongly on SEO (trying to keep up with every Panda, Penguin, Hummingbird, or Pirate that Google releases into the wild) that their websites are a mess.</p>
<p>What’s worse, conflict between site-optimized copy, positioning, and key messaging is actually damaging their brands.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-5777" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/giphy.gif" alt="giphy" width="320" height="240" /></p>
<p>But it doesn’t have to be like this — SEO and brand can live in harmony. Here, we outline some areas to focus your SEO efforts without weakening your brand and losing your voice.</p>
<h3><strong>Before You Get Started</strong></h3>
<p>Let’s just be clear: SEO is about your website traffic and ranking. On the other hand, brand is everything — social, advertising, content, sales, customer service, events, <em>and</em> website — it&#8217;s just so much bigger. SEO is a marketing tactic, and like all tactics, it’s worth very little without a clear, consistent and authentic brand.</p>
<p>So, in order for you to nail your SEO strategy, you need a full understanding of your brand&#8217;s position, purpose, and values. With those elements in your back pocket, the right keywords will come.</p>
<h3><strong>Basic Research</strong></h3>
<p>If you aren’t already doing the basic due-diligence for SEO, start now. Make sure you know what your brand keywords are and any alternative phrasing your potential customer base would use. This research can be an intensive process, but it’s invaluable. It will benefit traffic and ranking in the long run, and it may also lead you to discover valuable search phases that could influence ideas for messaging moving forward. Keep that list handy and check it often.</p>
<p>And about that content. Make sure that with every new blog post, whitepaper, press release, or service offering that makes it onto your website has a title tag, meta tags, image alt attributes, and H tags. If you don’t know what those are, read up <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/tags/tag_title.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>, <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/tags/tag_meta.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>, <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/tags/att_img_alt.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>, and <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/tags/tag_hn.asp" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here</a>.</p>
<h3><strong>The New Kids on the Block</strong></h3>
<p>Search engines like Google have one simple goal (well, maybe a few <a href="http://mashable.com/2012/03/01/google-privacy-data-policy/#OgkMWsLSHZqj" target="_blank" rel="noopener">more</a>, but we’re not going into that here) and that is to provide <em>what</em> the user is looking for <em>when</em> they ask for it. It’s as simple as that.</p>
<p>In SEO’s infancy, that meant keyword stuffing a business-to-business marketing website with brand-positioning digital services online advertising copy that focuses on the digital development and brand marketing services that a brand manager for a B2B and B2C business might be looking for on a search engine optimization search platform.</p>
<p>You see what I did there?</p>
<p>Today, a lot of that keyword-stuffing-for-the-sake-of-keyword-stuffing is identified and either demoted to the dregs of search results, or cast aside and evaluated for the merits of newer search ranking criteria:</p>
<p><em><strong>Responsive design</strong></em><br />
Google made waves <a href="https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/6196932?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener">last year</a> when they announced that websites that weren’t mobile friendly might take a hit in their search rankings. This of course only reflected searches made on mobile devices, but since <a href="http://searchengineland.com/its-official-google-says-more-searches-now-on-mobile-than-on-desktop-220369" target="_blank" rel="noopener">more Google searches take place on mobile devices than on computers</a>, it’s a pretty big deal.</p>
<p>When it comes time to create a shiny new website, make sure it’s designed responsively. And be responsible about image file size, JavaScript load time, and user interface design. That means you shouldn’t try and serve up a 2mb marquee image, or load a script on every page if it’s only used once, or have a form’s submit and cancel buttons be so small a thumb can’t find them.</p>
<p>To find out where you rank in terms of mobile-friendly usability, check out <a href="https://www.google.com/webmasters/tools/mobile-friendly/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google’s helpful online tool</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>Video transcription<br />
</strong></em>Google loves websites that contain rich media. They also love it when you make it easier to determine the relevancy of a video against the keywords your website targets. Make sure you have a transcript of a video’s content linked with a subtitles or captions tag to enhance your ranking.</p>
<p><em><strong>Structured data markup</strong></em><br />
Arguably the most important element of all, Structured Data is becoming more and more important as Google and other search engines place an increasing amount of focus on semantic search.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-5887 alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Google-data.jpg" alt="Google data" width="800" height="828" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Google-data.jpg 800w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Google-data-213x220.jpg 213w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Google-data-768x795.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></p>
<p>By identifying key components of your business — your company name, telephone, address, business hours — you’re helping Google to identify its DNA. The search engine then matches that up with the content on your website to provide more accurate results for all those folks searching for, say, a business-to-business marketing agency with brand-positioning digital services.</p>
<p>Google’s <a href="https://www.google.com/webmasters/markup-helper/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Structured Data Markup Helper</a> and <a href="http://schema.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Schema.org</a> are great places to start. You can also feel free to have a <a href="mailto:*protected email*">conversation with us</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>The Social Network<br />
</strong></em>You’ve no doubt heard it before, but the impact of social media is real — even in B2B. More than just a place where your neighbor posts status updates before, during, and after his amazing crock-pot chicken dinner, social platforms are where we explore, discover, and connect with others&#8230; including in the professional world.If you’ve uploaded a blog post recently and never bothered to let your Twitter followers know, please go do that right now. I’ll wait.</p>
<p>Every time you have valuable insight to customers (and potential customers) make sure you’re doing your part to spread the word. Make sure you’re paying attention to other experts in your field and follow their insight as well.</p>
<p>That way, when you reference your latest bit of wisdom, the community gets an opportunity to digest what you have to offer and share it with their friends. And then maybe they can rave about an amazing crock-pot chicken recipe they just found.</p>
<h2><strong>Marketing magic</strong></h2>
<p>SEO is a vital part of any digital marketing strategy; it can add huge value, so it’s important you follow the steps discussed above. But it is a tactic, and it should be treated as one. In the time of the educated, informed, and engaged B2B buyer who is doing research and forming opinions, being in the first position on the first page of Google is nowhere near a clincher. You might score a few clicks because you’re highly visible, but then what? If nobody likes what they see, your search ranking is a wasted opportunity.</p>
<p>If the leads aren’t coming in as you’d like and your conversions are down, it&#8217;s probably not due to SEO woes. It’s more likely that your messaging is muddled, you’re not putting the right kind of content in the right place at the right time, or you’re not communicating the most relevant information to prospects.</p>
<p>The best way to support your SEO efforts is to establish a strong and consistent brand. The clearer your position and messaging becomes, the more familiar and more consistent those search queries will be. That’s how branding and marketing can really solve your SEO problem.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cross-browser testing: how to live with Internet Explorer</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/24/2014/cross-browser-testing/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 15:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4251</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Ask a group of web designers what they think of Internet Explorer and you&#8217;ll get a fair share of groans.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ask a group of web designers what they think of Internet Explorer and you&#8217;ll get a fair share of groans. Most will grumble about CSS hacks and quasi-transparency support, and the rest will make hilarious jokes like &#8220;Internet Explorer is only good for downloading other browsers.&#8221;</p>
<p>What&#8217;s really at the heart of all this hostility—to a once industry-leading product—is simply the aggravation of writing code that isn&#8217;t always accepted by all browsers (and the need to have to troubleshoot in so many different potential environments).</p>
<p>While there are <a href="http://www.w3.org/standards/webdesign/htmlcss" target="_blank">HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Mobile</a> coding standards, a browser that doesn&#8217;t support the new &#8220;whiz bang&#8221; techniques becomes a headache for designers (think transparency and rounded corners). On top of that, the user experience that morphs from a desktop hit to a mobile hit can dramatically alter the performance of a website (much like drop down menus and hover effects on touch screen devices).</p>
<h3>The Players</h3>
<p>We&#8217;ve gone from a world in which everyone used Netscape to steal Metallica MP3s, to one in which a user&#8217;s browser may change as they transition from their desk to their car to their couch. Even if you could control what browsers people use, it&#8217;s nearly impossible to control what versions they have (or have not) updated to. In fact, it has become such a problem that a few big names have launched <a href="https://www.modern.ie/en-us/ie6countdown" target="_blank">campaigns to stop using their own products</a>. There&#8217;s just no guarantee which browser your visitors will be viewing your content in, so you need to optimize for them all.</p>
<p>At ThinkFVM.com, we see that our visitors use the usual suspects:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-4256 size-full alignleft" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM.png" alt="FVM Browsers by Type" width="822" height="532" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM.png 822w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.28.52-AM-220x142.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 822px) 100vw, 822px" /></a></p>
<p>A full 15% of our visitors are on IE, which immediately raises flags. Will all of them be able to handle our Parallax? Do we have border radius styles that are going to look good when they&#8217;re downgraded? How many of these visitors are using versions of IE that can&#8217;t handle background sizing?</p>
<p>So, since Internet Explorer is the biggest culprit in behind-the-times-itis, we usually keep an eye on visitors&#8217; IE browsers:</p>
<div id="attachment_4257" style="max-width: 825px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-4257 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM.png" alt="FVM Browsers by IE Version" width="815" height="522" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM.png 815w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-10.44.53-AM-220x140.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 815px) 100vw, 815px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text"><em>Seriously? There are still IE6 users out there?</em></p></div>
<p>Right out of the gate we know that almost 8% of our visitors have IE8 or earlier. Those are the biggest culprits we&#8217;re seeing today, and to them, our website may not look as spectacular as we intended it to. We&#8217;re used to this and we incorporate that thinking into our concepts, but we don&#8217;t always want to sacrifice design for a troubled few. So we build what we want to and test accordingly. However, short of owning a 1980s-esque room full of computers and outdated operating software, what&#8217;s a coder to do?</p>
<p>Well, there are tools to help us out.</p>
<h3>The Solution</h3>
<p>Our personal favorite browser testing website is <a href="http://www.crossbrowsertesting.com" target="_blank">CrossBrowserTesting.com</a>. We joined this subscription-based service when it first launched, at a time when coders were lost for quality tools, and it has grown with the market ever since. Although no matter which browser testing software you use—<a href="http://www.browserstack.com/" target="_blank">BrowserStack</a>, <a href="https://saucelabs.com/" target="_blank">SauceLabs</a>, <a href="http://browsershots.org/" target="_blank">BrowserShots</a>, <a href="http://www.ranorex.com/blog/cross-browser-test-automation" target="_blank">Ranorex</a>, and <a href="http://smartbear.com/products/qa-tools/automated-testing-tools/" target="_blank">SmartBear</a> all have their own products—the tools are straightforward: plug in a URL and see how pages are rendered on the screen, in various browsers, and in multiple operating systems.</p>
<p>CrossBrowserTesting.com offers two methods for its troubleshooting: screenshots and live tests. We typically run all new websites and landing pages through the screenshots application, running IE7-IE11, a current and legacy version of Firefox, Chrome, Opera, and even iOS and Android mobile browsers. With a few clicks, we can test each layout design and check back later to compile a punch list of CSS miscreants.</p>
<p>If there are any active elements on the page—say scrolling marquees, dynamic drop down lists, or unique hover states—we can click from the screenshot result to view a live test of the website. This also helps when troubleshooting a CSS fix to make sure it was effective.</p>
<h3>Use Case In Action</h3>
<p>When we built our website, we took advantage of full-bleed images, which came at a cost to lesser capable browsers. We knew that IE8 and 7 did not support the background-width property, so we started right out with a failsafe image placement. Still, our website looked like this:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1.png" class="swipebox"><img class="alignleft wp-image-4279 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1.png" alt="Screen Shot 2014-09-24 at 1.46.33 PM" width="973" height="710" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1.png 973w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-1.46.33-PM1-220x160.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 973px) 100vw, 973px" /></a></p>
<p>IE 9, 10, and 11 look great, as does IE7. IE8 however, doesn&#8217;t scale the background image properly, and the failsafe image that IE7 displays isn&#8217;t rendering in IE8 like it should. <em>Sorry to our one user who visits in IE6, but we don&#8217;t bother testing for that browser anymore. You need to upgrade!</em></p>
<p>Yeesh. Luckily we ran into this problem before and implemented an easy <a href="https://github.com/louisremi/background-size-polyfill" target="_blank">hack</a>.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1.png" class="swipebox"><img class="alignleft wp-image-4281 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1.png" alt="Screen Shot 2014-09-24 at 2.17.10 PM" width="968" height="679" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1.png 968w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2014-09-24-at-2.17.10-PM1-220x154.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 968px) 100vw, 968px" /></a></p>
<p>Now, our pages look as uniform as they can be. Sure, the transparent black behind our bios is nicer than the solid grey, but that&#8217;s life. There&#8217;s probably a transparency hack out there somewhere, but the design didn&#8217;t warrant the extra scripting for the expected payout. The point is that no matter what browser a visitor uses to view your website, they can still view the website. And, with the cross-browser testing tools that we have at our disposal, we didn&#8217;t spend a lot of time guaranteeing a uniform user experience.</p>
<p>After all, we have a lot of <a href="https://www.facebook.com/video.php?v=530140273781498" target="_blank">other stuff going on</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>User experience and the iPhone</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/05/09/2014/ux-smartphone-design/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 13:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UX]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3778</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I have a little secret to admit.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I have a little secret to admit. I really, really, really, really hate how people organize their smartphones. Take a look at someone&#8217;s phone nowadays and it&#8217;s screen after screen after screen of app icons, usually with no logic in place as to how they&#8217;re organized or arranged. As someone who has an eye towards UX, this drives me batty.</p>
<div id="attachment_3786" style="max-width: 110px" class="wp-caption alignright"><img class="wp-image-3786" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image1-146x220.png" alt="Exhibit A" width="100" height="150" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image1-146x220.png 146w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image1.png 640w" sizes="(max-width: 100px) 100vw, 100px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Exhibit A</p></div>
<p>Take for example, my wife&#8217;s phone—riddled with games, social media apps, and utilities—but in no discernible order. Ask her and she&#8217;ll gladly tell you that &#8220;everything is where it should be,&#8221; but I can tell it&#8217;s not. Having to flip through screens when using apps related to each other or even pausing to think about which screen an app might be on is straight up, a poor user experience.</p>
<p>Typically, a person thinks about user experience when they&#8217;re using a product that&#8217;s shared with the community—a company&#8217;s website, a piece of software, a methodology for ordering sandwiches at Whole Foods—but they don&#8217;t always equate user experience when they are the only user to experience it.</p>
<p>Just as I think about organizing website content, I think about organizing my devices. There are some client preferences (I don&#8217;t like too many rows of icons), some usability standards (reduce the number of clicks needed to open an app, organize content by themes), and some inherent properties (for example, how a person would use a phone as compared to a tablet). These are all things I think about when organizing my stuff.</p>
<p>Luckily for me, Apple has taken care to design their products to function in similar ways. They even migrated their computer OS to keep &#8220;apps&#8221; instead of programs, which I will admit was a little tough to process at first. So, as someone who loves to organize website data into something anyone could understand, Apple let me easily organize my devices and keep them consistent across the board.</p>
<p>Take for example, my iPhone:</p>
<div id="attachment_3779" style="max-width: 133px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Unknown.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-3779 size-medium" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-123x220.png" alt="Unknown" width="123" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-123x220.png 123w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Unknown-576x1024.png 576w" sizes="(max-width: 123px) 100vw, 123px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Exhibit B</p></div>
<p style="text-align: left;">I organized my apps into a few main buckets: Office (for those administrative things like email and calculator), Games (that&#8217;s pretty self-explanatory), Library (for pictures, books, and news), and A/V (for the camera, Pandora, and Roku). Apps that I use the most often are placed on their own, out of the folder structure. This includes some visual items like the calendar and the clock, both of which display the date and time so I can get visual info at-a-glance if I need to.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">And I take a similar approach to my iPad:</p>
<div id="attachment_3781" style="max-width: 175px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo1.png" class="swipebox"><img class="wp-image-3781 size-medium" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo1-165x220.png" alt="photo" width="165" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo1-165x220.png 165w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo1-768x1024.png 768w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo1.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 165px) 100vw, 165px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Exhibit C</p></div>
<p style="text-align: left;">Most of the same old culprits are there—Office, Games, Library, and A/V—but I&#8217;ve organized some of my go-to apps differently, based upon how I used my tablet compared to my phone. Email is front and center (I try not to check my email in the elevator), and I use my tablet most often for notes and to-dos, where I use my phone for music and GPS.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">The thread that holds the devices together, is that all of the other many, many, many apps that I have are housed in the same folders on my phone, my tablet, and even my computer. My news apps can be found in the Library, my Dropbox is always in the Office, and if I want to pull up <a href="http://www.wxpn.org" target="_blank">WXPN</a>, I know the radio will be under A/V.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">A lot of our clients have more than one website, and use cases on each website are different, much like that of a phone and tablet. <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/tag/brand-strategy/">Brand strategy</a> is extremely important for our clients, for obvious reasons. What some people forget about, is that a logo isn&#8217;t the only thing users use to identify a brand. Knowing where to look for content on a website and seeing your expectations pleasantly met will help increase your brand name and lower frustration.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Here at FVM we love to reorganize a website. Classification, card sorting, and qualitation—this is our bag, baby. There&#8217;s nothing like the feeling of redesigning a website that&#8217;s more organized, more efficient, and more streamlined than it was before. Except of course, diving into the analytics and user testing to see where else you can improve.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Some people might make fun of my smart device habits, but I know that the user experience on my iPhone is 100%. Of course if you ask my wife, she&#8217;ll probably tell you, &#8220;I can never find anything on this phone.&#8221;</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Oh well, time to take another look at the analytics&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brand strategy: web design that takes a bird&#8217;s-eye-view</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/03/18/2014/tbd/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3506</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Tackling long-term objectives for digital projects can be a daunting process.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tackling long-term objectives for digital projects can be a daunting process. Often clients devise a “hit list” of top priorities, hoping to accomplish these one-by-one and as quickly as possible. At FVM, we tend to look at overall strategic efforts with a bird’s eye approach; and it’s amazing how different the view is from above.</p>
<p>One of the most common project requests is a website redesign. That’s easy enough; throw together a couple of Photoshop mockups, slap together a few lines of code, and boom. Instant website, right? Not quite.</p>
<p>A website redesign is much more encompassing than looks and functionality. What about the user experience? How is the site’s content organized? How does a design fit with the brand strategy? What about sister websites, email campaigns, back-end content management, or email databases? Suddenly a simple project doesn’t seem so simple.</p>
<p>We like to take a holistic approach towards our work, and we think that it shows in the success of our clients. When one website needs a new site structure, we don’t just re-architect a new one, we make sure that model works for all of the other websites or properties a user may touch. (Think about it, there may be 30 MLB teams, but our beloved Philadelphia Phillies share a similar site architecture with those pesky Atlanta Braves.)</p>
<p>Looking at things with a broader scope-of-work allows us to lay the groundwork for the rest of our digital projects. What we do in redesigning a website makes its way into emails, advertisements, mobile apps, and even print materials, saving time in the long run. Call it trickle down webonomics.</p>
<p>When those at the bottom of the priority list are finally attended to, taking this holistic approach will save you manpower (and budget). It will also keep your properties consistent, and more familiar to the end user. And isn’t that always the goal?</p>
<div></div>
<div><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/birds-eye1.png" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-3598" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/birds-eye1.png" alt="birds-eye" width="600" height="414" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/birds-eye1.png 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/birds-eye1-220x151.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a></div>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Giving Company Materials a Little Spice for the Holidays</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/20/2013/giving-company-materials-a-little-spice-for-the-holidays/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3400</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Everybody who’s flown a lot probably knows an airline’s take off instructions by heart.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everybody who’s flown a lot probably knows an airline’s take off instructions by heart. However, government-required informational videos can be something that enhances your brand, and not just a checkmark on the “must have” list.</p>
<p>Case in point: Delta Airlines’ holiday-themed safety video:</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/0P-fqUoHMBc?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FVM: Cruciverbalists At Large</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/11/26/2013/fvm-cruciverbalists-at-large/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 06:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3254</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[We’re not just hard work and great creative here at FVM, we like to have a little fun too.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We’re not just hard work and great creative here at FVM, we like to have a little fun too. Here’s a Thanksgiving crossword puzzle to get you in the holiday spirit.</p>
<div id="attachment_3256" style="max-width: 210px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FVM-First-Thanksgiving.pdf" target="_blank"><img class=" wp-image-3256" alt="Thanksgiving Crossword Puzzle" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2013-11-20-at-3.38.09-PM.png" width="200" height="200" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2013-11-20-at-3.38.09-PM.png 461w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2013-11-20-at-3.38.09-PM-80x80.png 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2013-11-20-at-3.38.09-PM-220x220.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 200px) 100vw, 200px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Download the Crossword Puzzle</a></p></div>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Understanding responsive design</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/17/2013/understanding-responsive-design/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 19:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[responsive design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2812</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When a client asks us to design a new website, they almost always include a caveat for creating an additional template specific to mobile phones.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When a client asks us to design a new website, they almost always include a caveat for creating an additional template specific to mobile phones. Mobile phones of course are surging in popularity — according to Wikipedia, more than 17% of web traffic is performed on a mobile device.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s true that a lot of mobile phones display websites &#8220;the way they were intended to display&#8221;, but what if that&#8217;s not good enough? What looks good on a big screen doesn&#8217;t always look good on a small one.</p>
<p>Additionally, creating a mobile-friendly website shouldn&#8217;t mean creating one website for desktop users and another one for mobile users &#8212; that type of practice generally leads to a poor user experience and fractured website content.</p>
<p>So what&#8217;s the solution? Responsive Design.</p>
<h2>What is Responsive Design?</h2>
<p>Responsive Design is a coding methodology that allows for a template to automatically adjust its settings to the width or height of the browser window. This means that the website displays flawlessly in a 320 pixel-wide iPhone or a 1024 pixel-wide desktop. Layouts, font sizes, and column widths can change, but the content stays the same.</p>
<p>Want to see an example of this? Just adjust your browser window because our website is already built this way. Go ahead, we&#8217;ll wait.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Our website&#8217;s template expands and contracts to fit the user&#8217;s device. For example, a website could have two possible layout arrangements, the latter of which only kicks in if the user is viewing the website on devices smaller than 768 pixels:</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter" alt="responsive-layout-desktop" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/responsive-layout-desktop.jpg" width="300" height="228" /> <img class="aligncenter" alt="responsive-layout-mobile" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/responsive-layout-mobile.jpg" width="149" height="300" /></p>
<p>In the end, it&#8217;s important to offer up a consistent approach towards web design. Repeat visitors to your website may use an array of devices, and it&#8217;s important that you create a website that looks good on all devices, and still provides the same familiar content they saw the last time they visited.</p>
<p>The main column in this template would be 66% wide, so it would fit in regular desktop monitors or widescreen desktop monitors accordingly. What about mobile devices? Those columns would be so thin, they wouldn’t really be readable. So we collapse the side-by-side columns so that they’re on top of one another:</p>
<p>Now, responsive design is a little more complicated than that, but you get the idea. The ultimate point is that your agency should be thinking responsively when building a website. Adjusting for alternative screen resolutions shouldn’t be something that’s thought about after-the-fact.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Attention all browsers: Testing websites in all conditions</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/29/2013/attention-all-browsers-testing-websites-in-all-conditions/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 19:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AB testing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[analytics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cross browser]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2818</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Designers all too often understand the frustration of having so many web browsers.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Designers all too often understand the frustration of having so many web browsers. A beautiful looking website works great on modern web browsers like Safari, Firefox, and Chrome, but performs horridly in older versions of Internet Explorer. So what’s the solution? Cross browser testing.</p>
<p>The web is evolving, pretty much every minute of every day. Web browsers are constantly updating their programs to accommodate for new technologies and pushing out updates to their software on a regular basis. Unfortunately that leaves designers and coders at the mercy of their users, some of whom may not have or cannot update to more savvy HTML5 browsers. So cross browser testing is an important step in the development process.</p>
<p>Cross browser testing is exactly what it sounds like. You look at a coded website in one browser, click all the links, view all the page templates, and make sure that everything looks and works as expected. It gets tedious sometimes. There are tools to help you along the way, probably the best is <a href="http://www.crossbrowsertesting.com/" target="_blank">http://www.crossbrowsertesting.com/</a>.</p>
<p>This monthly subscriptions service provides remote machine access to dozens of web browser platforms old and new. Their screenshot feature allows you to submit a URL and automatically scan and save images of your website’s layout in every browser you choose. You can also use their live testing method to select an operating system and web browser to actively navigate a website’s functionality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Using full-bleed photography to make websites pop</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/29/2013/using-full-bleed-photography-to-make-websites-pop/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 19:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[full-bleed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2820</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If you haven’t noticed already, this website is filled with full-bleed photography.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you haven’t noticed already, this website is filled with full-bleed photography. Just see <a title="Home" href="/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="Work" href="/work/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="Jordy Pickel" href="/people/jordy-pickel/" target="_blank">here</a>, <a title="About" href="/about/" target="_blank">here</a>, and <a title="Contact" href="/contact/" target="_blank">here</a>. This type of coding process allows for hi-resolution images to expand or contract to the frame’s width, resulting in a flawless edge to edge look. There are of course, some things to watch out for:</p>
<h3>1. Have really nice images</h3>
<p>If your photos are hi-resolution, there’s little point in stuffing your design with full-bleed photos. You have to allow for the image to expand to some of the largest browser sizes. On a typical desktop, that could 1,500 pixels wide. New computers such as the MacBook with Retina display or the new iPad have two times the screen resolution as they used to. That means that a standard 1,024 x 768 iPad actually has a resolution of 2,048 x 1,536 pixels.</p>
<p>On our website we use images that are 2,400 pixels wide. For now, that’s probably enough to look good on most every device. However, as resolutions standards continue to increase, the max image size is probably going to have to go up.</p>
<h3>2. Use CSS to format images, not JavaScript</h3>
<p>Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) are code documents that tell your website how to look. It controls column width, typography, colors, and image effects. JavaScript on the other hand is a script that&#8217;s loaded as the page loads, and can alter the look and feel of a website. JavaScript isn&#8217;t horrible in this scenario, but CSS is just an easier way to go.</p>
<p>To allow for images to expand and contract to their frame, just indicate the image&#8217;s full width:</p>
<pre>img { width: 100%; height: auto; }</pre>
<p>This will adjust the image&#8217;s width to 100% of the container it&#8217;s in, and adjust the height proportionally. If you wanted to make the image &#8220;bleed&#8221; off the page (go 100% of the width while <em>also</em> going 100% of the height) you&#8217;ll want to place the image as a background image. In that scenario, you would indicate that the background image have a cover effect:</p>
<pre>div { background-image: url(imagepath.jpg); background-size: cover; }</pre>
<p>This adjusts the background image to fit both horizontally and vertically in the container you specify. If the image is a wide one, it will expand to 100% of the frame&#8217;s height and the sides of them image would be cut off. If it were a skinny image, the width would expand to 100% and the top and bottom would be cut off.</p>
<p>This is of course not an exact science; you website&#8217;s design will look slightly different according to the user&#8217;s browser size. However, with the proper background images, it can look really nice.</p>
<h3>3. Understand that not all browsers are your friend</h3>
<p>As is the case with most HTML5 techniques, image resizing doesn&#8217;t always work in every browser. Namely, Internet Explorer 7 and 8. Rather than loading in a separate page or image for those specific browsers, you can fix their deficiencies with <a href="http://www.modernizr.com" target="_blank">Modernizr</a> or using a <a href="https://github.com/louisremi/background-size-polyfill" target="_blank">Polyfill</a>. Always cross browser check!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
