<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>media buying &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/media-buying/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Are Super Bowl Ads Worth The Investment?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/30/2014/are-super-bowl-ads-worth-the-investment/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commercials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl XLVIII]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3422</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event. It&#8217;s the most watched program of the year. Even those who have no idea who the Denver Broncos or the Seattle Seahawks are will tune in. Why? Typically it&#8217;s because everyone else is doing it, but another reason is the advertising. In 2013, the average cost of a 30-second spot was $4 million. The effectiveness of these ads in boosting a company&#8217;s sales has been in question over the past few years. Experts have compared the investment of the cost of an ad vs. overall increased revenue after the Super Bowl, and it shows little to no change. Forbes magazine claims that most companies would be better off airing 10 commercials at $400,000 each, to increase repetition. Forbes also claims that Super Bowl Ads have become memorible for presentation, but forgettable in terms of persuasion.</p>
<p>The University of Wisconsin-Eau Claire <a href="http://www.uwec.edu/newsbureau/release/past/2000/00-01/010400super.html">did a study of over 500 Super Bowl spots that ran between 2000 and 2009</a>, and found that many did not work. Some Super Bowl Ads fail due to the fact that people typically recall the story, but not the product. More often than not, Super Bowl ads attempt to deliver broad humor for entertainment purposes, rather than sell the product. Sometimes companies will enlist celebrities to sponsor their Super Bowl Ad, but experts have also concluded this tactic is ineffective as the celebrity may lack relevance to the product. Still the question must be asked, is the Super Bowl ad worth the investment?</p>
<p>Forbes magazine says yes.</p>
<p>The real reason companies invest in Super Bowl spots is because the announcement of buying airtime for the Super Bowl can boost their stock price, at least in the short term. A business will typically announce their Super Bowl buy weeks prior to the big game, and even debut the advertisement early on social sites such as YouTube, Facebook and Twitter. Experts have found that any positive impact on a businesses stock price comes at the announcement of the Super Bowl spot, not after the spot runs. Whether or not an advertisement is successful is secondary to the impact it has on a business&#8217; exposure in the stock market. So yes, for an enterprise business that can afford the $4,000,000+ on advertising their investment is well worth it.</p>
<p>Whether you watch for the love of the game, advertising, or Peyton Manning––sit back, relax and enjoy the entertainment. It&#8217;ll be a long time until your next fantasy football draft night, and that&#8217;s depressing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>So, I&#8217;m a Marketing Nerd!</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/20/2014/so-im-a-marketing-nerd/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 14:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deadliest Catch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TLC]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3300</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[While watching Deadliest Catch on the Discovery Channel with my husband one night a few months ago, I started noticing a pattern.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While watching <i>Deadliest Catch</i> on the Discovery Channel with my husband one night a few months ago, I started noticing a pattern. During every commercial break, we were assaulted with commercials for men’s products: Ford F-150 pickup trucks, razors with four blades for a closer shave, Slim Jims–the list goes on.</p>
<p>I laughed out loud and said, &#8220;Oh man, I guess I&#8217;m not in the target market for <i>this </i>show. I love when that happens! I feel like I&#8217;m beating the system!&#8221; I expected my husband to chuckle and agree. Instead, he looked at me like I had three heads and said, &#8220;What?&#8221;</p>
<p>I realized, then, that not everybody in the world notices or pays attention when they&#8217;re being marketed to. For the first time, I felt special as a professional working in marketing.  Over the next few weeks I noticed that I really do find it fun to determine if I am inside or outside the target market for the products or services I&#8217;m being marketed.</p>
<p>Here are a few examples:</p>
<ul>
<li>On a random weekday home sick, I was watching <i>The Price is Right</i> on CBS. Denture cleaner–Nope!  Nice try, marketers, but thankfully I have all my teeth!  Scooter Store–Nope!  Emergency Life Alert button–Nope!  Pampers Cruisers diapers…OK, you got me on that one.  Touché, marketers.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Checking my Email: Groupon to Niagra Falls–Nope!  Adidas Men&#8217;s Golf Shoes–Nope!  50% off on preschool portraits…wait, let me see that one.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Watching <i>What Not to Wear</i> on TLC, while folding laundry on a Saturday afternoon: OK, I admit, I am 100% in the center circle of TLC&#8217;s target market diagram.  Whatever I see a commercial for, I want to buy, to watch, to check out.  Way to go, TLC, you found me!</li>
</ul>
<p>Marketers have a different way of looking at the world–of breaking down human behavior and trying to understand, at the core, what moves and motivates people. I am happy to consider myself part of this group of professionals. I feel at home in this little world because it&#8217;s really interesting to me. I am also happy that I&#8217;m not tasked with advertising to smart-ass marketers like myself!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pay-Per-Gaze: The future of advertising</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/13/2014/pay-per-gaze-the-future-of-advertising/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 19:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google Glass]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marty McFly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mashable]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pay-per-click]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3272</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[&#8220;Advertising is going to change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 100,&#8221; says Chris Taylor of Mashable OP-ED.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Advertising is going to change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 100,&#8221; <a title="says Chris Taylor of Mashable OP-ED." href="http://mashable.com/2013/08/15/the-future-of-advertising-pay-per-gaze-is-just-the-beginning/" target="_blank">says Chris Taylor of Mashable OP-ED. </a>In recent months Google, the world’s largest search engine provider, was granted a patent for a Google Glass-based ad system known as &#8220;pay-per-gaze.”</p>
<p>Google Glass is a wearable computer with an optical head-mounted display, which is being developed by Google as part of a mission to produce a mass-market ubiquitous computer.  To operate Google Glass, wearers simply tilt their head 30 degrees upward or tap the touchpad and say, &#8220;O.K., Glass.&#8221;  After the glasses are activated simple requests can be made such as, &#8220;Take a picture”, &#8220;Record a video&#8221;, or &#8220;Send a message to.”  That&#8217;s where &#8220;pay-per-gaze&#8221; comes in.  Google’s &#8220;pay-per-gaze&#8221; would charge advertisers for the number of times someone looks at their ad through Google Glass, the same way pay-per-click works today when users click on a link.  Google Glass contains technology that would track the direction the wearer’s pupils are pointing, and for how long they are gazing at a message.</p>
<p>This technology could potentially be a major risk for Google as people are infinitely exposed to advertising.  The money would flow in endlessly, and advertisers might second-guess themselves and their decision to invest in &#8220;pay-per-gaze.”  Still, this technology is something not even Marty McFly would have imagined.  Personally, I&#8217;ll stick with my Ray Bans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Actions Speak Louder Than Ads</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/11/2013/actions-speak-louder-than-ads/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 18:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coca Cola]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Haiyan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Phillipines]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Typhoon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Typhoon Haiyan]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3318</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Coca Cola put the brakes on any and all of their advertising spending last Monday in order to help those in need.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coca Cola put the brakes on any and all of their advertising spending last Monday in order to help those in need. How does this work? Well, the sugary-sweet beverage company decided to take all the money they would have spent on advertising and pass it along to aid in the relief and rebuilding efforts in the Philippines after Typhoon Haiyan.</p>
<p>Not only does this story warm the cockles of my heart, but it&#8217;s also nice to see a major business setting such a good example for the rest of the nation (and the world). As a trained &#8220;communicator,&#8221; I&#8217;d venture to guess no one will miss Coke&#8217;s advertisements this holiday season—in fact, I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if this soda-pushing powerhouse sees an increase in sales as a result of such positive publicity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Modern Family, and What it Means for Advertisers</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/02/2013/the-modern-family-and-what-it-means-for-advertisers/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[modern family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proctor & Gamble]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thanksgiving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3322</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey. I prepared with two practice rounds in early November, roasting whole chickens for my husband and me. I was ready.</p>
<p>On the big day, as my dad read each instruction for turkey prep–remove gizzards, rinse turkey, pat dry, lay on roasting rack, rub salt–<del cite="mailto:Michael%20Garcia" datetime="2013-12-02T09:23"></del>a refrain began to take shape. “Oh, Jordy normally does that part,” I kept saying.</p>
<p>My mom, supervising from the sidelines had caught on to what my husband, to date, hasn’t. “What exactly do <i>you </i>do to cook if Jordy does all this work?”* Oops, I’d been caught. Caught in the act of being a Modern Family.</p>
<p>With both of us working (and two dogs to care for), the “traditional” roles are thrown out the window in my household. We contribute equally (or so I’ve duped my husband into thinking, hehe) when it comes to the household chores. I do my share, but he has taken on a wide range of household tasks, from cooking, to vacuuming, and (in my greatest victory of all), grocery shopping.  On and on his list goes, our modern roles taking shape before our (and my mother’s) very eyes.</p>
<p>The other group to have caught on to the modern family? Tide detergent. Over the holiday weekend, I watched both a holiday movie marathon on Lifetime AND a thrilling Villanova basketball game (victory over Kansas!) on NBC Sports. I saw more Tide laundry detergent commercials on the latter, clearly targeted towards husbands who help around the house. Slowly, I’ve been noticing these ads cropping up. Their messages are heartwarming and humorous, and I love what Proctor &amp; Gamble has done to get there.</p>
<p>Tide and P&amp;G went right back to the basics. They got to know their audience, all over again. It may not be the same audience it’s been since its introduction 67 years ago, and that’s okay. It is one thing to stay where your audience is–social media, mobile devices, Netflix–but entirely  another thing to truly know who your audience is now and will be down the road. It takes work, it takes research, and it takes the ability to not only accept change but to capitalize on it.</p>
<p>Kudos, Tide. I can’t wait to see what happens next time “laundry detergent” is on the grocery list.</p>
<p>*In case you’ve been wondering, my role in the chicken and turkey cooking comes in once the gross handling of raw fowl is complete, and I can season, stuff, smother it in butter and spices, and place it in the oven.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hey, you&#8217;re walking on my ad!</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/01/2013/hey-youre-walking-on-my-ad-2/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 15:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[print]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3083</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I came across a cascading escalator advertisement the other day.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I came across a cascading escalator advertisement the other day. The ad was rather simple, directing foot traffic to a nearby store, but I appreciated its unconventional approach. It got me thinking about all the clever ways that functional, everyday items are being brought into the fold of strategic advertising.</p>
<p><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-3084" alt="escalator02" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/escalator02-193x220.jpg" width="193" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/escalator02-193x220.jpg 193w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/escalator02.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 193px) 100vw, 193px" /></p>
<p>Now more than ever, advertising no longer ends with the conventional billboard or printed page (although they still have their place). Bourgeoning creativity mixed with seemingly boundless possibilities has brought us to an exciting and inventive period of advertising. The world is a canvas that agencies are painting in clever, thought-provoking ways. Should the message be right and the position advantageous, look out: no escalator, street light or park bench is safe!</p>
<p>Here are some other <a href="http://www.creativeguerrillamarketing.com/guerrilla-marketing/unconventional-outdoor-advertising/" target="_blank">really cool examples</a> of unconventional guerrilla advertising tactics.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The fight for the bottom</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/23/2013/the-fight-for-the-bottom/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 15:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3073</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Since I’ve started working on online advertising, the belief has been that you want your ads as close to the top of the page as possible.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since I’ve started working on online advertising, the belief has been that you want your ads as close to the top of the page as possible. These above-the-fold ads are typically more expensive to purchase as they are thought to be the most premium positions on the page for viewers.</p>
<p>However, the <em>Washington Post</em> recently conducted research that showed it’s the ads more toward the bottom that actually perform the best. Why? Because people have become so accustomed to landing on a webpage and immediately scrolling down to the content they are looking for.</p>
<p>I haven’t seen the published report yet, but as an advertiser, this new insight is exciting for the future of online advertising. What are innovative ways we can reach visitors to break up their banner blindness? What new units will publishers offer to get visitor attention? How will this research affect pricing and media buying moving forward?</p>
<p>Read more on the study <a href="http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/ads-above-fold-are-not-more-viewable-151331" target="_blank">here.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WARNING: 230,000+ insects were harmed in the making of this ad</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/05/31/2013/230000-insects/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 22:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[billboards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pest control]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=2530</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Today&#8217;s creative inspiration is brought to you by Alexandra Pickel, our Director of Branding and all-around &#8220;bug gal.&#8221; Alex spotted an insecticide company that&#8217;s taking their advertising to the next level with killer messaging that really sticks.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><img class="size-full wp-image-2531 aligncenter" alt="Orphea billboard" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/orphea_outdoor_fubiz-640x384.jpg" width="640" height="384" /></p>
<p>Today&#8217;s creative inspiration is brought to you by <a title="Alexandra Pickel" href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/people/alexandra-pickel/">Alexandra Pickel</a>, our Director of Branding and all-around &#8220;bug gal.&#8221; Alex spotted an insecticide company that&#8217;s taking their advertising to the next level with killer messaging that really sticks. Orphea4D insecticide decided to transform an ordinary billboard into a giant insect trap for some real-life pest protection. Pretty incredible, huh? We certainly thought so!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Forget the box, think outside the oven</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/05/13/2013/forget-the-box-think-outside-the-oven/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 19:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[creativity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=2542</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Inspiration is everywhere.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2543" alt="bus shelter" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/6a00d8341c51c053ef0147e18aa1b9970b-450wi.134840.jpeg" width="425" height="340" /></p>
<p>Inspiration is everywhere. Sometimes, all we have to do is look up.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/people/jordy-pickel/">Jordy Pickel</a>, FVM&#8217;s Director of Digital Development, spotted this article about how a local coffee company is warming Minnesotans, one bus shelter at a time.</p>
<p>Thanks, Jordy! Maybe this will inspire the FVM team to cook up some creative advertising recipes of our own.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter is advancing: Are you?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/05/2012/twitter-is-advancing-are-you/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 18:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=2416</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The debate over Twitter’s place in modern day culture is complex –some people mock it and some people tweet it.  But one thing’s for sure: businesses are benefitting immensely from the social networking site.  Without a doubt, Twitter has allowed businesses to grow their brands, extend customer service, boost SEO performance and the list goes [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The debate over Twitter’s place in modern day culture is complex –some people mock it and some people tweet it.  But one thing’s for sure: businesses are benefitting immensely from the social networking site.  Without a doubt, Twitter has allowed businesses to grow their brands, extend customer service, boost SEO performance and the list goes on.  Whether you’re the type of person who scans Twitter every hour for celebrity perspectives on life or you’re doing life just fine without Twitter , you will have difficulty in trying to argue against Twitter’s long list of benefits to a business’s success.</p>
<p>We can tackle all the specific benefits more in-depth at another time (or visit this <a href="http://www.ragan.com/Main/Articles/15_business_benefits_of_Twitter__44058.aspx">Ragan article</a> for a quick review), but what I want to convey immediately is that <strong>now</strong> is the time for businesses to immerse themselves.  There’s a new door opening to join (if you haven’t already) or to improve your Twitter ROI.</p>
<h2>Twitter is changing in big ways, fast</h2>
<p>In December, Twitter launched branded pages.  If you are unaware of this development, you’ll want to review Twitter’s <a href="https://business.twitter.com/advertise/enhanced-profile/">Enhanced Profile</a> help page.  Basically, in December, Twitter launched a branded page as an option, which “increases your brand’s Twitter presence by prominently featuring your most important content and visually branding your page.”</p>
<p>With the enhanced profile pages in mind, Twitter is now moving forward with a new focus on creating a new “experience,” both for businesses and their customers.  In my mind two major developments capture this new focus entirely.</p>
<h3>1. The Open Platform</h3>
<p>Twitter’s end goal with an open platform is to create new ways for customers to engage with your brand.  The industry’s majority agrees with <a href="http://www.readwriteweb.com/archives/author/richard-macmanus.php">Richard Macmanus</a> in that open web services is a major web trend picking up and Twitter’s new API (Application Program Inteface) is an ideal platform to see the advantages.  By opening their platform to independent developers, Twitter allows “brands to create deeper interactions with consumers through custom experiences,” says Mashable’s David Clarke.  From smaller mobile applications to versions of Twitter visually recreated, developers now have the capability to build onto Twitter’s infrastructure and expand the user’s experience exponentially.  A brand is not limited to its look and feel living on Twitter.  You can now combine Twitter’s functions with your own ideas.  Biz Stone says &#8220;The API has been … inarguably, the most important thing we’ve done with Twitter.”</p>
<h3>2. T-Commerce</h3>
<p>Facebook failed at it, now Twitter will attempt to succeed where it’s adversary failed.  E-commerce on Twitter has pronounced itself loud and clear just recently with multiple real opportunities for e-commerce companies that you’ve probably overlooked.</p>
<ul>
<li>First and foremost, the most easily forgotten, the <strong>call-to-action</strong>: you must provide a link in every tweet.  If someone is interested in a product or service, make sure you’ve given them a way to act.</li>
<li>Provide great customer service. Everything is public, so customers will gain trust that you will stand by your offerings.</li>
<li>Pay on Twitter.  Yes, customers can now pay directly via Twitter.  This will expedite purchasing process and reduce consumer hesitation.  Look into <a href="http://chirpify.com/">Cherpify</a> and Twitpay.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you currently using Twitter to help grow your business and reach customers?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
