<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>account planning &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/account-planning/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Are Super Bowl Ads Worth The Investment?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/30/2014/are-super-bowl-ads-worth-the-investment/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commercials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl XLVIII]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3422</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event. It&#8217;s the most watched program of the year. Even those who have no idea who the Denver Broncos or the Seattle Seahawks are will tune in. Why? Typically it&#8217;s because everyone else is doing it, but another reason is the advertising. In 2013, the average cost of a 30-second spot was $4 million. The effectiveness of these ads in boosting a company&#8217;s sales has been in question over the past few years. Experts have compared the investment of the cost of an ad vs. overall increased revenue after the Super Bowl, and it shows little to no change. Forbes magazine claims that most companies would be better off airing 10 commercials at $400,000 each, to increase repetition. Forbes also claims that Super Bowl Ads have become memorible for presentation, but forgettable in terms of persuasion.</p>
<p>The University of Wisconsin-Eau Claire <a href="http://www.uwec.edu/newsbureau/release/past/2000/00-01/010400super.html">did a study of over 500 Super Bowl spots that ran between 2000 and 2009</a>, and found that many did not work. Some Super Bowl Ads fail due to the fact that people typically recall the story, but not the product. More often than not, Super Bowl ads attempt to deliver broad humor for entertainment purposes, rather than sell the product. Sometimes companies will enlist celebrities to sponsor their Super Bowl Ad, but experts have also concluded this tactic is ineffective as the celebrity may lack relevance to the product. Still the question must be asked, is the Super Bowl ad worth the investment?</p>
<p>Forbes magazine says yes.</p>
<p>The real reason companies invest in Super Bowl spots is because the announcement of buying airtime for the Super Bowl can boost their stock price, at least in the short term. A business will typically announce their Super Bowl buy weeks prior to the big game, and even debut the advertisement early on social sites such as YouTube, Facebook and Twitter. Experts have found that any positive impact on a businesses stock price comes at the announcement of the Super Bowl spot, not after the spot runs. Whether or not an advertisement is successful is secondary to the impact it has on a business&#8217; exposure in the stock market. So yes, for an enterprise business that can afford the $4,000,000+ on advertising their investment is well worth it.</p>
<p>Whether you watch for the love of the game, advertising, or Peyton Manning––sit back, relax and enjoy the entertainment. It&#8217;ll be a long time until your next fantasy football draft night, and that&#8217;s depressing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How a starfish sparked an idea</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/02/2013/how-a-starfish-sparked-an-idea/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 17:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3066</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I was beaming.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="attachment_3104" style="max-width: 175px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img class="size-medium wp-image-3104" alt="Isn't she adorable?!" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-165x220.jpeg" width="165" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-165x220.jpeg 165w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-768x1024.jpeg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 165px) 100vw, 165px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Isn&#8217;t she adorable?!</p></div>
<p>I was beaming. My favorite family member (don’t tell my husband), Macy, had just graduated from Puppy Kindergarten with flying colors, and she was totally into the toy I bought her for a congratulatory present. So into it, in fact, that I immediately logged on to the company’s website to hunt for more. Because, you know, her 5 ½-month birthday is just around the corner.</p>
<p>And there it was: “Become a Dog Toy Tester.” The deal was, sign up to receive four toys a year. Agree to write a review and you get those toys at 40% off. 40% off toys Macy loves? And I get to share stories of my puppy with the entire world? What’s not to love?</p>
<p>At that exact same time, our B2B client was looking to increase reviews of products on their website. The strategy was an Apple product giveaway—always a great incentive, but what about giving the actual products away at a discount in return for a review? You better believe that in the long run, it’s going to sell more product. Here’s why it works:</p>
<p>1. It shows customers you value their opinion, which creates loyalty.<br />
2. It gives customers more of what they need. Sure, an iPad mini is great, but that product I was going to buy anyway? I need that.<br />
3. The discount encourages customers to try new products—if it doesn’t work out, at least they didn’t pay full price.<br />
4. It’s less hassle on your end. No need to run complex sweepstakes giveaways, partner with third parties, jump through legal hoops, or figure out complex rules.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A to-do list app</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/16/2013/a-to-do-list-app/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 15:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3090</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[As an account exec, I’m not only responsible for client communication—there’s a lot of internal communication and project management to juggle, too.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As an account exec, I’m not only responsible for client communication—there’s a lot of internal communication and project management to juggle, too. With an endless list of things to manage, I decided to test drive the Asana project management app. It’s an extremely intuitive tool for traffic, project and account managers—an interactive alternative to the daily written checklist.</p>
<p>I found the app to be useful as I was able to track projects in a mobile environment as I moved throughout the agency and spoke to different people involved in my projects. The app’s coolest feature was its ability to seamlessly update itself through several sources without need for refreshing. For example, as I clicked &#8220;project complete&#8221; on my iPhone, it would update itself on the desktop version, too.</p>
<p>Another helpful feature is &#8220;team sharing&#8221;. If my co-workers were to download the app and enter their individual projects, we could share access to each other’s environments and answer status questions, without having to physically tracking each other down.</p>
<p>Of course, FVM is a small, close-knit agency. The Keurig machine sits farther away from me than the creative department, so I’ll continue using my manual method of project management. But for those working in larger agencies, this app could be extremely helpful.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter is advancing: Are you?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/05/2012/twitter-is-advancing-are-you/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 18:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=2416</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The debate over Twitter’s place in modern day culture is complex –some people mock it and some people tweet it.  But one thing’s for sure: businesses are benefitting immensely from the social networking site.  Without a doubt, Twitter has allowed businesses to grow their brands, extend customer service, boost SEO performance and the list goes [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The debate over Twitter’s place in modern day culture is complex –some people mock it and some people tweet it.  But one thing’s for sure: businesses are benefitting immensely from the social networking site.  Without a doubt, Twitter has allowed businesses to grow their brands, extend customer service, boost SEO performance and the list goes on.  Whether you’re the type of person who scans Twitter every hour for celebrity perspectives on life or you’re doing life just fine without Twitter , you will have difficulty in trying to argue against Twitter’s long list of benefits to a business’s success.</p>
<p>We can tackle all the specific benefits more in-depth at another time (or visit this <a href="http://www.ragan.com/Main/Articles/15_business_benefits_of_Twitter__44058.aspx">Ragan article</a> for a quick review), but what I want to convey immediately is that <strong>now</strong> is the time for businesses to immerse themselves.  There’s a new door opening to join (if you haven’t already) or to improve your Twitter ROI.</p>
<h2>Twitter is changing in big ways, fast</h2>
<p>In December, Twitter launched branded pages.  If you are unaware of this development, you’ll want to review Twitter’s <a href="https://business.twitter.com/advertise/enhanced-profile/">Enhanced Profile</a> help page.  Basically, in December, Twitter launched a branded page as an option, which “increases your brand’s Twitter presence by prominently featuring your most important content and visually branding your page.”</p>
<p>With the enhanced profile pages in mind, Twitter is now moving forward with a new focus on creating a new “experience,” both for businesses and their customers.  In my mind two major developments capture this new focus entirely.</p>
<h3>1. The Open Platform</h3>
<p>Twitter’s end goal with an open platform is to create new ways for customers to engage with your brand.  The industry’s majority agrees with <a href="http://www.readwriteweb.com/archives/author/richard-macmanus.php">Richard Macmanus</a> in that open web services is a major web trend picking up and Twitter’s new API (Application Program Inteface) is an ideal platform to see the advantages.  By opening their platform to independent developers, Twitter allows “brands to create deeper interactions with consumers through custom experiences,” says Mashable’s David Clarke.  From smaller mobile applications to versions of Twitter visually recreated, developers now have the capability to build onto Twitter’s infrastructure and expand the user’s experience exponentially.  A brand is not limited to its look and feel living on Twitter.  You can now combine Twitter’s functions with your own ideas.  Biz Stone says &#8220;The API has been … inarguably, the most important thing we’ve done with Twitter.”</p>
<h3>2. T-Commerce</h3>
<p>Facebook failed at it, now Twitter will attempt to succeed where it’s adversary failed.  E-commerce on Twitter has pronounced itself loud and clear just recently with multiple real opportunities for e-commerce companies that you’ve probably overlooked.</p>
<ul>
<li>First and foremost, the most easily forgotten, the <strong>call-to-action</strong>: you must provide a link in every tweet.  If someone is interested in a product or service, make sure you’ve given them a way to act.</li>
<li>Provide great customer service. Everything is public, so customers will gain trust that you will stand by your offerings.</li>
<li>Pay on Twitter.  Yes, customers can now pay directly via Twitter.  This will expedite purchasing process and reduce consumer hesitation.  Look into <a href="http://chirpify.com/">Cherpify</a> and Twitpay.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you currently using Twitter to help grow your business and reach customers?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
