<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>illustration &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/illustration/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The art of illustration in web design</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/08/15/2014/the-art-of-illustration-in-web-design/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 13:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4135</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I’ve always tried to be an individualist when it comes to design.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I’ve always tried to be an individualist when it comes to design. From the 3-year-old child who drew a giant fish on our family rug while no one was watching, right through to my current status as grey-haired designer, the greatest outlet for this expression of independent thought has been illustration.</p>
<p>For me, the written word felt incomplete at times without an image to support it. Illustration – the visual or pictorial companion to words – helps me understand an idea more completely. It also can be a hook that pulls you into a story.</p>
<p>Makes sense in terms of web design, doesn’t it? But it can be a hard sell. The commercial world’s easy solution is to reach for stock photos and use tidy, linear design. Illustration seems to have been relegated to something that stands for arty-vagueness, abstraction, decoration, and is often seen as risky. But this just isn’t the case, and it’s time for more brands to take a leap.</p>
<h2></h2>
<h2><strong>Top 5</strong></h2>
<p>Not every brand or web design is suited to illustration, but when there is an opportunity, you should try it. Here’s five reasons why.</p>
<h3><strong>1. This time, it’s personal</strong></h3>
<p>In the saturation of samey-samey stock imagery, it’s good to stand out as a personality, as something exclusive. Is your message different? Is your product? Are your people? They should be. And so should your imagery. It is probably easier and cheaper to go with stock imagery or even stock illustration, then add a logo, a tag, some copy, and go live, all in time for dinner. It can be effective and achieve results, but it’s design by numbers, and may leave your brand invisible. What do polished, airbrushed, generic images of fake people give the impression of? You’ve got it! And some other site has it too.</p>
<div id="attachment_4141" style="max-width: 490px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4141" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/k4lab.jpg" alt="http://www.k4lab.info/" width="480" height="320" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/k4lab.jpg 480w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/k4lab-220x146.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 480px) 100vw, 480px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://www.k4lab.info/</p></div>
<h3><strong>2. Never underestimate the importance of having fun</strong></h3>
<p>People want to relate to brands, and adding even a hint of playfulness can make you more approachable. Fun, lively imagery can energize a brand, messaging, or copy and make you more exciting. Illustrations can be a joy to create, and the feel-good emotion coming from this process can transfer to the reader/viewer.</p>
<div id="attachment_4142" style="max-width: 625px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4142" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/22.jpg" alt="https://booki.sh/ " width="615" height="429" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/22.jpg 615w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/22-220x153.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 615px) 100vw, 615px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">https://booki.sh/</p></div>
<p>Even using illustrated elements in something as standard as website bios, for example, can add character.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4175" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/cv-biopics-3.jpg" alt="" width="5513" height="2161" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/cv-biopics-3.jpg 5513w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/cv-biopics-3-220x86.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/cv-biopics-3-1024x401.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 5513px) 100vw, 5513px" /></p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4176" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/sean3.jpg" alt="" width="1656" height="2016" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/sean3.jpg 1656w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/sean3-180x220.jpg 180w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/sean3-841x1024.jpg 841w" sizes="(max-width: 1656px) 100vw, 1656px" /><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4177" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/fvm-biopics-3.jpg" alt="Print" width="5004" height="2161" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-biopics-3.jpg 5004w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-biopics-3-220x95.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/fvm-biopics-3-1024x442.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 5004px) 100vw, 5004px" /></p>
<p>And fun doesn’t have to mean unsophisticated.</p>
<div id="attachment_4156" style="max-width: 469px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4156" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/537e1f5356d3b.jpeg" alt="http://pioneers.brancottestate.com/" width="459" height="328" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/537e1f5356d3b.jpeg 459w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/537e1f5356d3b-220x157.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 459px) 100vw, 459px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://pioneers.brancottestate.com/</p></div>
<h3><strong>3. We’re engaged!</strong></h3>
<p>In the Internet age our attention spans are shorter, calendars have become more packed, blah, blah, blah. You’ve heard it before, and it’s true. Everyone online has a short amount of time to grab your attention. Make an impact with something unique and interesting that enhances your visibility.</p>
<div id="attachment_4178" style="max-width: 976px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-4178 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Untitled1.png" alt="http://summer.tcm.com/" width="966" height="657" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled1.png 966w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled1-220x149.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 966px) 100vw, 966px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://summer.tcm.com/</p></div>
<div id="attachment_4179" style="max-width: 976px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="wp-image-4179 size-full" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Untitled2.png" alt="http://whiterabbitbeer.com.au/" width="966" height="600" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled2.png 966w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Untitled2-220x136.png 220w" sizes="(max-width: 966px) 100vw, 966px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://whiterabbitbeer.com.au/</p></div>
<p>From a more technical perspective, illustration can be more striking by eliminating background distractions and zeroing in on the point. The use of color can influence mood, and a reduced palette can simplify, as it requires less thought from the reader.</p>
<div id="attachment_4146" style="max-width: 467px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4146" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/enjoythis2.jpg" alt="http://enjoythis.co.uk/" width="457" height="250" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/enjoythis2.jpg 457w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/enjoythis2-220x120.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 457px) 100vw, 457px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://enjoythis.co.uk/</p></div>
<h3><strong>4. Beyond boundaries</strong></h3>
<p>With the ability to alter reality, illustration can pique interest. Distorting reality to suit your needs can make people think differently. Your website can be an interactive storybook; your landing page can be its own world; your CEO can be an alien (!). You can truly break the rules, create a different experience, stand apart, and deliver your message in an unconventional way.</p>
<div id="attachment_4145" style="max-width: 469px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4145" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/53e216d80e9f3.jpeg" alt="http://www.rtolymp.ru/" width="459" height="328" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/53e216d80e9f3.jpeg 459w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/53e216d80e9f3-220x157.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 459px) 100vw, 459px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://www.rtolymp.ru/</p></div>
<div id="attachment_4148" style="max-width: 469px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4148" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/537a7426aea97.jpeg" alt="http://www.bevisionare.com/" width="459" height="328" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/537a7426aea97.jpeg 459w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/537a7426aea97-220x157.jpeg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 459px) 100vw, 459px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">http://www.bevisionare.com/</p></div>
<h3><strong>5. Break it down now</strong></h3>
<p>Rather than trying to digest a large expanse of gray copy, people prefer to be given information in colorful, tasty, bite-size pieces. Expressive, creative visualization can help create punctuation and add clarity to even the most complicated messages and technical information. Take something as basic as statistics. In this example, the typography becomes the illustration and survey percentages take center stage, telling the story visually.</p>
<div id="attachment_4153" style="max-width: 2073px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-full wp-image-4153" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/CV-cio-data-woes-infographic.jpg" alt="CommVault 'Data Woes' infographic" width="2063" height="4276" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/CV-cio-data-woes-infographic.jpg 2063w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/CV-cio-data-woes-infographic-106x220.jpg 106w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/CV-cio-data-woes-infographic-494x1024.jpg 494w" sizes="(max-width: 2063px) 100vw, 2063px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">CommVault &#8216;Data Woes&#8217; infographic</p></div>
<h2></h2>
<h2><strong>Danger! Hand-crafted</strong></h2>
<p>Clients presented with the idea of illustration are concerned about cost, control, and breaking from the norm. Unless you’re hiring Milton Glazer (not that he’d agree to it, even if you did have the money), there’s no shortage of talent at a reasonable price, who will give the client control, refine until everyone is happy, and produce something memorable that sets the brand apart.</p>
<h2></h2>
<h2><strong>Get the best out of your illustrator</strong></h2>
<p>Still fazed? Don’t be. A good illustrator is only a good illustrator because they’re a good interpreter, so try to have some questions answered and ideas formed before you sit down and open a dialogue. Who is the audience? What message do you want to convey? What do you want people to experience? How do you want them to feel? What is your goal? What are you trying to do? Can the illustration be whimsical or humorous? Can it be a literal representation or an abstraction? Has a precedent been set in terms of color, style, mood, or is it wide open?</p>
<p>Bring examples or a “mood board” of websites, photography, or artwork inspiration.</p>
<p>Once the illustrator has a grasp on what you’re looking for, set them free!</p>
<p>They’ll probably create something that you could never have imagined. It may even inspire other elements such as messaging or logo. What is for certain is that custom illustration will make you more distinctive, recognizable, and memorable. It will make you an individualist.</p>
<p><em>Sources: http://www.awwwards.com/websites/illustration/</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doodling</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/02/07/2014/doodling/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[art direction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doodling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3368</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ve always doodled.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve always doodled. I doodle in meetings and when I&#8217;m on the phone. Some of my doodles blossom into full-fledged drawings. At my previous job, this practice was frowned upon. The boss thought I wasn&#8217;t paying attention. But I was. My current bosses accept and even encourage it. This blog post will provide you, the reader, with different levels of detail about this topic, broken down as follows:</p>
<p><b>For the person who thinks reading a blog is like a homework assignment and just wants to look at pictures of some of the doodles that I&#8217;ve made:</b></p>
<p><b>For the person who can&#8217;t be bothered reading long, boring blog posts, read this:</b></p>
<p>Doodling helps people retain information during meetings (stop here) (or, for the person that is skeptical and would like a little more clarification):</p>
<p><b>For the person who is skeptical and just wants a little more detail:</b></p>
<p>When you doodle, you don&#8217;t daydream. Daydreaming may seem absentminded and pointless, but it actually demands a lot of the brain&#8217;s processing power. You start daydreaming about a vacation, which leads you to think about potential destinations, how you would pay for the trip, whether you could get the flight upgraded, how you might score a bigger hotel room. These cognitions require what psychologists call &#8220;executive functioning&#8221; — for example, planning for the future and comparing costs and benefits.</p>
<p>Doodling, in contrast, requires very few executive resources but just enough cognitive effort to keep you from daydreaming, which — if unchecked — will jump-start activity in cortical networks that will keep you from remembering what&#8217;s going on. Doodling forces your brain to expend just enough energy to stop it from daydreaming but not so much that you don&#8217;t pay attention.  (stop here) (or, for entire articles on the subject):</p>
<p><b>For the person who wants to read entire articles on the subject:</b></p>
<p><a href="http://content.time.com/time/health/article/0,8599,1882127,00.html#ixzz2mXaZ1ClX">http://content.time.com/time/health/article/0,8599,1882127,00.html#ixzz2mXaZ1Cl</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2012/08/03/i-draw-pictures-all-day">http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2012/08/03/i-draw-pictures-all-day</a>/</p>
<p><a href="http://www.cnn.com/2013/10/03/business/doodlilng-in-a-meeting-drawing">http://www.cnn.com/2013/10/03/business/doodlilng-in-a-meeting-drawing</a>/</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simpana 10 Launch</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/18/2013/simpana-10-launch/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 15:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[demand generation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sales enablement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design & development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3155</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When CommVault released their latest and greatest software, Simpana 10, FVM answered with an innovative content strategy and multi-media launch.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When CommVault released their latest and greatest software, Simpana 10, FVM answered with an innovative content strategy and multi-media launch. We used digital media to drive the IT world to a content-packed interactive microsite—including, demos, videos, literature, partner interviews and more—which was explored for an average of 10 minutes per visit. The splash was felt globally and established the product as an industry leader.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TandD Foods</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/16/2013/tandd-foods/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 16:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3160</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Regulatory policies are complicated for food service businesses.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Regulatory policies are complicated for food service businesses. So when Japan-based data management company TandD Foods wanted to break into the U.S. market, FVM took a unique approach. Rather than worry about complexity, we chose to focus on a simple solution: the easiest way to keep perishable food safe and compliance in check. We targeted decision makers through an integrated digital strategy, topped with refreshed, relevant branding.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Termidor HE Launch</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/10/2013/termidor-he-launch/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 17:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research & intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sales enablement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tradeshow planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3173</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When BASF made their best even better, they had to go epic.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When BASF made their best even better, they had to go epic. FVM devised a three-phase approach to launch the new formulation of the most successful liquid termiticide ever—Termidor HE. By blending traditional, digital and social tactics—including the pest control industry’s first product launch webcast—we cost-effectively reached professionals nationwide, culminating in a hugely successful rollout.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arrrrgh, Matey!</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/20/2013/arrrrgh-matey/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 17:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[logo design]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3068</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Every month or two I sit down at my computer and go on Ebay, Amazon, Facebook and Google Images to see my work displayed.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every month or two I sit down at my computer and go on Ebay, Amazon, Facebook and Google Images to see my work displayed.</p>
<p>Am I proud? Yes. Annoyed? Immensely.</p>
<p>A few years ago, I designed some images of fish and thought it would be fun to reproduce them as decals to sell. What I never would have anticipated was that others would pillage my designs from the internet to sell as their own or to promote their businesses, sometimes in ways I never would have imagined. My coworkers say I should be flattered when others do this, after all, they must really like my designs. Every time I see it happen, my heart drops. I could be creating new work, but instead I spend my time navigating the internet in search of my stolen gems. As a designer, the lure of the treasures that are readily available to us on the intenet is quite tempting. All it takes is a right click (control/click if you’re old school) and what you see magically appears on your desktop to do with as you please. We’ve probably all done it at one time or another—I’m no exception. You hear about internet piracy all of the time but it never really resonates until it lands on your shore.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-3101" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo.JPG-e1381511543132.jpeg" alt="photo.JPG" width="240" height="320" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo.JPG-e1381511543132.jpeg 240w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo.JPG-e1381511543132-165x220.jpeg 165w" sizes="(max-width: 240px) 100vw, 240px" /></p>
<p>Come on people what the hell does a striped bass have to do with carpet anyway?</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Remembering Professor Anliker</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/14/2013/remembering-professor-anliker/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 18:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[art direction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3112</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[These days, college graduates can boast that they are a proud owner of a degree in computer design.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>These days, college graduates can boast that they are a proud owner of a degree in computer design. That is like having a degree in pencil design. After all, the computer is also a tool to create visual art. Who is teaching these students about how to compose an image; to utilize the visual elements; to even understand what the visual elements are; to understand typography; to understand color concepts; to draw? I consider myself very fortunate to have received superior training in all of those areas, and so much more, largely in one classroom/studio and under the direction of one remarkable person. His name is professor Roger Anliker, and he passed away on September 25 at the age of 89.</p>
<div id="attachment_3113" style="max-width: 230px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img class="size-medium wp-image-3113" alt="Painting by Roger Anliker, self portrait, title and date unknown" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/roger-220x173.jpeg" width="220" height="173" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/roger-220x173.jpeg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/roger-1024x808.jpeg 1024w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/roger.jpeg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Painting by Roger Anliker, self portrait, title and date unknown</p></div>
<p>I took a drawing and painting class freshman year, and was introduced to the man who now comes up in my conversations almost daily. Professor Anliker gave demonstrations in class that were awe-inspiring. He read us passages from Nabokov while we worked. He had us compile lists of things that we would eagerly enter into our notebooks, often alphabetically starting from A. I can remember doing a list of structures and someone calling out chicken-coop for C; a list of flowers with bachelor button for B; a list of hats with snood or shako for S. Everything in the visual arts was based on a strong foundation with Roger. Drawing was first. In writing, he taught us, spelling comes first. That is the foundation. One cannot spell “creatively or artfully.”</p>
<p>He came into the studio on nights and weekends to design, construct, paint and decorate elaborate stages for the live model to integrate with. As he worked on these set-ups, he was always careful to use muted colors, earth tones, gentle shapes and arches, various screens and transparent screeds, all designed to enhance and support the human figure that was to inhabit the space, not detract from it.</p>
<p>He stayed after class to answer questions for students, but while most hurried off to get back to the dorms or leave, a friend and I stayed. Often hours would pass, with Professor Anliker patiently explaining a technical process or even going back to a demonstration. Although we were exhausted, we couldn’t help but think about how much education we were receiving for our tuition dollar. It was practically one-on-one training for hours and hours after everyone else had left.</p>
<p>He was always watching out for students, telling them when to complain to the University when our needs were not being met. He was a sharp critic, and could find flaws in almost anything. It made us work harder as not to disappoint him. He gave us advice from what colors look good on cars to how to eat properly. Even how to keep proper posture when ascending stairs by imagining a string attached to the top of your head being pulled taut as you lift each knee.</p>
<p>Every phase of the arts were covered in the eight courses that I took with Professor Anliker. It didn’t even matter what the course was called, pastel drawing, whatever. As long as I was in the class. He considered me such a fine student that he invited me and a friend over to his inner-sanctum for dinner some time after graduation. We were in awe. The paintings that we had only glimpsed in photos before were on well-lit walls all around his house in full splendor. I can remember the tuna salad he served had grapes in it, which I didn’t think would work, but I was so wrong. The beverage he served was about the best thing I ever tasted. He explained that it was comprised of five fruit juices in carefully measured amounts.</p>
<p>Hours went by that evening, with Professor Anliker explaining concepts to us in all fields, not just fine arts. Just when we thought the evening was over and we started heading for the door in sheer exhaustion, he invited us to sit down as he slid a record out of a sleeve and placed it on the turntable. A multiple-part spoken word record series of Dante’s Inferno started to crackle through the speakers. We started to discreetly slap ourselves, for our bodies could take no more and we were fighting with every ounce of energy to stay awake. We did not want to disappoint the master.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
