<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>copywriting &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/copywriting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What One-Liners Have Taught Me About Writing</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/06/2014/what-one-liners-have-taught-me-about-writing/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 17:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3304</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Jokes are beautiful.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">Jokes are beautiful. Done right, they fit together perfectly, like equations. Each word is a necessary and contributing part of the whole. They&#8217;re reduced until they are as concentrated as they can be, while still keeping their intended meaning. And, like equations, once you get past the basic structure, they say something pretty profound.</p>
<p>One-liners are jokes in their purest form. There’s no unnecessary context or stylistic stuff. When I&#8217;m writing copy, I want it to be <b>brief </b>and <b>engaging.</b> When I hear a great one-liner, those same two words come to mind.</p>
<p>Here are two of my favorites:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> <i>My one regret in life is that I am not someone else.</i></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">                                              -Woody Allen</p>
<p align="center"> <i>Those are my principles. If you don’t like them, I have others.</i></p>
<p align="center">                                                -Groucho Marx</p>
<p> They’re both 12 words.  Neither can be reduced any further without sacrificing meaning, and any additional words would weaken them. Both of them resonate, and speak to feelings we all share–in these cases, alienation and insecurity. Not to mention, they&#8217;re funny.</p>
<p>Great ads are the same way. In my experience, good copywriting takes all the product information, target market characteristics, and branding concerns into consideration, and puts out a simple, understandable message that creates an emotional response in the reader. It’s that easy, and it’s that hard.</p>
<p>Oh, by the way:</p>
<p align="center"><i>The story of my life is taking a while to get good.</i></p>
<p style="text-align: left;" align="center">That’s one of mine. It’s 12 words, and while it might not put me among the greats, it’s something I think is true, and it’s simply put. Is it funny? I hope so, otherwise it’s just a sad fact.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Univar ES Rebrand</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/11/18/2013/univar/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 17:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tradeshow planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design & development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3221</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Univar Environmental Sciences is widely known for providing top-quality chemical products, but their brand lacked humanity.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Univar Environmental Sciences is widely known for providing top-quality chemical products, but their brand lacked humanity. So, FVM engaged in research, asked some tough questions, and created an authentic and differentiated brand position—brought to life through vibrant design. The result: a stronger, warmer, more down-to-earth brand that showcased the human element so crucial to Univar’s success, and laid the foundation for all future marketing efforts.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>OCE Choose My Future</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/20/2013/oce-choose-my-future/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 14:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[email marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design & development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3147</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[What did the Office of Catholic Education do when they need to increase numbers at Catholic High Schools?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What did the Office of Catholic Education do when they need to increase numbers at Catholic High Schools? They called FVM and the full-fledged marketing and awareness campaign “Choose My Future” was born. Now in its third year, the enrollment-boosting campaign is email nurturing, content marketing and advertising at its best and can be seen on planes (over the Jersey shore), trains and buses across Philadelphia.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simpana 10 Launch</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/18/2013/simpana-10-launch/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 15:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[demand generation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sales enablement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web design & development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3155</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When CommVault released their latest and greatest software, Simpana 10, FVM answered with an innovative content strategy and multi-media launch.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When CommVault released their latest and greatest software, Simpana 10, FVM answered with an innovative content strategy and multi-media launch. We used digital media to drive the IT world to a content-packed interactive microsite—including, demos, videos, literature, partner interviews and more—which was explored for an average of 10 minutes per visit. The splash was felt globally and established the product as an industry leader.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TandD Foods</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/16/2013/tandd-foods/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 16:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3160</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Regulatory policies are complicated for food service businesses.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Regulatory policies are complicated for food service businesses. So when Japan-based data management company TandD Foods wanted to break into the U.S. market, FVM took a unique approach. Rather than worry about complexity, we chose to focus on a simple solution: the easiest way to keep perishable food safe and compliance in check. We targeted decision makers through an integrated digital strategy, topped with refreshed, relevant branding.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Termidor HE Launch</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/10/2013/termidor-he-launch/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 17:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordy Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[graphic design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[illustration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research & intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sales enablement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tradeshow planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?post_type=portfolio_post&#038;p=3173</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When BASF made their best even better, they had to go epic.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When BASF made their best even better, they had to go epic. FVM devised a three-phase approach to launch the new formulation of the most successful liquid termiticide ever—Termidor HE. By blending traditional, digital and social tactics—including the pest control industry’s first product launch webcast—we cost-effectively reached professionals nationwide, culminating in a hugely successful rollout.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digesting copy over lunch</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/03/2013/lunchtime-reading/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chipotle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=2993</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Lunch at Chipotle is always awesome.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lunch at Chipotle is always awesome. Today, it was especially awesome to see good ole fashioned words on paper telling an effective brand story in this impatient, digital world of ours. The burrito king’s cups and wrapping paper are playfully covered with musings about all-things-Chipotle, from the pleasure of foil licking to the reservoir of deliciousness at the bottom of each burrito. The kind of things that we Chipotle-lovers can relate to—and, more importantly, help to build brand loyalty.</p>
<p>Copy is still a powerful tool. You just need to seek out those rare moments when your audience is happy to read them. Like when they have a big, fat, juicy burrito in their hands.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Easy steps for effective writing</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/01/2013/easy-steps-for-effective-writing/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 18:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[copywriting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3009</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Want to be a more effective writer?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Want to be a more effective writer? Here are five tips to get you there.</p>
<p><strong>1. Keep it plain English</strong><br />
Write it like you’d speak it. It’s not about dumbing down – it’s about helping people understand what you’re saying on a first reading.</p>
<p><strong>2. Keep it short</strong><br />
Say the most with the fewest words possible. Why use 50 words when 10 will do? A great line from the classic <em>Elements of Style</em>: “A sentence should contain no unnecessary words, for the same reason a machine should have no unnecessary parts.”</p>
<p><strong>3. Keep it active</strong><br />
Active writing involves the reader. For example, “your email was received by us yesterday” is passive and distant. Whereas, “we received your email yesterday” is active and immediate.</p>
<p><strong>4. Keep the pace</strong><br />
If one sentence has, say, 15 words in it, write a shorter one after it. Like this one. It helps keep the pace and draws your reader through.</p>
<p><strong>5. Keep it relevant</strong><br />
Always put yourself in the reader’s shoes. What’s in it for them? Make sure you give them a reason to keep reading.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
