<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Brand &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/brand/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Amazon takes the feminine approach</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/02/14/2014/untitled-ar-post/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 18:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3477</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It may have been named for the world’s longest river, but it should have been named for the mythological Amazon––tall, beautiful, striking, and most importantly, with a female brain.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It may have been named for the world’s longest river, but it <i>should</i> have been named for the mythological Amazon––tall, beautiful, striking, and most importantly, with a female brain.</p>
<p>She’s tall: her wingspan reaches from my front porch, to my living room TV, to my nightstand. Whether it&#8217;s a package arriving, Downton Abbey on the Prime channel on the Roku, or the latest dystopian society trilogy on my Kindle, this Amazon is large enough to reach every facet of my home.</p>
<p>She’s beautiful: have you been on the site recently? Her simple form and elegance jumps out from the minute I type in the URL all the way to when I check out. The simple navigation, beautiful photographs, and page layouts give me the information I need without having to hunt for it, and the confirmation page is simple and speedy.</p>
<p>She’s striking: it’s truly unbelievable what this warrior can do. She knows my favorites and anticipates what I&#8217;ll want next. Then, she gets it into my hands with one mouse click and (at most) two days&#8217; time.</p>
<p>But underlying her ability to perform her task so beautifully? A female brain: organized, logical, and on top of every detail. And, in true Amazon warrior fashion, she wasn’t afraid to remind me.</p>
<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/98BIu9dpwHU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Sure, Amazon lets you know through this commercial that they are anticipating the latest and greatest technology, and plants the seed that if anyone could do it, they could. But even more strikingly, they&#8217;re reminding you that they have already perfected their craft.</p>
<p>The most telling piece of this ad is not at 0:33 when the product is loaded into the drone, but everything before that. Here, Amazon gives us a sneak peak at what makes drone delivery possible. It just so happens to also make 10-day, 7-day, 2-day and 1-day delivery possible. It doesn’t matter whether the product leaving the warehouse gets on a drone, a truck, or a donkey. What matters is how quickly and accurately it left the warehouse. They’ll do it right in the future, because they’re doing it right now.</p>
<p>And so Amazon has reminded us of their core, and in so doing reminded us to never forget ours. Despite where your brand goes, knowing its core and sticking to it no matter what will help you go a long way….maybe all the way down the Amazon river.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
