<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>brand workshop &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/brand-workshop/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Modern Family, and What it Means for Advertisers</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/02/2013/the-modern-family-and-what-it-means-for-advertisers/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[modern family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proctor & Gamble]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thanksgiving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3322</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey. I prepared with two practice rounds in early November, roasting whole chickens for my husband and me. I was ready.</p>
<p>On the big day, as my dad read each instruction for turkey prep–remove gizzards, rinse turkey, pat dry, lay on roasting rack, rub salt–<del cite="mailto:Michael%20Garcia" datetime="2013-12-02T09:23"></del>a refrain began to take shape. “Oh, Jordy normally does that part,” I kept saying.</p>
<p>My mom, supervising from the sidelines had caught on to what my husband, to date, hasn’t. “What exactly do <i>you </i>do to cook if Jordy does all this work?”* Oops, I’d been caught. Caught in the act of being a Modern Family.</p>
<p>With both of us working (and two dogs to care for), the “traditional” roles are thrown out the window in my household. We contribute equally (or so I’ve duped my husband into thinking, hehe) when it comes to the household chores. I do my share, but he has taken on a wide range of household tasks, from cooking, to vacuuming, and (in my greatest victory of all), grocery shopping.  On and on his list goes, our modern roles taking shape before our (and my mother’s) very eyes.</p>
<p>The other group to have caught on to the modern family? Tide detergent. Over the holiday weekend, I watched both a holiday movie marathon on Lifetime AND a thrilling Villanova basketball game (victory over Kansas!) on NBC Sports. I saw more Tide laundry detergent commercials on the latter, clearly targeted towards husbands who help around the house. Slowly, I’ve been noticing these ads cropping up. Their messages are heartwarming and humorous, and I love what Proctor &amp; Gamble has done to get there.</p>
<p>Tide and P&amp;G went right back to the basics. They got to know their audience, all over again. It may not be the same audience it’s been since its introduction 67 years ago, and that’s okay. It is one thing to stay where your audience is–social media, mobile devices, Netflix–but entirely  another thing to truly know who your audience is now and will be down the road. It takes work, it takes research, and it takes the ability to not only accept change but to capitalize on it.</p>
<p>Kudos, Tide. I can’t wait to see what happens next time “laundry detergent” is on the grocery list.</p>
<p>*In case you’ve been wondering, my role in the chicken and turkey cooking comes in once the gross handling of raw fowl is complete, and I can season, stuff, smother it in butter and spices, and place it in the oven.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s all about the trust</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/16/2013/its-all-about-the-trust/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 19:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Van Metre]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand consulting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[competitive analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[logo design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3127</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I couldn’t help myself.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I couldn’t help myself. I opened my eyes at 5am one morning, the TV still on from the night before, and what program was on? <em>The Pitch</em>, AMC’s reality show that gives a behind-the-scenes view as two ad agencies vie for a new account. How could I NOT watch?</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-3131" alt="0614_fuller-brush2" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2-147x220.jpg" width="147" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2-147x220.jpg 147w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2.jpg 500w" sizes="(max-width: 147px) 100vw, 147px" /></p>
<p>In this case, the account was The Fuller Brush Company. <em>THE</em> Fuller Brush Company! An iconic brand from my childhood whose distribution channel was The Fuller Brush Man (thousands of them, actually) selling door-to-door-to-door-to-door. Seriously.</p>
<p>Fuller, one of America’s oldest and most trusted brands that was once known by every household in America (and according to my mother, “Made the best toilet brush on the planet,”) is now virtually unknown by anyone under the age of 45. With a new owner who just rescued the 100-year-old company from bankruptcy, the agency assignment was to “reboot the brand for the modern market.” Again, who wouldn’t love this show?</p>
<p>Without going blow by blow through the episode, suffice it to say, I found it both entertaining and a bit unbelievable. Particularly the part when both agencies came up with exactly the same “Live Fuller” concept to build their pitches around. Yeah, kinda’ fishy.</p>
<p>Anyway, the question is, how does CEO David Sabin choose between two agencies <em>that just presented the exact same big idea?</em></p>
<p>My answer (and here comes the lesson): Clients don’t choose agencies based on the creative they pitch. They choose agencies based on whether they can imagine trusting the agency’s people with their brand.</p>
<p>Think about your closest relationships, your best friends. The best ones are those who spend the most time with you, expend the most energy on you, appreciate you and love you just the way you are. And more than likely, they are also the ones whom you allow to carefully, kindly, and almost naturally help you grow into a better version of yourself. Because they are the ones you trust.</p>
<p>In my view, the Monogram agency didn’t win because of their creative execution. They won because they showed the client he could trust them because they took the time to understand. They spent time on research and then shared their views of potential new customers; they first understood and then echoed the client’s love of The Fuller Brush Man icon while recommending a modern makeover; and they even showed personal empathy and appreciation for the quality of the brand by mentioning using a Fuller hairbrush for over 50 years.</p>
<p>Monogram got it. They understood that the pitch wasn’t about the idea, the destination. It was about their process, their journey to understanding – recounting what they did, what they learned and then what they recommended based on years of experience and expertise.</p>
<p>Monogram got it all &#8212; the brand, the client’s trust, and the account.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
