<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>account management &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/account-management/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The new to-do list</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/03/24/2014/the-new-to-do-list/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 15:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3503</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[For other positions within the agency, there always seems to be something &#8220;new&#8221; out there.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For other positions within the agency, there always seems to be something &#8220;new&#8221; out there. Whether it&#8217;s a new web application framework, an update to design software, or even video editing software or techniques. Our developers and designers have to know the latest and greatest technology, learn it, and keep up with it.</p>
<p>But for my role, the good old standbys of email (I guess at one point this was new), a notepad, and a pile of as-brightly-colored-as-possible Post-Its are the tools I rely on each day. I think most account executives would agree that the to-do list is our most important tool for staying on top of everything.</p>
<p>In the absence of technological advances in pen and paper (thank goodness), it&#8217;s up to me to find a better way, and I think maybe I have. I recently read an article on to-do lists, that said in today&#8217;s work environment, they have become somewhat obsolete. Why? Because we put too many items on them. The article suggested that we put no more than 3 items on our to-do list on any given day. And more than that, narrow down the tasks to the <em>first</em> task of each item on that list. That first task actually becomes the to-do; it flows from there.</p>
<p>It seems so counterintuitive — less on my list to get more done? How could that possibly work? And what about all the other stuff I am not getting to?*</p>
<p>Well, I tried it, and guess what? It works.</p>
<p>Not only did I complete my entire to-do list, but I did each job thoroughly, giving it the attention it deserves. This alone lead to a lot less hassle, back and forth, revising and re-working later on. And, I had plenty of room in my day for those requests, questions, and emergencies that never fail to crop up. Here too, I had the time needed to get the job done right the first time.</p>
<p>The beauty of my new to-do list is that it forces me to prioritize. What REALLY has to get done today? That goes on the list. Those other tasks don&#8217;t. And what I&#8217;ve noticed is that those tasks that used to end up moving from day-to-day-to-week usually: a. don&#8217;t need to get done at all because they have sorted themselves out, or b. are part of a bigger project that gets completed when and where they should.</p>
<p>Each night I still get a little bit of anxiety when I write out my list, but I hold myself to the 3-item limit, and am loving the increased productivity.**</p>
<p>*I think my favorite part about the article was that you could have a side list of the little nigglers you don&#8217;t want to forget about. PHEW. At least they have a home, even if I never visit them there.</p>
<p>**Confession, I allow myself up to 5 items, because…well I&#8217;m not <em>that </em>great at adopting new &#8220;technologies&#8221; sometimes. Actually 6 items…one day I just <em>needed</em> 6. But I didn&#8217;t get them all done.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are Super Bowl Ads Worth The Investment?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/30/2014/are-super-bowl-ads-worth-the-investment/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ads]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commercials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Super Bowl XLVIII]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3422</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Super Bowl is more than just a game, it&#8217;s a global event. It&#8217;s the most watched program of the year. Even those who have no idea who the Denver Broncos or the Seattle Seahawks are will tune in. Why? Typically it&#8217;s because everyone else is doing it, but another reason is the advertising. In 2013, the average cost of a 30-second spot was $4 million. The effectiveness of these ads in boosting a company&#8217;s sales has been in question over the past few years. Experts have compared the investment of the cost of an ad vs. overall increased revenue after the Super Bowl, and it shows little to no change. Forbes magazine claims that most companies would be better off airing 10 commercials at $400,000 each, to increase repetition. Forbes also claims that Super Bowl Ads have become memorible for presentation, but forgettable in terms of persuasion.</p>
<p>The University of Wisconsin-Eau Claire <a href="http://www.uwec.edu/newsbureau/release/past/2000/00-01/010400super.html">did a study of over 500 Super Bowl spots that ran between 2000 and 2009</a>, and found that many did not work. Some Super Bowl Ads fail due to the fact that people typically recall the story, but not the product. More often than not, Super Bowl ads attempt to deliver broad humor for entertainment purposes, rather than sell the product. Sometimes companies will enlist celebrities to sponsor their Super Bowl Ad, but experts have also concluded this tactic is ineffective as the celebrity may lack relevance to the product. Still the question must be asked, is the Super Bowl ad worth the investment?</p>
<p>Forbes magazine says yes.</p>
<p>The real reason companies invest in Super Bowl spots is because the announcement of buying airtime for the Super Bowl can boost their stock price, at least in the short term. A business will typically announce their Super Bowl buy weeks prior to the big game, and even debut the advertisement early on social sites such as YouTube, Facebook and Twitter. Experts have found that any positive impact on a businesses stock price comes at the announcement of the Super Bowl spot, not after the spot runs. Whether or not an advertisement is successful is secondary to the impact it has on a business&#8217; exposure in the stock market. So yes, for an enterprise business that can afford the $4,000,000+ on advertising their investment is well worth it.</p>
<p>Whether you watch for the love of the game, advertising, or Peyton Manning––sit back, relax and enjoy the entertainment. It&#8217;ll be a long time until your next fantasy football draft night, and that&#8217;s depressing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Modern Family, and What it Means for Advertisers</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/02/2013/the-modern-family-and-what-it-means-for-advertisers/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[audience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[modern family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proctor & Gamble]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thanksgiving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3322</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year, I got to make the Thanksgiving turkey. I prepared with two practice rounds in early November, roasting whole chickens for my husband and me. I was ready.</p>
<p>On the big day, as my dad read each instruction for turkey prep–remove gizzards, rinse turkey, pat dry, lay on roasting rack, rub salt–<del cite="mailto:Michael%20Garcia" datetime="2013-12-02T09:23"></del>a refrain began to take shape. “Oh, Jordy normally does that part,” I kept saying.</p>
<p>My mom, supervising from the sidelines had caught on to what my husband, to date, hasn’t. “What exactly do <i>you </i>do to cook if Jordy does all this work?”* Oops, I’d been caught. Caught in the act of being a Modern Family.</p>
<p>With both of us working (and two dogs to care for), the “traditional” roles are thrown out the window in my household. We contribute equally (or so I’ve duped my husband into thinking, hehe) when it comes to the household chores. I do my share, but he has taken on a wide range of household tasks, from cooking, to vacuuming, and (in my greatest victory of all), grocery shopping.  On and on his list goes, our modern roles taking shape before our (and my mother’s) very eyes.</p>
<p>The other group to have caught on to the modern family? Tide detergent. Over the holiday weekend, I watched both a holiday movie marathon on Lifetime AND a thrilling Villanova basketball game (victory over Kansas!) on NBC Sports. I saw more Tide laundry detergent commercials on the latter, clearly targeted towards husbands who help around the house. Slowly, I’ve been noticing these ads cropping up. Their messages are heartwarming and humorous, and I love what Proctor &amp; Gamble has done to get there.</p>
<p>Tide and P&amp;G went right back to the basics. They got to know their audience, all over again. It may not be the same audience it’s been since its introduction 67 years ago, and that’s okay. It is one thing to stay where your audience is–social media, mobile devices, Netflix–but entirely  another thing to truly know who your audience is now and will be down the road. It takes work, it takes research, and it takes the ability to not only accept change but to capitalize on it.</p>
<p>Kudos, Tide. I can’t wait to see what happens next time “laundry detergent” is on the grocery list.</p>
<p>*In case you’ve been wondering, my role in the chicken and turkey cooking comes in once the gross handling of raw fowl is complete, and I can season, stuff, smother it in butter and spices, and place it in the oven.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s all about the trust</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/16/2013/its-all-about-the-trust/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 19:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Van Metre]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand consulting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand workshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[competitive analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[logo design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategic planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3127</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I couldn’t help myself.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I couldn’t help myself. I opened my eyes at 5am one morning, the TV still on from the night before, and what program was on? <em>The Pitch</em>, AMC’s reality show that gives a behind-the-scenes view as two ad agencies vie for a new account. How could I NOT watch?</p>
<p><img class="alignleft size-medium wp-image-3131" alt="0614_fuller-brush2" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2-147x220.jpg" width="147" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2-147x220.jpg 147w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/0614_fuller-brush2.jpg 500w" sizes="(max-width: 147px) 100vw, 147px" /></p>
<p>In this case, the account was The Fuller Brush Company. <em>THE</em> Fuller Brush Company! An iconic brand from my childhood whose distribution channel was The Fuller Brush Man (thousands of them, actually) selling door-to-door-to-door-to-door. Seriously.</p>
<p>Fuller, one of America’s oldest and most trusted brands that was once known by every household in America (and according to my mother, “Made the best toilet brush on the planet,”) is now virtually unknown by anyone under the age of 45. With a new owner who just rescued the 100-year-old company from bankruptcy, the agency assignment was to “reboot the brand for the modern market.” Again, who wouldn’t love this show?</p>
<p>Without going blow by blow through the episode, suffice it to say, I found it both entertaining and a bit unbelievable. Particularly the part when both agencies came up with exactly the same “Live Fuller” concept to build their pitches around. Yeah, kinda’ fishy.</p>
<p>Anyway, the question is, how does CEO David Sabin choose between two agencies <em>that just presented the exact same big idea?</em></p>
<p>My answer (and here comes the lesson): Clients don’t choose agencies based on the creative they pitch. They choose agencies based on whether they can imagine trusting the agency’s people with their brand.</p>
<p>Think about your closest relationships, your best friends. The best ones are those who spend the most time with you, expend the most energy on you, appreciate you and love you just the way you are. And more than likely, they are also the ones whom you allow to carefully, kindly, and almost naturally help you grow into a better version of yourself. Because they are the ones you trust.</p>
<p>In my view, the Monogram agency didn’t win because of their creative execution. They won because they showed the client he could trust them because they took the time to understand. They spent time on research and then shared their views of potential new customers; they first understood and then echoed the client’s love of The Fuller Brush Man icon while recommending a modern makeover; and they even showed personal empathy and appreciation for the quality of the brand by mentioning using a Fuller hairbrush for over 50 years.</p>
<p>Monogram got it. They understood that the pitch wasn’t about the idea, the destination. It was about their process, their journey to understanding – recounting what they did, what they learned and then what they recommended based on years of experience and expertise.</p>
<p>Monogram got it all &#8212; the brand, the client’s trust, and the account.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How a starfish sparked an idea</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/02/2013/how-a-starfish-sparked-an-idea/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 17:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Alexandra Pickel]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3066</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I was beaming.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="attachment_3104" style="max-width: 175px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img class="size-medium wp-image-3104" alt="Isn't she adorable?!" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-165x220.jpeg" width="165" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-165x220.jpeg 165w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/photo-e1381771767340-768x1024.jpeg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 165px) 100vw, 165px" /><p class="wp-caption-text">Isn&#8217;t she adorable?!</p></div>
<p>I was beaming. My favorite family member (don’t tell my husband), Macy, had just graduated from Puppy Kindergarten with flying colors, and she was totally into the toy I bought her for a congratulatory present. So into it, in fact, that I immediately logged on to the company’s website to hunt for more. Because, you know, her 5 ½-month birthday is just around the corner.</p>
<p>And there it was: “Become a Dog Toy Tester.” The deal was, sign up to receive four toys a year. Agree to write a review and you get those toys at 40% off. 40% off toys Macy loves? And I get to share stories of my puppy with the entire world? What’s not to love?</p>
<p>At that exact same time, our B2B client was looking to increase reviews of products on their website. The strategy was an Apple product giveaway—always a great incentive, but what about giving the actual products away at a discount in return for a review? You better believe that in the long run, it’s going to sell more product. Here’s why it works:</p>
<p>1. It shows customers you value their opinion, which creates loyalty.<br />
2. It gives customers more of what they need. Sure, an iPad mini is great, but that product I was going to buy anyway? I need that.<br />
3. The discount encourages customers to try new products—if it doesn’t work out, at least they didn’t pay full price.<br />
4. It’s less hassle on your end. No need to run complex sweepstakes giveaways, partner with third parties, jump through legal hoops, or figure out complex rules.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A to-do list app</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/09/16/2013/a-to-do-list-app/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 15:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3090</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[As an account exec, I’m not only responsible for client communication—there’s a lot of internal communication and project management to juggle, too.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As an account exec, I’m not only responsible for client communication—there’s a lot of internal communication and project management to juggle, too. With an endless list of things to manage, I decided to test drive the Asana project management app. It’s an extremely intuitive tool for traffic, project and account managers—an interactive alternative to the daily written checklist.</p>
<p>I found the app to be useful as I was able to track projects in a mobile environment as I moved throughout the agency and spoke to different people involved in my projects. The app’s coolest feature was its ability to seamlessly update itself through several sources without need for refreshing. For example, as I clicked &#8220;project complete&#8221; on my iPhone, it would update itself on the desktop version, too.</p>
<p>Another helpful feature is &#8220;team sharing&#8221;. If my co-workers were to download the app and enter their individual projects, we could share access to each other’s environments and answer status questions, without having to physically tracking each other down.</p>
<p>Of course, FVM is a small, close-knit agency. The Keurig machine sits farther away from me than the creative department, so I’ll continue using my manual method of project management. But for those working in larger agencies, this app could be extremely helpful.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter is advancing: Are you?</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/05/2012/twitter-is-advancing-are-you/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 18:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[FVM]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[account planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[search engine optimization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[twitter]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=2416</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The debate over Twitter’s place in modern day culture is complex –some people mock it and some people tweet it.  But one thing’s for sure: businesses are benefitting immensely from the social networking site.  Without a doubt, Twitter has allowed businesses to grow their brands, extend customer service, boost SEO performance and the list goes [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The debate over Twitter’s place in modern day culture is complex –some people mock it and some people tweet it.  But one thing’s for sure: businesses are benefitting immensely from the social networking site.  Without a doubt, Twitter has allowed businesses to grow their brands, extend customer service, boost SEO performance and the list goes on.  Whether you’re the type of person who scans Twitter every hour for celebrity perspectives on life or you’re doing life just fine without Twitter , you will have difficulty in trying to argue against Twitter’s long list of benefits to a business’s success.</p>
<p>We can tackle all the specific benefits more in-depth at another time (or visit this <a href="http://www.ragan.com/Main/Articles/15_business_benefits_of_Twitter__44058.aspx">Ragan article</a> for a quick review), but what I want to convey immediately is that <strong>now</strong> is the time for businesses to immerse themselves.  There’s a new door opening to join (if you haven’t already) or to improve your Twitter ROI.</p>
<h2>Twitter is changing in big ways, fast</h2>
<p>In December, Twitter launched branded pages.  If you are unaware of this development, you’ll want to review Twitter’s <a href="https://business.twitter.com/advertise/enhanced-profile/">Enhanced Profile</a> help page.  Basically, in December, Twitter launched a branded page as an option, which “increases your brand’s Twitter presence by prominently featuring your most important content and visually branding your page.”</p>
<p>With the enhanced profile pages in mind, Twitter is now moving forward with a new focus on creating a new “experience,” both for businesses and their customers.  In my mind two major developments capture this new focus entirely.</p>
<h3>1. The Open Platform</h3>
<p>Twitter’s end goal with an open platform is to create new ways for customers to engage with your brand.  The industry’s majority agrees with <a href="http://www.readwriteweb.com/archives/author/richard-macmanus.php">Richard Macmanus</a> in that open web services is a major web trend picking up and Twitter’s new API (Application Program Inteface) is an ideal platform to see the advantages.  By opening their platform to independent developers, Twitter allows “brands to create deeper interactions with consumers through custom experiences,” says Mashable’s David Clarke.  From smaller mobile applications to versions of Twitter visually recreated, developers now have the capability to build onto Twitter’s infrastructure and expand the user’s experience exponentially.  A brand is not limited to its look and feel living on Twitter.  You can now combine Twitter’s functions with your own ideas.  Biz Stone says &#8220;The API has been … inarguably, the most important thing we’ve done with Twitter.”</p>
<h3>2. T-Commerce</h3>
<p>Facebook failed at it, now Twitter will attempt to succeed where it’s adversary failed.  E-commerce on Twitter has pronounced itself loud and clear just recently with multiple real opportunities for e-commerce companies that you’ve probably overlooked.</p>
<ul>
<li>First and foremost, the most easily forgotten, the <strong>call-to-action</strong>: you must provide a link in every tweet.  If someone is interested in a product or service, make sure you’ve given them a way to act.</li>
<li>Provide great customer service. Everything is public, so customers will gain trust that you will stand by your offerings.</li>
<li>Pay on Twitter.  Yes, customers can now pay directly via Twitter.  This will expedite purchasing process and reduce consumer hesitation.  Look into <a href="http://chirpify.com/">Cherpify</a> and Twitpay.</li>
</ul>
<p>Are you currently using Twitter to help grow your business and reach customers?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
