<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Russell Falk &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/blog/author/rfalk/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Archer: The visual brand</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/03/05/2015/archer-the-visual-brand/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4986</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[FVM recently rebranded Market Street Advisors as Archer. Working with the financial services software company through research, value proposition, architecture, naming, tone of voice, and design was a great experience.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FVM recently rebranded Market Street Advisors as Archer. Working with the financial services software company through research, value proposition, architecture, naming, tone of voice, and design was a great experience. Our process resulted in a strong, modern and consistent brand designed to give Archer an edge in the market, and it’s something we’re proud of.</p>
<p>While the strategic concepts, rationale and writing were developed by our senior leadership cadre, creating Archer’s visual brand fell on my desk. Now that the brand’s launch is in our rear view mirror and our <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/work/portfolio_post/archer/" target="_blank">case study</a> is up, I can offer a peek behind the design curtain.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5220" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/logo-tag-lockup1.jpg" alt="logo-tag-lockup1" width="996" height="439" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/logo-tag-lockup1.jpg 996w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/logo-tag-lockup1-220x97.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 996px) 100vw, 996px" /></p>
<p>The Archer logo is a simple geometric sans-serif wordmark. The R’s slightly exaggerated bowl hints at the opulence of early 20<sup>th</sup>-century typographic styles, and the flourishes on the A and C—symbolizing an arrow drawn tight in its bow and aimed at its target—provide a modern flair. The bright, gradated color compliments Archer&#8217;s warm, friendly and dynamic personality.</p>
<p>I spent days creating and refining round after round of logo concepts, and we were so happy with that work that we struggled separating the wheat from the chaff. We explored a variety of icon-based treatments, and though I always intended on offering some purely typographic marks, a case of severe creative block saw several design rounds come and go before this solution made it up on our creative room’s wall.</p>
<p>Although the C-as-target glyph looks like a self-evident basis for the mark, it was actually the A that initiated the thinking behind this design. Like many of my designs, the idea for the A’s displaced crossbar rudely shoved its way into my head while brushing my teeth late one evening, and the initial sketches were created into the early morning hours in my home office. The target-C was actually not in the first versions at all. The logo’s final state may seem like an obvious solution, but the creative process is often more tangled.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5222" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/archer-logo-sketch.jpg" alt="archer-logo-sketch" width="1000" height="333" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/archer-logo-sketch.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/archer-logo-sketch-220x73.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Once the wordmark was resolved, the rest of the brand’s visuals poured forth more easily. Patterns, icons, illustrations, and other visual elements utilize similar geometric primitives and echo the construction of Archer&#8217;s distinctive A. Continuing the geometric motif, type is set in Proxima Nova and Lubalin Graph at mostly lighter weights with generous spacing to create and open, approachable impression. We balanced the somewhat recessive type treatments and straightforward copywriting with a bold, energetic color palette to arrive at the brand’s full personality.</p>
<h6>Value proposition and personality<br />
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5223" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/valueprop-personality.jpg" alt="valueprop-personality" width="1000" height="1000" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/valueprop-personality.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/valueprop-personality-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/valueprop-personality-220x220.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></h6>
<p>Like the wordmark, Archer’s secondary blue was also a late arrival in the creative process, but one that I think rounds out the palette and lends a bit of sobriety to the otherwise loud visual impression of orange, purple and black.</p>
<h6>Digital properties<br />
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5224" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/digital-mockups.jpg" alt="digital-mockups" width="996" height="787" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/digital-mockups.jpg 996w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/digital-mockups-220x174.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 996px) 100vw, 996px" /></h6>
<h6><strong>Business card<br />
</strong><strong><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5225" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/archer-business-card-mockup.jpg" alt="archer-business-card-mockup" width="700" height="467" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/archer-business-card-mockup.jpg 700w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/archer-business-card-mockup-220x147.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></strong></h6>
<h6>Visual brand elements<br />
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-5226" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/visual-assets.jpg" alt="visual-assets" width="1000" height="1000" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/visual-assets.jpg 1000w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/visual-assets-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/visual-assets-220x220.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></h6>
<p>When viewed against the more traditional visual branding of others in the investment management sector, our approach positions Archer as a bold, new and forward-thinking competitor. However, <a href="#http://archerims.com/">the landing page that introduced Archer is just the beginning</a>. We’re now kicking off a more comprehensive web design process to build Archer’s modest digital presence into a full site, and I’m excited to see how the brand ultimately lends itself to a fuller, more robust interactive experience. So stay tuned, as I’m sure we’ll have more to show of Archer’s creative development in the coming months.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I know your type</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/07/2014/spark-of-design-i-know-your-type/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 17:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=4316</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Can you instantly spot the difference between Helvetica and Arial?]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Can you instantly <a href="http://www.ironicsans.com/helvarialquiz/index.php" target="_blank">spot the difference between Helvetica and Arial</a>? Do you know your transitional serifs from your didones? Do you feel a slight twinge of pain when someone says “font” instead of “typeface”? If the answer’s no, then you probably work in client services. But to designers, this stuff’s important. Type is vital in grabbing and retaining reader attention, and reinforces the meaning of text. So here’s some hot new type as part of our new regular Spark series &#8211; providing industry inspiration and insight from FVMers.</p>
<p>The League of Moveable Type – one of the best type foundries and purveyors of high quality open source typefaces – recently unveiled their newest face, <a href="https://www.theleagueofmoveabletype.com/league-spartan" target="_blank">League Spartan</a>.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4318" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/league-spartan-2.jpg" alt="league-spartan-2" width="820" height="300" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/league-spartan-2.jpg 820w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/league-spartan-2-220x80.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 820px) 100vw, 820px" /></p>
<p>It&#8217;s an excellently crafted geometric sans that bares a healthy resemblance to Futura without seeming trapped in the mid-20th century. I&#8217;ve already started experimenting with it as the base for custom wordmarks in some logo work and have found it extremely useable. For motion designers, there&#8217;s also an animated version available from <a href="http://animography.net/products/league-spartan" target="_blank">Animography</a> for an affordable price.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4325" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/01_LS_Specimen_uppercase_1024x1024.jpg" alt="01_LS_Specimen_uppercase_1024x1024" width="1024" height="576" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/01_LS_Specimen_uppercase_1024x1024.jpg 1024w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/01_LS_Specimen_uppercase_1024x1024-220x123.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4319" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/02_LS_Specimen_lowercase_1024x1024.jpg" alt="02_LS_Specimen_lowercase_1024x1024" width="1024" height="576" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/02_LS_Specimen_lowercase_1024x1024.jpg 1024w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/02_LS_Specimen_lowercase_1024x1024-220x123.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>Much like the development of the Raleway family, the League has released a single weight under an open source license and will likely be looking for contributions from the design community to help build out a fuller collection of styles and weights. So if you&#8217;re aspiring to be the next Tobias Frere-Jones, fork it on <a href="https://github.com/theleagueof/league-spartan">GitHub</a> and get busy.</p>
<p>Speaking of TFJ, it seems that his <a href="http://www.fastcodesign.com/3036423/type-stars-jonathan-hoefler-and-tobias-frere-jones-settle-their-bitter-lawsuit" target="_blank">very messy and public breakup with Jonathan Hoefler</a> is finally drawing to a close, and it&#8217;s good to see that he&#8217;ll be getting some recompense for his efforts on behalf of perhaps the most influential type foundry of our time. Tobias has been blogging <a href="http://www.frerejones.com">here</a>, posting beautiful examples of the world&#8217;s best type design as he moves on to his next endeavor.</p>
<p>Oh yeah, while we’re talking about type design, let me squeeze this in: <a href="http://scottyfivealive.com/Exhibitions-The-Distance-Between-Two-Points" target="_blank">The Distance Between Two Points</a></p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-4317" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/Type.jpg" alt="Type" width="600" height="400" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Type.jpg 600w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/Type-220x146.jpg 220w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></p>
<p>The exhibition by Scott Albrecht explores time, perception and interconnectivity, and is on display at Art In The Age Of Mechanical Reproduction in Old City, Philadelphia through the end of October. I saw the opening night and it comes highly recommended.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Real branding from a fictional world</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/06/11/2014/real-branding-from-a-fictional-world/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 18:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3861</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[As brands become an ever more prevalent aspect of our cultural landscape, works of present-day fiction demand increasingly well-crafted identities and applications for the imaginary commercial ventures that populate those worlds.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As brands become an ever more prevalent aspect of our cultural landscape, works of present-day fiction demand increasingly well-crafted identities and applications for the imaginary commercial ventures that populate those worlds. Fictional brands are an interest of mine (as comedian George Carlin said, &#8220;hobbies cost money; interests are quite free&#8221;), and from time to time I&#8217;ll be writing here about the most successful and purposeful ones I encounter.</p>
<p>Before we get to the good stuff, I should qualify what I mean by purposeful. Many celebrated fictional brands, despite their cult status, are trivial in context. They serve mostly as directorial signatures (<a href="http://wiki.tarantino.info/index.php/Red_Apple_cigarettes" target="_blank">Red Apple Cigarettes</a>) or wink-nudge jokes for the most savvy audiences (<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Finder-Spyder" target="_blank">Finder-Spyder</a>, <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oceanic_Airlines" target="_blank">Oceanic Airlines</a>). I&#8217;m more interested in those that perform important functions in establishing set and setting (<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QYy80trSPSI" target="_blank">Quietus</a>), or more still ones that play central roles in character development or plot (<a href="http://www.tryablixa.com/" target="_blank">Ablixa</a>).</p>
<p>I recently saw <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1205537/" target="_blank">&#8220;Jack Ryan: Shadow Recruit&#8221;</a>, the latest addition to the Tom Clancy canon. One of the more delightful things about the movie was the range and polish of the applications for Cherevin, a Russian financial firm at the center of a plot to collapse the US dollar, named for its chief, Viktor Cherevin (played with expert menace by Kenneth Branagh).</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/logo.gif" class="swipebox"><img src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/logo.gif" alt="logo" width="800" height="531" /></a></p>
<p>The Cherevin logo itself, a brooding geometric monogram that looks to be the lovechild of <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Enron_Logo.svg" target="_blank">Enron</a> and <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Omni_Consumer_Products_(RoboCop)#Omni_Consumer_Products" target="_blank">Omni Consumer Products</a>, is rational and unfeeling, conjuring up Cold War fears of opaque foreign bureaucracy. The wordmark is never shown in its entirety on screen, but I&#8217;ve attempted to recreate it based on the portion that is visible and other instances of similar Cyrillic lettering that appear throughout the movie.<img src="file:///Users/mgarcia/Downloads/package/apps1.jpg" alt="" /></p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/apps1.jpg" class="swipebox"><img src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/apps1.jpg" alt="apps1" width="800" height="1028" /></a></p>
<p>Of course, there is the standard array of logo-on-stuff applications &#8211; the side of a building, a lobby sculpture, brushed metal key cards, frosted glass doors, spinning 3D screensavers, you get the idea. Its sturdy diamond construction is easily recognizable even out of focus, so when a file folder is passed around or a uniformed officer runs past, the vague impression of the shape is enough to signal to the audience this document is not trustworthy or the bad guy owns the cops.</p>
<p>This diamond structure &#8211; hard edges, perpendicular lines, 45 degree angles &#8211; can be seen pervasively throughout the movie&#8217;s set and prop design, and it’s in this area that the more inventive interpretations really shine. The logo is repeated and rotated to generate an elegant pattern that adorns office walls and smartphone backgrounds. The UI on a security guard&#8217;s computer incorporates a diagonal grid and a bevy of aggressive diamond-shaped icons and cursors. Even Cherevin&#8217;s office building has diamond support structures around the exterior. The resulting impression is monolithic, oppressive: Cherevin is everywhere&#8230;and it’s ruthlessly on brand.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/apps2.jpg" class="swipebox"><img src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/apps2.jpg" alt="apps2" width="800" height="1375" /></a></p>
<p>Perhaps the most unique and outlandish implementation comes in the movie&#8217;s closing moments during a visualization of a brute-force computer hack. The logo becomes a hollow, deconstructed wireframe that spins about as it slowly fills in and reassembles itself in pixelated chunks, much like watching a hard drive defragment or 3D animation software render an image in buckets. It&#8217;s clearly nothing like real hacking, but it&#8217;s simple for the viewer to gather what&#8217;s happening. Like the other UIs in the movie, it&#8217;s in full-on angry computer mode, echoing the personality of Branagh&#8217;s antagonist.<img src="file:///Users/mgarcia/Downloads/package/hack.gif" alt="" /></p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/hack.gif" class="swipebox"><img src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/hack.gif" alt="hack" width="800" height="331" /></a></p>
<p>Cherevin may be the evil aggressors of economic warfare, but I&#8217;d love to have them as a client. They could teach me about propping up housing markets, and I might be able to offer them a nugget or two about reducing security breaches through better interaction design. Plus, I bet it&#8217;s fun to get a project brief with the objective of &#8216;instilling fear and obedience.&#8217;</p>
<p>You can check out more images below. Hopefully that&#8217;s enough to hold you over until the inevitable remake of Patriot Games.<img src="file:///Users/mgarcia/Downloads/package/extra.jpg" alt="" /></p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/extra.jpg" class="swipebox"><img src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/extra.jpg" alt="extra" width="800" height="1028" /></a></p>
<p>All images in this post are the intellectual property of Paramount Pictures/Skydance Productions and are published here in fair use.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aether&#8217;s attention to detail helps create a world class brand</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/02/11/2014/aethers-attention-to-valuable-details-helps-create-a-world-class-brand/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aether]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Branding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Design]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3495</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Aether Apparel makes, among other things, absurdly comfortable and great-fitting hooded sweatshirts.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.aetherapparel.com/" target="_blank">Aether Apparel</a> makes, among other things, absurdly comfortable and great-fitting hooded sweatshirts. I&#8217;ve recommended them to friends. An old girlfriend tried to steal mine. Earlier this fall I went back for a second. If you stop by FVM&#8217;s offices this winter, there&#8217;s a decent chance I&#8217;ll be wearing one and you can try it on. But for now, I can share with you the gorgeous presentation they put on with their packaging. With a few small touches, they make an impression much more in line with a high-end lifestyle or fashion brand than with a typical sportswear outfitter.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/journal1.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-3496" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/journal1-220x146.jpg" alt="journal1" width="220" height="146" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/journal1-220x146.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/journal1.jpg 800w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a></p>
<p>For me, the real centerpiece of an Aether package, other than the item ordered of course, is the Aether Journal, a fold-out 16 page zine of redesigned <a href="http://www.aetherapparel.com/journal/" target="_blank">content from their blog and newsletter</a>. It&#8217;s printed on a lightly textured medium-weight matte stock that compliments the muted tones of their photography. The issue I received contains behind-the-scenes looks at how they designed a motorcycle jacket and a retail space; features on traveling the Peruvian Amazon, reading clouds to spot warm fronts, and rock climber Beverly Johnson; and product reviews of a foldable kayak and bike shelves &#8211; items Aether doesn&#8217;t sell but which their customers are likely to find interesting. Before receiving the Journal, I wasn&#8217;t inclined to look at their blog at all, but it was the little bit of encouragement I needed. Its content is similar but reveals additional interests in industrial design and architecture, and to my surprise links to other sites I regularly visit like <a href="http://www.thefoxisblack.com/" target="_blank">The Fox Is Black</a>. The whole experience deftly signals that the people behind Aether have interests similar to mine, or at least know their customers well and are happy to cater to them beyond simply promoting their own goods.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/allthings.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-3497" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/allthings-220x220.jpg" alt="allthings" width="220" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/allthings-220x220.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/allthings-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/allthings.jpg 800w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a></p>
<p>Other details are maybe a bit less impressive on their own but together create a cohesive and perhaps even sophisticated feel: a catalog with attractive full-bleed photography and neatly drawn icons; a heavyweight envelope/sleeve containing the receipt, order information and return labels; a thick, solid clothing tag attached with rope and some sort of safety pin that I&#8217;ve never seen before (always good not to have to find scissors). The icing on the cake is a synthetic cloth tote bag containing all of the package&#8217;s contents. Granted, I was already a satisfied repeat customer, but the care and attention to detail they put into the peripheral elements of their packaging helps to create a strong, unique brand and goes a long way to making me fan for life.</p>
<p><img src="file:///Users/mgarcia/Downloads/blog-content/allthings.jpg" alt="" /></p>
<p>What can a marketer learn here? The lesson isn&#8217;t that you need to print your blog or put your stuff in a tote bag. It&#8217;s that you don&#8217;t always need to reimagine your product or overhaul your identity to take your brand to the next level. Sometimes, the difference between forgettably average and memorably extraordinary is just a few seemingly minor details. Look for new ways to make what you&#8217;re already doing more valuable to your audience. Show your customers you know who they are, that you care about their experience, and that maybe you have something in common. Of course, if you need a little assistance, <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/contact/">FVM can help you get started</a>.</p>
<p>Check out some more photos of Aether&#8217;s packaging materials below:</p>
<p><img src="file:///Users/mgarcia/Downloads/blog-content/catalog.jpg" alt="" /> <img src="file:///Users/mgarcia/Downloads/blog-content/tag.jpg" alt="" /> <img src="file:///Users/mgarcia/Downloads/blog-content/journal2.jpg" alt="" /><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-3498" style="line-height: 1.5em;" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/catalog-220x146.jpg" alt="catalog" width="220" height="146" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/catalog-220x146.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/catalog.jpg 800w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/tag.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-3499" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/tag-220x146.jpg" alt="tag" width="220" height="146" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/tag-220x146.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/tag.jpg 800w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/journal2.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-3500" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/journal2-220x146.jpg" alt="journal2" width="220" height="146" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/journal2-220x146.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/journal2.jpg 800w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sports Authority Holiday Spot Hits the Right Notes</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/12/13/2013/sports-authority-holiday-spot-hits-the-right-notes/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 07:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brand Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[corporate identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holiday]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Authority]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video production]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3311</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I caught this ad for Sports Authority during a recent Clippers-Thunder game and it tugged at me in a way that few commercials do.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><iframe width="500" height="281" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/5K9GPJiRLno?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>I caught this ad for Sports Authority during a recent Clippers-Thunder game and it tugged at me in a way that few commercials do. I&#8217;m not a Luddite, fanatical holiday shopper, or obsessive sports fan. I just appreciate a nice message that captures something pertinent about our time, and this one does.</p>
<p>In addition to the usual annual slate of electronics, this holiday season sees the arrival of two new video game consoles, which are now released every six years or so. At the same time, culturally we seem to be more and more experiencing a sort of post-tech-explosion malaise. For many people, the honeymoon bliss of social networks and mobile computing is fading and they&#8217;re trying to reconnect with the more organic joys in life.</p>
<p>With all that in mind, this ad from <a href="http://www.factorylabs.com/" target="_blank">Factory Design Lab</a> seems especially well-timed and on-point. So well done, guys. I don&#8217;t have any kids to give basketballs to, but if I did, I&#8217;d have to give it some serious thought.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Go easy on the eyes</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/10/05/2013/go-easy-on-the-eyes/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 19:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Russell Falk]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BBEdit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CSS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[digital strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HTML]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Notepad++]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TextWrangler]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[web development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://3dot0.fvm.d1.fvm.sc/?p=3019</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The other day as I was working on the newly-redesigned Faith In The Future Foundation website, FVM Sr.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The other day as I was working on the <a href="http://www.faithinthefuture.com" target="_blank">newly-redesigned Faith In The Future Foundation website</a>, FVM Sr. Art Director Mark Parker idled for a moment as he strolled past my desk and made the following comment:</p>
<p>&#8220;I can&#8217;t believe you like to code like that.&#8221;</p>
<p>Code like what? I thought I was doing it correctly. Not so. He was of course referring to TextWrangler&#8217;s default color settings, which, though not deal-breaking, do leave something to be desired. I tried to justify my nonchalant (read: negligent) attitude towards optimizing my workspace, but he remained unimpressed and, if I was being honest with myself, my position was defensible only by laziness.</p>
<div id="attachment_3020" style="max-width: 230px" class="wp-caption alignright"><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-1.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="size-medium wp-image-3020 " alt="In TextWrangler's factory settings, attribute names and values are actually different colors, but you wouldn't know from looking..." src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-1-220x220.jpg" width="220" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-1-220x220.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-1-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-1.jpg 425w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">In TextWrangler&#8217;s factory settings, attribute names and values are actually different colors, but you wouldn&#8217;t know from looking&#8230;</p></div>
<p>One of the few things I miss about my old Windows-based workstation is <a href="http://notepad-plus-plus.org" target="_blank">Notepad++</a>, with its granular syntax highlighting options and slew of built in color schemes that make changing it up a breeze (although even the default settings look good). TextWrangler ostensibly has but two options: the factory settings, or customizing each color manually. You can, however, add color preference files to the ~/Library/Application Support/TextWrangler/Color Schemes/ directory and then activate them using the preset dropdown in the Text Colors preferences menu from within TextWrangler. In newer versions of OS X, the user Library folder is hidden by default, so you&#8217;ll need to use the Terminal or hit Go &gt; Go to Folder in the Finder.</p>
<p>Overhearing our conversation, our new developer, Kat Sioson, suggested <a href="http://www.andrewhazelden.com/blog/2012/06/midnight-blue-color-scheme-for-textwrangler-and-bbedit/" target="_blank">Andrew Hazelden&#8217;s Midnight Blue color scheme for BBEdit and TextWrangler</a>, and soon I was knee deep in the world of user-created color schemes. You can find a good entry point <a href="http://bbeditextras.org/wiki/index.php?title=Color_Schemes" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
<p>I found Midnight Blue to be pretty good though I modified it so that general markup is a different color than plain text. I&#8217;m particularly fond of <a href="http://ethanschoonover.com/solarized" target="_blank">Ethan Schoonover&#8217;s Solarized Dark</a>, which is available, along with a Light counterpart, for a variety of applications beyond those from Bare Bones Software.</p>
<p>In the spirit of giving back, I figured I&#8217;d add my own contribution &#8211; <a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FVM-Color-Schemes.zip" target="_blank">FVM Dark</a>, which uses the tones on our newly-redesigned agency website.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/FVM-Color-Schemes.zip">FVM-Color-Schemes</a></p>
<p>I spend the bulk of my coding time working with HTML and CSS, so if you spend more time with Javascript, Ruby, Python, etc., you may find it needs some tweaking. Just drag and drop the colors around until you find something that works for you.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-3.jpg" class="swipebox"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-3021" alt="image-3" src="http://www.thinkfvm.com/wp-content/uploads/image-3-220x220.jpg" width="220" height="220" srcset="http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-3-220x220.jpg 220w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-3-80x80.jpg 80w, http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/wp-content/uploads/image-3.jpg 425w" sizes="(max-width: 220px) 100vw, 220px" /></a><br />
If you&#8217;re in the mood for a more seasonally appropriate work environment, also included in that archive is an Autumn color scheme I put together as well, inspired by the foliage outside our offices. Happy coding!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
