<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Deadliest Catch &#8211; FVM</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/thinkfvm/tag/deadliest-catch/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm</link>
	<description>B2B Marketing and Advertising Agency in Philadelphia</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 16:26:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>So, I&#8217;m a Marketing Nerd!</title>
		<link>http://localhost:8888/thinkfvm/blog/01/20/2014/so-im-a-marketing-nerd/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 14:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Karen Murphy]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Everything]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FVM Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deadliest Catch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[market research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marketing strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[media planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TLC]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.thinkfvm.com/?p=3300</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[While watching Deadliest Catch on the Discovery Channel with my husband one night a few months ago, I started noticing a pattern.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While watching <i>Deadliest Catch</i> on the Discovery Channel with my husband one night a few months ago, I started noticing a pattern. During every commercial break, we were assaulted with commercials for men’s products: Ford F-150 pickup trucks, razors with four blades for a closer shave, Slim Jims–the list goes on.</p>
<p>I laughed out loud and said, &#8220;Oh man, I guess I&#8217;m not in the target market for <i>this </i>show. I love when that happens! I feel like I&#8217;m beating the system!&#8221; I expected my husband to chuckle and agree. Instead, he looked at me like I had three heads and said, &#8220;What?&#8221;</p>
<p>I realized, then, that not everybody in the world notices or pays attention when they&#8217;re being marketed to. For the first time, I felt special as a professional working in marketing.  Over the next few weeks I noticed that I really do find it fun to determine if I am inside or outside the target market for the products or services I&#8217;m being marketed.</p>
<p>Here are a few examples:</p>
<ul>
<li>On a random weekday home sick, I was watching <i>The Price is Right</i> on CBS. Denture cleaner–Nope!  Nice try, marketers, but thankfully I have all my teeth!  Scooter Store–Nope!  Emergency Life Alert button–Nope!  Pampers Cruisers diapers…OK, you got me on that one.  Touché, marketers.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Checking my Email: Groupon to Niagra Falls–Nope!  Adidas Men&#8217;s Golf Shoes–Nope!  50% off on preschool portraits…wait, let me see that one.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Watching <i>What Not to Wear</i> on TLC, while folding laundry on a Saturday afternoon: OK, I admit, I am 100% in the center circle of TLC&#8217;s target market diagram.  Whatever I see a commercial for, I want to buy, to watch, to check out.  Way to go, TLC, you found me!</li>
</ul>
<p>Marketers have a different way of looking at the world–of breaking down human behavior and trying to understand, at the core, what moves and motivates people. I am happy to consider myself part of this group of professionals. I feel at home in this little world because it&#8217;s really interesting to me. I am also happy that I&#8217;m not tasked with advertising to smart-ass marketers like myself!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
